<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Updates on Snoonet</title><link>http://localhost:1313/</link><description>Recent content in Updates on Snoonet</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 21:43:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Key</title><link>http://localhost:1313/anope/key/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 22:31:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/anope/key/</guid><description>&amp;lt;these brackets&amp;gt; denote required information.
{these brackets} denote that you may pick one of the options presented.
[these brackets] denote entirely optional parameters.
Command Optional Alias /msg NickServ [COMMAND] /ns [COMMAND] /msg ChanServ [COMMAND] /cs [COMMAND] /msg MemoServ [COMMAND] /ms [COMMAND] /msg BotServ [COMMAND] /bs [COMMAND]</description></item><item><title>Matching Extbans</title><link>http://localhost:1313/extbans/matching_extbans/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 22:31:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/extbans/matching_extbans/</guid><description> Name Syntax Effect Oper O:[operlevel] Matches the opertype. Can accept wildcards for all opers Account R:[account] Matches the service account. Accepts a wildcard Unregistered U:[ban] Matches an unregistered user who matches the [ban] Channel j:[state][#channel] Matches a user in the channel. State defines the user&amp;rsquo;s level, such as +, %, or @ Gecos (realname) r:[gecos] Matches against the gecos (real name field) Server s:[server] Matches against all users on the servername SSL Fingerprint z:[fingerprint] Matches against all users with the ssl fingerprint. Accepts a wildcard</description></item><item><title>Modes</title><link>http://localhost:1313/modes/modes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 22:31:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/modes/modes/</guid><description>Name Syntax Description Allow invite A Allows anyone to invite anyone else to the channel. Block Caps B Block all caps lines from the channel No CTCP C Blocks CTCPs, other than ACTION, from the channel Delay Join D Hide JOINs until the user speaks Nick Flood F [num]:[sec] Allows only [num] nick changes every [sec] Chan history H [num]:[sec] On join, replays the last [num] lines from within the last [sec] seconds to the connecting user Invite Exception I n!u@h Allows matching masks to have a permanent channel invite Kick Rejoin Delay J [sec] Disallows a user from rejoining the channel until [sec] seconds after a kick No Knock K Prevents KNOCK attempts against the channel Redirect when full L [#channel] Forwards users to [#channel] when the channel limit is reached Registered only speech M Prevents non-registered users from speaking No Nicks N Prevents Nick Changes for any user in the channel Oper only O Restricts a channel to only network operators Permanent P Channel will continue to exist even when empty and over server restarts No Kicks Q Prevents any kicks. Does not affect services Registered users only R Only registered users may join the channel Strip Color S Strips color codes from messages in the channel, but allows the message through, sans colors No Notices T Prevents any NOTICEs to be sent to the entire channel Rate Limit W [num]:[sec] Prevents [num] or more messages in [sec]. Similar to +f, but only blocks messages when the rate is exceeded, instead of kicking. Exempt Modes X [permission]:[mode] Gives users with [mode] additional permissions. See below Oper-join (prefix: !) Y [nick] Marks a staff member on official business, can only be set by an oper Dummy List Z A dummy mode used by m_namedmodes.so allowing you to view the current channel modes as named modes. /mode #channel Z will output the list, same as /prop #channel Ban b n!u@h Bans the matching mask from the channel Block Color c Blocks color lines from the channel Delay Msg d [sec] Prevent a user from speaking for [sec] seconds after joining Ban Exception e n!</description></item><item><title>User Rules</title><link>http://localhost:1313/rules/user/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 22:31:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/rules/user/</guid><description>Nicknames / NickServ Any unregistered and otherwise available nicknames may be freely registered so long as they do not violate network policy. There is a maximum of 5 grouped nicknames per account. Please use NickServ&amp;rsquo;s GROUP command to add a nickname to your account as opposed to registering a new account. For more information or to request assistance, please join #help. Nickname squatting is not permitted. We ask that all registered or grouped names be put to use. Nicknames must not contain any racial slurs, bigotry, or other words and/or phrases which violate our Terms of Service. We reserve the right to suspend, forbid and/or otherwise prohibit access to these names. Temporary/disposable email addresses are prohibited. Snoonet reserves the right to delete your registration if you register with a false/throwaway email address. Nicknames expire after 9999 days of no usage. Upon request in the #help channel, accounts holding only one name and having at least 1 year of inactivity may be dropped. Nicknames grouped to any account may be ungrouped or dropped after at least 6 months of inactivity. Requests for nicknames to be made available will be subject to the discretion of staff. Requests for nicknames that violate Snoonet policies will be refused. Hostmasks Your IP address is masked by default when you connect to Snoonet. This mask does not reveal your real IP address. When you register an account on our network and confirm your account registration, you are eligible to receive a default user cloak. If you do not wish to keep your default cloak after confirming your nickname, please reach out in #help to have it removed. Channel specific cloaks may be available. Requests for channel cloaks will be subject to staff discretion. For a user to qualify for a channel cloak, they must be on the access list of the channel in question. Please reach out in #help for more information. We do not currently offer custom vanity hosts except in special circumstances, such as network events. Users that already hold a custom vanity cloak may request their cloak be changed at any time. Bots Bots may freely be run on our network, providing that the bot conforms to our Terms of Service and other network rules as outlined both above and below. Bots should have their own, separate registered account and are required to have an identifiable cloak, which includes the name of the bot as well as its operator.</description></item><item><title>Introduction</title><link>http://localhost:1313/help/introduction/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 19:35:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/help/introduction/</guid><description> If you have any questions, feel free to ask in #help or generate a support ticket. - Snoonet staff is available for assistance 24/7. Don&amp;rsquo;t be shy, you will be treated politely and fairly. If you are completely new to IRC we suggest you read up on basic commands and functionality here: IRC Help - New2irc To register your user nickname you must have a valid e-mail address. You may group additional nicknames to your current one.</description></item><item><title>Paradox</title><link>http://localhost:1313/staff/paradox/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/staff/paradox/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Acting Extbans</title><link>http://localhost:1313/extbans/acting_extbans/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 22:31:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/extbans/acting_extbans/</guid><description> Syntax Effect A:[ban] Blocks matching users from using /INVITE B:[ban] Disallows matching users from using ALL CAPS. C:[ban] Blocks CTCPs from matching users. N:[ban] Disallows matching users from changing their nickname while in the channel. Q:[ban] Disallows /KICK from matching users. S:[ban] Strips control codes from messages matching users. T:[ban] Disallows NOTICEs from matching users to the channel c:[ban] Blocks messages from matching users if they contain color codes. m:[ban] Blocks messages to the channel from matching users. p:[ban] Hides part messages from matching users.</description></item><item><title>Network Conduct</title><link>http://localhost:1313/rules/network_conduct/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 22:31:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/rules/network_conduct/</guid><description>Network-Wide Rules Repeated and/or intentional ban evasion may earn you a timed network ban. To request a ban appeal, follow the policy of appeals (where one exists) or message the banning OP. Bans from Snoonet network channels or the Snoonet IRC network in its entirety must be addressed via support ticket. Please respect your fellow users. Do not intentionally harass other users. This includes &amp;ldquo;trolling&amp;rdquo;. Action may be taken on a channel-to-channel basis, where such rules exist. If harassment is persistent, across multiple channels or targets a specific user for a length of time, the offending user may be banned. Get along with others! We understand that there are multiple types of humor, but do not excessively attack any other user on this network. Please note that sarcasm doesn&amp;rsquo;t translate well over IRC. Posting the personal information of others is grounds for a permanent network ban. Attempting to collect personal info of users is dealt with in the same manner. No solicitation. This includes, but is not limited to, public spam, private message spam, repeated solicitation of services, solicitation of other network channels, and vote brigading on social media (eg. encouraging others to upvote/downvote a thread on reddit). Solicitation of services for financial gain is only permitted by asking the channel operators. No user is to request money from others. While we understand many are in times of need, please register a gofundme account and state why you are asking for money. Please ask permission from the channel operators. Begging, and contacting multiple users requesting money is a network offense and will be dealt with warnings and removal from the network. Listen to network staff. They can be identified by the &amp;ldquo;snoonet/rank/nickname&amp;rdquo; hostmask. /whois NICKNAME to confirm that they are a Snoonet staff member. You can view the staff directory here Do not ignore network operators or channel operators. If you have an issue with the conduct of a network operator, kindly open an &amp;ldquo;Abuse&amp;rdquo; support ticket and your complaint will be noted and addressed. Issues with the conduct of an operator in a specific channel should be addressed with that channel directly. User impersonation is prohibited. If you&amp;rsquo;re found to be intentionally impersonating Snoonet users, you may face removal from the network for a length of time to be decided at the time of incident. For Your Information Please don&amp;rsquo;t spam/flood the network. If you need to paste a large chunk of text, consider https://pastebin.</description></item><item><title>NickServ</title><link>http://localhost:1313/anope/nickserv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 22:31:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/anope/nickserv/</guid><description>General NickServ in-network help:
/msg NickServ HELP [COMMAND]
Without a [COMMAND] parameter, this will list the NickServ commands and descriptions. If you fill in the [command] parameter it will give you detailed instructions on that command.
To use the awesome features from NickServ, you must first register your nick. Make sure you&amp;rsquo;re using the nick that you want by typing:
/nick &amp;lt;nick&amp;gt;
Then type this to register your nick:
/msg NickServ REGISTER &amp;lt;password&amp;gt; &amp;lt;email&amp;gt;
Make sure that you use a valid email, as you&amp;rsquo;ll have to confirm that it is yours. If you don&amp;rsquo;t get the email you may have the server resend it to you using this command:
/msg NickServ RESEND
Every time you join Snoonet after registering your nick, you&amp;rsquo;ll be prompted for your password. Just type this:
/msg NickServ IDENTIFY &amp;lt;password&amp;gt;
and you&amp;rsquo;ll be logged in!
Most clients offer a way to save your password so that you do not have to manually type it each time. For client specific help, visit #TechSupport.
Forgot your password? No problem. Use this:
/msg NickServ RESETPASS &amp;lt;nick&amp;gt; &amp;lt;email&amp;gt;
Sometimes you get disconnected, but your nick is still present on the network. When this happens you can regain control of your nick by typing:
/msg NickServ GHOST &amp;lt;nick&amp;gt; &amp;lt;password&amp;gt;
Or
/msg NickServ RECOVER &amp;lt;nick&amp;gt; &amp;lt;password&amp;gt;
You can have multiple nicks. Just switch to the nick you want to add to your registered nick and type:
/msg NickServ GROUP &amp;lt;mainnick&amp;gt; &amp;lt;password&amp;gt;
to undo it, type: /msg NickServ UNGROUP [nick]
To see all the nicknames you have in your group, type:
/msg NickServ GLIST
If you no longer wish to have your nickname registered, type:
/msg NickServ DROP &amp;lt;nick&amp;gt;
To view the information about your nick, such as when you registered, type:
/msg NickServ INFO &amp;lt;nick&amp;gt;
To edit the items that people can view about you with the INFO command such as your facebook or email, type:
/msg NickServ SET [option]
You can also set up a list of channels to join automatically when you log in! The command for this is:
/msg NickServ AJOIN {ADD|DEL} [nickname] &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt; [key]
To view your autojoin channels, type:
/msg NickServ AJOIN LIST
List channels you have access on:
/msg ChanServ ALIST</description></item><item><title>Notes</title><link>http://localhost:1313/modes/notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 22:31:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/modes/notes/</guid><description>Auto-mode w [mode]:[n!u@h]
Auto-mode allows you to automatically voice, op, or set other modes on users joining your channel. This is a powerful feature, that can replace the necessity for some bots
[mode] is one of the prefix modes, such as h for halfop, o for operator, or v for voiced.
Hostmask is any matching mask, including extbans
Exempt Modes X [permission]:[mode]
Exempt modes allows you to set more granular permissions, based on user modes Example: /mode #channel +X censor:v will allow voiced users and higher to bypass the censorship(chanmode +g) filters
[mode] is one of the prefix modes, such as h for halfop, o for operator, or v for voiced.
[permission] is one of the following:
topiclock: permission required to change the topic if +t is set auditorium-vis: permission required to always be visible in a +u channel auditorium-see: permission required to see all the users in a +u channel blockcaps: permission to send caps in a +B channel blockcolor: permission to use color in a +c channel filter: permission to bypass channel-level filters in a +g channel flood: Permission to bypass flood limits in a +f channel nickflood: Permission to bypass nick flood limits in a +F channel noctcp: Permission to send CTCPs in a +C channel nonick: Permission to change nicks in a +N channel nonotice: Permission to send notices in a +T channel regmoderated: Permission to bypass +R and +M slowmode: Permission to bypass the rate limit in a +W channel stripcolor: Permission to bypass color stripping in a +S channel</description></item><item><title>External Links</title><link>http://localhost:1313/help/external-links/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 21:50:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/help/external-links/</guid><description> Service command list Tor SSL/fingerprint information Channel modes User modes InspIRCd help system Bot help</description></item><item><title>Duck</title><link>http://localhost:1313/staff/duck/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/staff/duck/</guid><description>Duck duck [at] snoonet.org Hello all, Duck here! Thanks for flying Snoonet!
I joined staff in mid-2017 and presently oversee operations on the network as the Network Director. Part of my mission is to assist our staff with rules &amp;amp; guideline enforcement and to assist in the maintenance of our server infrastructure. I&amp;rsquo;m also involved with InspIRCd and DroneBL, both of which help keep this network ticking.
While not doing network-related things, I may be found chatting in a handful of the communities that we host. If you see me around, feel free to say hi, or send me a message at any time using /msg Duck Hi!
・゜゜・。。 ​ ・゜゜\​_0&amp;lt; QUA​CK!</description></item><item><title>Channel Rules</title><link>http://localhost:1313/rules/channel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 22:31:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/rules/channel/</guid><description>Registering a Channel Unregistered and otherwise available channels may be freely created or registered on Snoonet so long as they do not violate network policy. Abandoned channels may be claimed or dropped, subject to staff discretion. This service is offered as a privilege and not a right. We reserve the right to suspend or close any channels that encourage illegal activity or otherwise expose the network to liability. Unicode characters in channel names are not permitted. Accounts may register or otherwise be the founder of a maximum of 10 channels. Do not mass register channels that you have no intention of using, or solely to reserve a specific name. Such channels may be suspended or dropped at staff discretion. Logging It is understood that users on the network may keep their own private logs of any channel. Snoonet requests that these logs not be made public unless consent has been given by the operators of the channel in question.</description></item><item><title>ChanServ</title><link>http://localhost:1313/anope/chanserv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 22:31:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/anope/chanserv/</guid><description>General ChanServ in-network help:
/msg ChanServ HELP [COMMAND]
Without a [COMMAND] parameter, this will list the ChanServ commands and descriptions. If you fill in the [command] parameter it will give you detailed instructions on that command.
Register a channel:
/msg ChanServ REGISTER &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt; [description]
Cancel the registration of a channel:
/msg ChanServ DROP &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt; &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt;
Note: enter the same channel name twice. You can only do this if it is YOUR channel or you have a Snoonet admin do it for you.
List information about a registered channel:
/msg ChanServ INFO &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt;
This includes its founder, time of registration, and last time used. If the user issuing the command has the appropriate access for it, then the description, successor, last topic set, settings and expiration time will also be displayed when applicable.
Invite someone to a channel:
/msg ChanServ INVITE &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt; &amp;lt;nick&amp;gt;
*Note: You can invite yourself into a channel if you have the correct flags in that channel.
Set an entry message for a channel
/msg ChanServ ENTRYMSG &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt; ADD &amp;lt;message&amp;gt;
Remove an entry message for a channel
/msg ChanServ ENTRYMSG &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt; CLEAR
Kick a user:
/msg ChanServ KICK &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt; {nick | mask} [reason]
or
!kick {nick | mask} [reason]
Kicks a specified nick from a channel. You may kick by username or by hostmask.
Ban a user:
/msg ChanServ BAN &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt; [+expiry] {nick | mask} [reason]
or
!ban {nick | mask} [reason]
Bans specified nick from a channel. You may ban by username or by hostmask.
/msg ChanServ UNBAN &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt; [nick] Remove all bans preventing a user from entering a channel
or
!unban {nick | mask} [reason]
View user flags:
/msg ChanServ FLAGS &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt; LIST [mask | +flags]
or
!flags {nick | mask} [reason]
Clear all flags:
/msg ChanServ LIST channel CLEAR
Add user flags:
/msg ChanServ FLAGS channel MODIFY &amp;lt;username or hostmask&amp;gt; &amp;lt;+/- changes&amp;gt;
or
!flags modify {nick | mask} [reason]
For example /msg ChanServ FLAGS #snoonet modify *!*@snoonet/* +Bc will set all Snoonet staff to be allowed to use Botserv SAY and ACT commands, as well as grant them the ability to use fantasy commands.
Flag Use b Allowed to ban users B Allowed to use SAY and ACT commands c Allowed to use fantasy commands f Allowed to modify or view the access list F Allowed to issue commands restricted to channel founders G Allowed to use GETKEY command g Greet message displayed on join H Automatic halfop upon join h Allowed to (de)halfop users and him/herself I Allowed to get full INFO output i Allowed to use the INVITE command K Allowed to use the AKICK command, modify badwords list k Allowed to use the KICK command m Allowed to read channel memos N Prevents users being kicked by Services O Automatic channel operator status upon join o Allowed to (de)op users and him/herself s Allowed to assign/unassign a bot, use MODE commands and set channel settings t Allowed to change channel topics u Allowed to unban users V Automatic voice on join v Allowed to (de)voice users and him/herself You can also view the list of users that have access in a given channel by using /msg ChanServ ACCESS &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt; list</description></item><item><title>See Also</title><link>http://localhost:1313/modes/see_also/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 22:31:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/modes/see_also/</guid><description> User Modes Extended Ban Syntax</description></item><item><title>Using webchat (the super easy way)</title><link>http://localhost:1313/help/webchat/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 19:37:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/help/webchat/</guid><description>The absolute easiest way to connect to Snoonet is by using our webchat. Many subreddits you may have heard of Snoonet from will provide direct links to the chat. Our webchat uses the KiwiIRC client. To connect to Snoonet webchat simply visit the webchat and choose a nickname.
The webchat can be used anywhere, at work, at home, or on mobile. This simplicity comes with the drawback of a few less features than a desktop client. A desktop client is customizable and has more functions. If you want to use a desktop client just read the next section. If you have problems setting up the desktop client you can always go back to the webchat, it&amp;rsquo;s just a click away.
To get started, enter a nickname for yourself and the channel that you wish to enter. Select start and you&amp;rsquo;re connected to Snoonet!
To see a list of the communities on Snoonet, type /list into the chat area. When you find a community you are interested in, simply click on the name of the chat and it adds a tab at the top of the page for you. You can switch between chats using these tabs.
To register your nickname so that you can return and use the same nickname without worrying that someone else will steal it, make sure you are using the nickname you want to register and type /msg nickserv REGISTER &amp;lt;password&amp;gt; &amp;lt;email&amp;gt;. You do not need to include the brackets. Make sure to use a real email, because we will send your verification to that email and you will lose the nickname if you do not submit your code. When your registration is successful, upon returning to chat, you&amp;rsquo;ll need to select the box that says you have a password, and enter your password there.</description></item><item><title>Mike</title><link>http://localhost:1313/staff/mike/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/staff/mike/</guid><description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Mike.
You can verify my identity on the network with the client certificate fingerprint 5f354892970d867aafe9256a1155160d.
If you need to e-mail me, you can contact me using mike [at] snoonet.org.</description></item><item><title>BotServ</title><link>http://localhost:1313/anope/botserv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 22:31:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/anope/botserv/</guid><description>General BotServ in-network help:
/msg BotServ HELP [COMMAND]
Without a [COMMAND] parameter, this will list the BotServ commands and descriptions. If you fill in the [command] parameter it will give you detailed instructions on that command.
Botlist:
/msg BotServ BOTLIST
Lists all available bots on Snoonet.
BotServ Info:
/msg BotServ INFO {channel | nickname}
Allows you to see BotServ information about a channel or a bot. If the parameter is a channel, then you&amp;rsquo;ll get information such as enabled kickers. If the parameter is a nick, you&amp;rsquo;ll get information about a bot, such as creation time or number of channels it is on.
Assign a bot:
/msg BotServ ASSIGN &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt; &amp;lt;nick&amp;gt;
Assigns a bot to a channel. You can then configure the bot for the channel so it fits your needs. You can only assign one bot through BotServ at a time.
Configure bot options:
/msg BotServ SET &amp;lt;option&amp;gt; (channel | bot) &amp;lt;settings&amp;gt;
For more information on a particular option and its settings, type /msg BotServ HELP set &amp;lt;option&amp;gt;.
Set Use BANEXPIRE Configures the time bot bans expire in DONTKICKOPS Protects ops against bot kicks DONTKICKVOICES Proctects voices against bot kicks FANTASY Enables fantaisist commands GREET Enables greet messages NOBOT Prevents a bot from being assigned to a channel PRIVATE Prevents a bot from being assigned by non IRC operators Configure kickers:
/msg BotServ KICK &amp;lt;option&amp;gt; &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt; {ON|OFF} [settings]
For more information on a particular option and its settings, type /msg BotServ HELP kick &amp;lt;option&amp;gt;
Kick Use AMSG Allows bot to kick users who send the same message to multiple channels where BotServ bots are. BADWORDS Allows bot to kick users who say certain words on the channels. BOLDS Allows bot to kick users who use bolds. CAPS Allows bot to kick users who are talking in caps. COLORS Allows bot to kick users who use colors. FLOOD Allows bot to kick users who are flooding the channel with multiple lines of text. ITALICS Allows bot to kick users who use italics. REPEAT Allows bot to kick users who are repeating themselves. REVERSES Allows bot to kick users who use reverses.</description></item><item><title>Using a desktop IRC client</title><link>http://localhost:1313/help/desktop-client/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 19:46:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/help/desktop-client/</guid><description>IRC is a fairly popular chat protocol, it has many thousands of users around the world. It&amp;rsquo;s no surprise that the choice of clients is huge. There&amp;rsquo;s IRC clients for every operating system and most of them are free.
Choosing an IRC client comes down to preference, but here are some of the more popular ones:
AdiIRC (Free - Windows/Mac OS/Linux) Colloquy (Free - Mac OS) HexChat (Free - Windows/Mac OS/Linux) IceChat (Free - Windows) irssi (Free - Mac OS/Linux - Command line client/Advanced) LimeChat (Free - Mac OS) mIRC (Paid - Windows) Smuxi (Free - Windows/Mac OS/Linux) Textual (Paid - Mac OS) weechat (Free - Mac OS/Linux - Command line client/Advanced) All these clients are different (some more, some less) but they all have some stuff in common. They all allow for storing a list of networks and for setting global information about yourself, like a nickname and your real name (you don&amp;rsquo;t have to put your actual name there, you can put anything in the real name field). So you should choose your desired nickname and move on to the next steps.</description></item><item><title>MemoServ</title><link>http://localhost:1313/anope/memoserv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 22:31:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/anope/memoserv/</guid><description>General MemoServ in-network help:
/msg MemoServ HELP [COMMAND]
Without a [COMMAND] parameter, this will list the MemoServ commands and descriptions. If you fill in the [command] parameter it will give you detailed instructions on that command.
Information:
MemoServ is a utility allowing IRC users to send short messages to other IRC users, whether they are online at the time or not, or to channels. Both the sender&amp;rsquo;s nickname and the target nickname or channel must be registered in order to send a memo.
/msg MemoServ INFO
Displays information on the number of memos you have, how many of them are unread, and how many total memos you can receive.
/msg MemoServ INFO &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt;
Displays information on the number of memos the channel has, how many of them are unread, and how many total memos the channel can receive.
Set options:
/msg MemoServ SET &amp;lt;option&amp;gt; &amp;lt;parameters&amp;gt;
Sets various memo options.
Option Description NOTIFY Changes when you will be notified about new memos (only for nicknames) LIMIT Sets the maximum number of memos you can receive. For more information on a specific option type /msg MemoServ HELP SET &amp;lt;option&amp;gt;.
Read memos:
/msg MemoServ READ [channel] {LAST | NEW | num | list}
Sends you the text of the memos specified. If LAST is given, sends you the memo you most recently received. If NEW is given, sends you all of your new memos. Otherwise, sends you memo number num. You can also give a list of numbers, as in this example:
/msg MemoServ READ 2-5,7-9
Displays memos numbered 2 through 5 and 7 through 9.
List memo:
/msg MemoServ LIST [channel] [NEW | list]
Lists any memos you currently have. With NEW, lists only new (unread) memos. Unread memos are marked with a &amp;ldquo;&amp;rdquo; to the left of the memo number. You can also specify a list of numbers, as in the example below:
/msg MemoServ LIST 2-5,7-9
Lists memos numbered 2 through 5 and 7 through 9.
Ignore feature:
To add a new ignore entry
/msg MemoServ IGNORE [channel] ADD entry
To delete an existing ignore entry
/msg MemoServ IGNORE [channel] DELETE entry
To list all ignore entries
/msg MemoServ IGNORE [channel] LIST
Allows you to set users (by nick or host) to ignore, keeping them from sending a memo to you or a channel.</description></item><item><title>Connecting to the network</title><link>http://localhost:1313/help/connecting-to-the-network/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 19:49:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/help/connecting-to-the-network/</guid><description>Connecting to Snoonet is done using our IRC round-robin, that means that you connect to our distribution host and you will then be randomly put on one of our servers. This ensures a good load balance on the network and if your server would go down you would immediately connect to a different server. The IRC round-robin for Snoonet is irc.snoonet.org. To connect to IRC you always need a port, for IRC those ports are 6667 for normal connections and 6697 for SSL by default. Most networks use those very same ports and your client will likely automatically fill those in.
For some more information on our servers you can visit our website and read up about our different round-robins. We offer connectivity using IPv6, web ports for people behind a restrictive firewall, and even TOR connectivity.
The two clients I highlighted, HexChat and Textual, both come with Snoonet as a default server. Just select Snoonet from the list of servers available in the respective connection dialogs. In the other clients you can enter irc.snoonet.org as the address or host and 6697 as the port. Make sure to use SSL when you connect through port 6697 (there is a checkbox).
When you hit the connect button you should receive a bunch of messages from the server, like the MOTD (message of the day) and a few notices about security. When you get an error use our webchat as described above to connect and ask for help in #help.
By default when you connect to snoonet user mode +x is set, which obfuscates your IP address. Vhosts will mask your host, but only when you are identified with NickServ.</description></item><item><title>Using a mobile IRC client</title><link>http://localhost:1313/help/mobile-client/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 19:47:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/help/mobile-client/</guid><description>AndroIRC (Free with paid upgrades - Android) IRCCloud (Free with paid upgrades - Android/iOS)* Palaver (Paid - iOS) TurboIRC (Free - Amazon Devices) xoChat (Free - Windows Phone) * IRCCloud&amp;rsquo;s free plan does not support the BNC. Please select a different client if you wish to take advantage of the service.</description></item><item><title>DavidLuizsHair</title><link>http://localhost:1313/staff/davidluizhair/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/staff/davidluizhair/</guid><description>Alright? I&amp;rsquo;m DavidLuizsHair or DLH. Nice to meet you. I&amp;rsquo;m a recently appointed community admin. I&amp;rsquo;ve been on IRC intermittently throughout my teenage years, but have recently gotten back into it about a year ago. I&amp;rsquo;ve been on snoonet for about 10 months [as of drafting this message] so I&amp;rsquo;m still relatively quite young compared to others in that respect. I&amp;rsquo;m a pretty big sports fan mostly being a fan of football (soccer), formula 1 and intermittently following some NBA as well. In terms of other interests, I&amp;rsquo;m an avid fan of documentaries and I also intermittently cook, with varying results. Music wise I&amp;rsquo;m all over the board, I&amp;rsquo;m open to new kinds of music although various types of Indie, metalcore and rock tend to be my jam. Use /query DavidLuizsHair if you ever need any network help and I will do my best to help you. I go in phases of reading where I either read intensively or I don&amp;rsquo;t read at all, some of my favourite books include &amp;ldquo;To Kill A MockingBird&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;The Stranger&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;The Guest&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;By The Waters of Babylon.&amp;rdquo; Some of my favourite subreddits include /r/penmanshipporn, /r/soccer, /r/nba, /r/London and /r/BritishProblems.
The following statements below are compiled impressions of what IRC-ers who have interacted with me before describe me.
This is what my profile would look like if Ari created it: &amp;ldquo;Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m DavidLuizsHair. I have like 70 nicknames on Snoonet, most of them animals for some reason. According to Meow_Mix, I like dog gifs and sportsball. Sportsball is the best. I&amp;rsquo;m going to recruit channels to Snoonet that are already here! GO SPORTS, DO THE THING, SCORE THE GOAL!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;DavidLuizsHair i just remembered i had a dream about you. o.0 You took over the world dressed like a KFC bucket.&amp;rdquo; - f5184
&amp;ldquo;If you weren&amp;rsquo;t here I&amp;rsquo;d be fully clothed&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;yes, and if I wasn&amp;rsquo;t here, you&amp;rsquo;d be breaking and entering&amp;rdquo; - owlet
&amp;ldquo;DavidLuizshair used confusion, it was super effective. DavidLuizsHair hurt itself in it&amp;rsquo;s confusion&amp;rdquo; - linuxdaemon
This is what my smile looks like as described by noeatnosleep: http://www.reactiongifs.com/r/gddy.gif
This is the pic Meow_Mix uses to describe me with: http://24.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_m5tqqzDnrt1qet66oo1_500.png
Well, if you&amp;rsquo;ve made it this far. Have a pasta guide: http://pastafits.org/pasta-dictionary/</description></item><item><title>linuxdaemon</title><link>http://localhost:1313/staff/linuxdaemon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/staff/linuxdaemon/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Phase</title><link>http://localhost:1313/staff/phase/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/staff/phase/</guid><description/></item><item><title>ricin</title><link>http://localhost:1313/staff/ricin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/staff/ricin/</guid><description>Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m ricin. I own and operate one of the servers for Snoonet, as well as run some bots (Charlize, etc). I&amp;rsquo;ve been on IRC since 1993 and have been with Snoonet since the beginning. You can find me almost everywhere. Say hi if you see me!</description></item><item><title>ThatOneRoadie</title><link>http://localhost:1313/staff/thatoneroadie/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/staff/thatoneroadie/</guid><description>Heyo! I&amp;rsquo;m ThatOneRoadie, also known as Thor or TOR, from Denver, Colorado, USA. I&amp;rsquo;m one of the Senior Network Operations Staff here at Snoonet, responsible for the upkeep and maintenance of our network of servers. It&amp;rsquo;s a responsibility that changes on a daily basis, encompassing things such as monitoring network routes, upgrading and maintaining our IRC Daemon on all of our hub and leaf servers, commissioning and decommissioning servers on the network, stress testing new servers, and load balancing the users on the leafs that are active. At any given time, I&amp;rsquo;m responsible for the chat network used by over 4500 people simultaneously.
The team of Network Operations Staffers here at Snoonet maintain over 13 Client Leaf servers, and a number of hidden hub servers operating as the backbone to our IRC network. The leaf servers are in many geographically diverse locations, from Los Angeles, USA, to Dublin, Ireland, and even servers in Singapore (clearly you&amp;rsquo;ve never been to Singapore). We strive to keep these servers up-to-date with the latest security and software updates, protecting our users from any breach of data.
I, personally, maintain a number of servers for the Snoonet network, as well as a set of 16 blade servers and a 10TB SAN (Storage Area Network) in my home lab environment. In my free time, I tinker on this home lab with various virtual machines on an enterprise Cisco network. When I&amp;rsquo;m not doing that, I&amp;rsquo;m a student pilot here in the Denver area, working on my Private Pilot&amp;rsquo;s License.</description></item><item><title>weylin</title><link>http://localhost:1313/staff/weylin/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/staff/weylin/</guid><description>Hi I&amp;rsquo;m Weylin!</description></item><item><title>HostServ</title><link>http://localhost:1313/anope/hostserv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 22:31:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/anope/hostserv/</guid><description>General HostServ in-network help:
/msg HostServ HELP [COMMAND]
Without a [COMMAND] parameter, this will list the HostServ commands and descriptions. If you fill in the [command] parameter it will give you detailed instructions on that command.</description></item><item><title>Authing on connect</title><link>http://localhost:1313/help/authing-on-connect/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 19:50:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/help/authing-on-connect/</guid><description>Snoonet uses IRCDs and Services that follow the IRCv3 standard, and as such, we offer several ways for a user to auth to services before joining channels.
Many older clients will automatically send PRIVMSG NickServ :identify username password. This isn&amp;rsquo;t optimal, as its slow, and somewhat insecure. Furthermore, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t run till you join a channel, which can expose your hostname as well as annoy everyone with 3 join messages.
There are a few ways to prevent this, and be authorized before you even join a channel:
CertFP Snoonet network runs Anope services, which allows SSL certificate fingerprint authentification. This is by far the most secure method of connecting. For help on how to create an SSL certificate and identify with, please refer to this document.
SASL SASL is the preferred method for authing, and is supported by a variety of clients, either natively or through the use of third party scripts. You simply configure your client or plugin with your irc username and password, and when you connect it sends these to the server.
Libera.chat has an excellent guide to setting up SASL-based auth on many different clients.
Tor Snoonet no longer offers a hidden service. More info.
Server password If your client is not SASL capable, or you don&amp;rsquo;t want to set it up, there is an older, albeit less secure, method of authing to services. You can send your password at connect time.
We support a variety of strings, but the most compatible is &amp;ldquo;username:password&amp;rdquo;, where username is the main NickServ account and password is its password. Set this as your server password, and this will Auth you at connect.</description></item><item><title>Joining channels</title><link>http://localhost:1313/help/joining-channels/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 19:58:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/help/joining-channels/</guid><description>Many clients come with interfaces to join channels &amp;ldquo;more easily&amp;rdquo;, but really the easiest way to do this is the native IRC way. In IRC most stuff goes through so-called &amp;ldquo;Slash-Commands&amp;rdquo;, sounds complicated but it&amp;rsquo;s really not - all it means is that stuff you preceed with a slash (/) will not be sent to channels or people but instead be sent to the server as a command.
To join a channel you can type /join #channelname in the IRC client, web or desktop - it&amp;rsquo;s the same for every client. This will join you into any channel, whether it exists or not. You can use the command when you are on a channel or in your server information window (where the MOTD came up) or even in private message windows. It&amp;rsquo;s super easy and I believe it&amp;rsquo;s a lot easier than going through some bloated channel interface.
You can also use /list to see all the channels available.
All clients will keep a list of channels you are in, our webchat does that above the chat, most desktop clients do it in a sidebar on the left or the right.</description></item><item><title>cachinnate</title><link>http://localhost:1313/staff/cachinnate/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 16:01:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/staff/cachinnate/</guid><description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m cachinnate!</description></item><item><title>Getting help</title><link>http://localhost:1313/help/getting-help/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 19:59:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/help/getting-help/</guid><description>Do you have any problems with any of the things described here? Simply click this link and you will be taken to our webchat. Now choose a nickname (this can be almost anything) and connect, you will be put in our help channel (#help) automatically and you can ask staff your questions. Make sure to be descriptive about your issue.
There is also a detailed explanation of all services available on Snoonet here.</description></item><item><title>void</title><link>http://localhost:1313/staff/void/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/staff/void/</guid><description>Photography. Software Engineering. Caffeine. Sketching. Cocktails. Beards. Animals.
Feel free to ask me about my Small Dog.
🤙🏻</description></item><item><title>noeatnosleep</title><link>http://localhost:1313/staff/noeatnosleep/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 21:02:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/staff/noeatnosleep/</guid><description/></item><item><title>jotun</title><link>http://localhost:1313/staff/jotun/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/staff/jotun/</guid><description>Hello, I&amp;rsquo;m jotun, a software engineer living in sunny California.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been using IRC - and coding things for IRC - for nearly 20 years. You might&amp;rsquo;ve heard of my game, Idle RPG. If not, you can check it out in #idlerpg on Snoonet!
I discovered Snoonet about a year and a half ago and thought it&amp;rsquo;d be fun to work with a network that combined two of my favorite things - IRC and reddit. Since joining, I&amp;rsquo;ve had some really wild experiences and met some amazing new friends.
If you like to code, or are interested in learning to code, stop by #programming and say hello!</description></item><item><title>duk242</title><link>http://localhost:1313/staff/duk242/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/staff/duk242/</guid><description>Aloha! I am duk242
I&amp;rsquo;ve been on IRC for about 20 years now (Snoonet since 2017).
I chill in the #techsupport, #programming, #technology and #games channels for the most part.
IRL I&amp;rsquo;m an Aussie who likes games, gadgets and casual programming.
Feel free to say hi! I&amp;rsquo;m always up for a random chat about tech support, games or whatever.
– duk242</description></item><item><title>flotwig</title><link>http://localhost:1313/staff/flotwig/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/staff/flotwig/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m flotwig. You might have heard me called flotty, flotsam, Just Wiggy™, or thotwig.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been on IRC since 2007 or 2008 and I&amp;rsquo;ve been on Snoonet since week two of its existence. Nowadays, I&amp;rsquo;m a more active IRCer than I am a redditor.
My favorite channels are #gnulag, ##PartyMansion, #safefromparadox, and #idlerpg.
flotwig</description></item><item><title>Shadeblast</title><link>http://localhost:1313/staff/shadeblast/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/staff/shadeblast/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Zowlyfon</title><link>http://localhost:1313/staff/zowlyfon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/staff/zowlyfon/</guid><description>Hi, my name is Zowlyfon. I am a Free Software enthusiast studying Computer Science in the UK. I mainly develop and maintain custom software for Snoonet, as well as test out experimental ideas.
I am mainly active in #linuxmasterrace and I can also be contacted in #snoonet or via PM.
My email address is zowlyfon [at] snoonet.org.</description></item><item><title>Updates to IRC.com infrastructure</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2021/06/20/updates-to-irc-com-infrastructure/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 01:01:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2021/06/20/updates-to-irc-com-infrastructure/</guid><description>From: Network Director (duck@snoonet.org)
Good afternoon,
In 2018, Snoonet announced a partnership with IRC.com and made several changes to the network to support the services that they were introducing. These included a brand new IRC network running on modern IRC software, as well as a Bouncer-as-a-Service product which is still available and can be utilized with a custom application on the web, or on compatible Androidand Appledevices.
Starting today, Snoonet will begin implementing changes which will separate the IRC.com network from Snoonet. We will introduce some minor changes as soon as possible, with the eventual removal of IRC.com servers from Snoonet to follow in the coming days. If you currently use irc.irc.com to connect and wish to remain on our network, please update your IRC clients now to use irc.snoonet.org. If you registered a NickServ account on IRC.com, your account will be retained in our database and you will be able to use your existing credentials to authenticate on Snoonet.
Additionally, users that currently have a vhost of irc.com/user/name will have their vhost changed to user/name. Users with a snoonet.org/user/name will have the option to change to user/name.
If you have any questions or concerns, please do not hesitate to contact a Snoonet operator in #help, or open a ticket at https://support.snoonet.org/
Thank you for using Snoonet!</description></item><item><title>Services maintenance update: October 2020</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020/10/23/services-update-oct-2020/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2020 21:03:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020/10/23/services-update-oct-2020/</guid><description>From: Network Director (duck@snoonet.org)
Good afternoon,
On October 23rd, we carried out maintenance on our services package to fix an issue with respect to account registrations. While carrying out the maintenance, our services package behaved unexpectedly and after an investigation, we determined that some recent database changes are not recoverable and are thusly declaring an incident resulting in the loss of data.
If you registered an account on Snoonet, grouped a nickname to an existing account, registered a channel or made any changes to the access list of an existing channel, then please read the following information carefully.
What exactly happened? Whilst conducting maintenance, we noted that Anope was not saving its database correctly and was instead storing all recent changes in memory. While attempting to render a fix, Anope suffered a segmentation fault which terminated its program. The fault that terminated the program was caused as Anope was trying to save its database.
How will Snoonet respond? Upon declaring the data loss incident, we made the decision to restore the last backup that would work successfully. The backup was taken on October 4th at shortly after midnight (00:00) UTC. Any changes that were made after this time have been lost.
We&amp;rsquo;ve also added information to our logon news concerning the data loss incident.
For users that registered an account on or after the 4th of October, we have reached out to them directly to advise of the incident.
We will be immediately implementing stricter testing guidelines for any future software or configuration changes to avoid a repeat situation.
I realize that this situation is not ideal for some people and I offer my apologies for any inconvenience this may have caused you. If you have any concerns, you can either ask our network staff by joining #help. You can also reach out to me directly via private message on the network or by email at duck@snoonet.org.</description></item><item><title>#trees</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/trees/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 16:07:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/trees/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#bipolarreddit</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/bipolarreddit/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 13:42:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/bipolarreddit/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Your client and InspIRCd</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020/07/13/client-upgrades/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 18:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2020/07/13/client-upgrades/</guid><description>We are currently working on upgrading our network to InspIRCd v3. Older versions of some IRC clients (listed below) do not follow the IRC specification correctly and can not handle the way that InspIRCd v3 emits messages. More information about this can be found in the InspIRCd FAQ.
This update will keep us moving towards implementing cool new IRCv3 features.
Who needs to upgrade? You may recently have noticed messages from a network bot suggesting you run software updates.
A large majority of our users are not affected. However, if you are using a client older than the minimum version specified in the table below, you may start to see broken behaviour in some cases.
If you still use any version of XChat we recommend upgrading to HexChat.
Client Minimum version AdiIRC v3.6 HexChat v2.14.3 irssi v1.1.0 WeeChat v2.5.0 ZNC v1.8.0</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>http://localhost:1313/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 21:02:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/privacy-policy/</guid><description>SNOONET PRIVACY POLICY This website (&amp;lsquo;Snoonet.org&amp;rsquo;) wishes to define and inform you of any and all of the instances in which your personal data and information may be saved and how it may be used by Snoonet, how it may be shared, and the level of protection we use to safeguard your personal information when using our services.
PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT USES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED BY US DISCLOSURE AND USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION DATA RETENTION CalOPPA STATEMENT MAINTAINING THE SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION HOW WE TRANSFER PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED INTERNATIONALLY COPPA DISCLOSURE - ABOUT CHILDREN&amp;rsquo;S ONLINE PRIVACY HOW TO ACCESS AND CONTROL YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT back to top
From All Users of Our IRC Network
Internet Protocol (IP) address* for the purposes of account management and protection from abuse. (*You may use a virtual private network or &amp;lsquo;bouncer&amp;rsquo; service if you wish to obscure your IP address) Your user ID or &amp;lsquo;nickname&amp;rsquo; for the purposes of account management and protection from abuse. From Users Who Have Registered an Account on Our IRC Network
Internet Protocol (IP) address* for the purposes of account management and protection from abuse. (*You may use a virtual private network or &amp;lsquo;bouncer&amp;rsquo; service if you wish to obscure your IP address) Your user ID or &amp;lsquo;nickname&amp;rsquo; for the purposes of account management and protection from abuse. Your email address, for the purposes of account management and protection from abuse. From the Snoonet Website and Support System
Email address for the purposes of account management and protection from abuse, or for responding to support requests submitted by you. Internet Protocol (IP) Address* for the purposes of account management and protection from abuse. (*You may use a virtual private network or &amp;lsquo;bouncer&amp;rsquo; service if you wish to obscure your IP address) Your user ID, name, or &amp;lsquo;nickname&amp;rsquo; for the purposes of account management, protection from abuse or responding to support requests submitted by you. USES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED BY US back to top
E-mail address is used to confirm account ownership, for certain limited non-marketing communications by Snoonet to users, or to respond to support requests submitted through our support system. NGINX webserver logs are regularly pruned and are created by the webserver. No usernames or passwords are ever logged by the webserver.</description></item><item><title>#trivia</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/trivia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 14:50:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/trivia/</guid><description/></item><item><title>bloodygonzo</title><link>http://localhost:1313/staff/bloodygonzo/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 09:33:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/staff/bloodygonzo/</guid><description>bloodygonzo (alumnus) I am the Network Director of Snoonet. My goal for Snoonet is to:
Stabilize and secure the network with the best tools in automation, monitoring, and security. Build on the established team of volunteer staff to create an excellent experience for the communities on Snoonet. Provide an excellent end user experience for individuals on our network. Additionally:
I run gonzobot on Snoonet and enjoy customizing him to fit the needs of the various communities on Snoonet. My favorite hobby right now is smoking meat and every weekend I get the chance I try and smoke brisket or pork shoulder, or beef short ribs. Feel free to message me if you have any questions about Snoonet or ideas for improvement using: /query bloodygonzo.
For additional staff information please see the staff index.</description></item><item><title>#zougla</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/zougla/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 16:19:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/zougla/</guid><description>Στο Ελληνικό chat του zougla.gr μπορείτε να επικοινωνείτε γρήγορα και εύκολα με ασφαλή τρόπο.
Συζητείστε για ό,τι σας απασχολεί, ανταλλάξτε απόψεις, κάντε νέες γνωριμίες και φίλους.
Διαβάστε τους κανόνες και την πολιτική λειτουργίας για να γνωρίζετε τι ΔΕΝ πρέπει να κάνετε κατά την είσοδό σας.
Κανόνες και πολιτική λειτουργίας:
Το zougla.gr κατατάσσεται στις καλύτερες ιστοσελίδες στην Ελλάδα σύμφωνα με το Alexa Rank.
Οι χρήστες που συνδέονται στο #zougla οφείλουν να γνωρίζουν τους κανόνες και την πολιτική λειτουργίας του καναλιού.
Κύριος στόχος του καναλιού είναι η ανταλλαγή απόψεων και η δημιουργία συζητήσεων που δεν προσβάλλουν την ανθρώπινη υπόσταση και δεν στοχοποιούν συγκεκριμένες ομάδες ατόμων.
Βασικός στόχος είναι η ψυχαγωγία και όχι η προώθηση πολιτικών και θρησκευτικών πεποιθήσεων, απόψεις που δεν ενστερνίζονται όλοι.
Απαγορεύεται η χρήση προσωνύμιων που έχουν ρατσιστικό/σεξουαλικό ή άλλο χαρακτήρα, που θα μπορούσε να προσβάλλει κάποιο άλλο μέλος ή ολόκληρο το κανάλι, κάθε είδους διαφημίσεις Spam/Ιστοσελίδων/Blog που έχουν ως σκοπό οποιονδήποτε κερδοσκοπικό χαρακτήρα και τέλος κάθε είδους μορφή κατάχρησης όπως Flooding/Abuse των υπηρεσιών που σας παρέχονται.
Πώς μπορώ να γίνω operator(@) στο #zougla;
Η θέση του operator έχει περισσότερες ευθύνες σε σχέση με έναν απλό χρήστη και δεν είναι απλά ένας τίτλος.
Για να γίνει κάποιος operator στο #zougla θα πρέπει:
Να συμμετέχει ενεργά στο κανάλι και να μην δημιουργεί προβλήματα χωρίς λόγο. Να σέβεται τα υπόλοιπα μέλη του #zougla ανεξάρτητα από το αν έχουν παραπάνω προνόμια. Να γνωρίζει τουλάχιστον τις βασικές εντολές και την λειτουργία του IRC. Να μην μπλέκει τις προσωπικές του διαφωνίες με το κανάλι. Τα ban για προσωπικές διαφωνίες με άλλους χρήστες είναι λόγος διαγραφής operator.
Τα μόνιμα op(@) δεν μπορούν να μοιράζονται αυθαίρετα και σε άτομα που δεν γνωρίζουν σε μεγάλο βαθμό το IRC.
Κάθε άτομο που συχνάζει στο chat αποτυπώνει ένα χαρακτήρα και συνεπώς με την συμπεριφορά του αξιολογείται για το αν πρέπει ή όχι να αποκτήσει κάποιο προνόμιο.
Τα προσωπικά μηνύματα των χρηστών παρακολουθούνται/καταγράφονται;
Οι διαχειριστές/operators του #zougla δεν είναι σε θέση να γνωρίζουν/παρακολουθούν τα μηνύματα που ανταλλάσσετε μεταξύ σας (προσωπικά μηνύματα) και επομένως δεν φέρουν καμία ευθύνη για ενδεχόμενες μη νόμιμες ενέργειές σας.
Η διεύθυνση IP από την οποία συνδέομαι είναι ορατή σε άλλους χρήστες;
Οι πραγματικές IP διευθύνσεις των χρηστών που συνδέονται στο #zougla δεν είναι ορατές για λόγους προστασίας των προσωπικών σας δεδομένων.
Γιατί να κατοχυρώσω το ψευδώνυμό (nickname) μου;
Το ψευδώνυμο, είναι απαραίτητο για να σας αναγνωρίζουν οι υπόλοιποι, και σας δίνει μια ταυτότητα στο θέμα συζήτησης που θα συμμετάσχετε.</description></item><item><title>Ban Exemption List</title><link>http://localhost:1313/banexempt/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 22:09:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/banexempt/</guid><description>False-Positive Bans If you were lead here through IRC, your address is set to be auto-banned on connect due to a malicious user ban evading.
The reason and example:
Malicious user uses address 1an9-2b4a-3216-41k.example.com.
We ban 1an9-2b4a-3216-41k.example.com.
User changes their IP address/hostmask to be 22-2b.61.72.41.example.com to evade the original ban.
Since we don&amp;rsquo;t want to block access to all of (in this example) *!*@*.example.com, we apply bans through a service bot, which will allow us to give your specific nickname, identd, and IP address exemptions. Sometimes we will see that it&amp;rsquo;s a false-positive and automatically give you an exemption.
Some users are malicious and try to ruin it for many others, however we are here for you! If you don&amp;rsquo;t know what any of this means, we&amp;rsquo;ll handle all the technical stuff for you! Here&amp;rsquo;s what to do.
What to do For us to add an exemption so that you are not banned. Please e-mail support [at] snoonet.org with your IP address (www.whatismyip.com and copy your IP) the identd that you connect with (If you don&amp;rsquo;t know what it is, state so in the e-mail) and your IRC nickname so we may add an exemption for you specifically. We will e-mail you back within a few minutes and you will be able to connect to our services.
Sorry for the inconvenience</description></item><item><title>Snoonet COPPA Notice</title><link>http://localhost:1313/coppa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 22:04:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/coppa/</guid><description>While snoonet welcomes users and communities from all ends of the spectrum, our network is not designed for nor aimed at children - in accordance with the United States government and the Children&amp;rsquo;s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, individuals under the age of 13 are not permitted to browse snoonet nor create user accounts. We strongly recommend that minors 13 years of age or older ask their parents for permission before logging on, and to refrain from posting any information about themselves, personal or otherwise, on the network. Snoonet also has the option, to use at our discretion, of requiring parental confirmation via email or phone from anyone claiming to be under the age of 18. If you have collected information from or about a child under the age of 13, you will face a network ban.</description></item><item><title>Guide</title><link>http://localhost:1313/guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 22:00:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/guide/</guid><description>Registering your nickname with NickServ To create channels on Snoonet, you must be a registered user. To register your nick, first you must be using the nick you want to register.
Type /nick &amp;lt;yournicknamehere&amp;gt;
Then you may register by typing /msg NickServ REGISTER &amp;lt;password&amp;gt; &amp;lt;email&amp;gt;
Replace password with the password you&amp;rsquo;d like to use to identify yourself when you login (something you&amp;rsquo;ll remember!) and a legitimate email, as you&amp;rsquo;ll need to verify it. Passwords are case-sensitive.
Find out what else you can do with NickServ here
Creating a Channel Let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the use of your channel first. Is it subreddit related or is it a personal channel?
Subreddit channels should be created by a moderator of the subreddit or with the moderator(s) permission. These channels can be named #channel
Personal channels can be created by anyone and should be named ##channel
To create your channel, simply /join &amp;lt;#channelname&amp;gt; (or ##channelname)
You&amp;rsquo;ve done it! Now, to keep it as your channel, You must register with ChanServ.
Type /msg ChanServ REGISTER &amp;lt;#channel&amp;gt; &amp;lt;description&amp;gt;
Replace #channel with your channel name and description can be the topic or purpose of your channel.
Your channel is now registered. You may start inviting people or customizing your channel modes.
To invite someone, type /invite &amp;lt;usernick&amp;gt;</description></item><item><title>gonzobot</title><link>http://localhost:1313/gonzobot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 21:50:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/gonzobot/</guid><description>Welcome to the help page for gonzobot, a fork of the awesome IRC bot Cloudbot that has been customized for Snoonet. To send gonzobot a command use &amp;lsquo;.&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;@&amp;rsquo; as a prefix to any of the commands listed below, the terms listed in parenthesis are aliases and will work the same as the command. Example: .cake bloodygonzo
gonzobot Command list 8ball (eightball, 8): &amp;lt;question&amp;gt; - asks the all knowing magic electronic eight ball &amp;lt;question&amp;gt;
about: - Gives information about CloudBot. Use .about license for licensing information
addbad: &amp;lt;word&amp;gt; &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt; - adds a bad word to the auto kick list must specify a channel with each word ( Permission required: badwords)
adduser: &amp;lt;user&amp;gt; &amp;lt;group&amp;gt; - adds &amp;lt;user&amp;gt; to &amp;lt;group&amp;gt; ( Permission required: permissions_users)
aesthetic (fw, vapor): &amp;lt;string&amp;gt; &amp;ndash; Converts &amp;lt;string&amp;gt; to full width characters.
amazon (az): &amp;lt;query&amp;gt; &amp;ndash; Searches Amazon for query
antonym: &amp;lt;word&amp;gt; - Returns a list of antonyms for &amp;lt;word&amp;gt;.
ask (gonzobot, gonzo, cb, cleverbot): &amp;lt;text&amp;gt; - chat with cleverbot.com
awesome (iscool, cool): - Prints a webpage to show &amp;lt;nick&amp;gt; how awesome they are.
ban: &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt; &amp;lt;user&amp;gt; - bans &amp;lt;user&amp;gt; in &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt;, or in the caller&amp;rsquo;s channel if no channel is specified ( Permission required: op_ban, op, chanop)
bancount: &amp;lt;user&amp;gt; - gets a count of &amp;lt;user&amp;gt;&amp;rsquo;s minecraft bans from fishbans
band (la): &amp;lt;artist&amp;gt; - displays information about &amp;lt;artist&amp;gt;.
bang: - when there is a duck on the loose use this command to shoot it.
bans (fishbans): &amp;lt;user&amp;gt; - gets information on &amp;lt;user&amp;gt;&amp;rsquo;s minecraft bans from fishbans
base64: &amp;lt;string&amp;gt; &amp;ndash; Encode &amp;lt;string&amp;gt; with base64.
bdsm (dominate): &amp;lt;user&amp;gt; - Just a little bit of kinky fun.
beats: - Gets the current time in .beats (Swatch Internet Time).
beer: &amp;lt;user&amp;gt; - gives beer to &amp;lt;user&amp;gt;
befriend: - when there is a duck on the loose use this command to befriend it before someone else shoots it.
bible (passage): &amp;lt;passage&amp;gt; - Prints the specified passage from the Bible
bing (b): &amp;lt;query&amp;gt; - returns the first bing search result for &amp;lt;query&amp;gt;
bingimage (bis): &amp;lt;query&amp;gt; - returns the first bing image search result for &amp;lt;query&amp;gt;
bitcoin (btc): - Returns the current bitcoin value
bite: &amp;lt;user&amp;gt; - bites &amp;lt;user&amp;gt;
boobs (boobies): - prints boobies!
bookpun: - Suggests a pun of a book title/author.
books (gbooks): &amp;lt;query&amp;gt; - Searches Google Books for &amp;lt;query&amp;gt;.
bottomten (pointsbottom, hated): - prints the top 10 things with the lowest points in the channel. To see the bottom 10 items in all of the channels the bot sits in use .</description></item><item><title>Ban Appeal</title><link>http://localhost:1313/banappeal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 21:49:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/banappeal/</guid><description>G-Line / Z-Line If you received a message when attempting to connect stating that you&amp;rsquo;re banned, you may raise a ticket at https://support.snoonet.org/ with the exact ban message, your nickname/nicknames you&amp;rsquo;ve recently used and any information you have about why the ban might have been applied.
Some bans are applied by network security robots, for example, if you accidentally flood a channel or mass highlight a group of individuals. In instances like these, the ban will be removed as we are made aware of it. Again, please raise a ticket and include as many relevant details as possible.
Where a ban has been applied based on your actions, we still encourage you to contact us. We prefer to resolve issues through communication where possible, and we may use our discretion to lower/remove the ban entirely if ample reason and apology is given.
Bans for being on a blacklist / Open Proxy Bans When you connect to Snoonet, your IP address will be queried against known bad host/open proxy blacklists. Additionally, in order to protect our network against unknown threats, this network utilizes the Hybrid Open Proxy Monitor which scans specific commonly used ports on your host for open proxies. By connecting to Snoonet, you agree to be scanned. Scans will originate from scan.snoonet.org.
If you are banned because your IP address appears on one (or more) blacklists, you must address your concern directly with the blacklist identified in the ban message and ask for your IP to be removed. Snoonet is not responsible for the accuracy of the information contained in these blacklists. Until your IP(s) are removed, you may be repeatedly banned from connecting to Snoonet.
Identify before connecting (GA-Line) ISPs which include but are not limited to mobile service providers and public bouncers may be required to have their users identify to a valid NickServ account before connecting to Snoonet. We enforce this measure as these connections have been abused in the past.
To use SASL authentication, you may register an account at https://anope.snoonet.org (if you don&amp;rsquo;t already have one) and configure your client to use your registered username and password. We apologize for the inconvenience, but we feel this measure is necessary to help us maintain a fair, positive, and well-moderated community.</description></item><item><title>Volunteer Recruitment</title><link>http://localhost:1313/volunteer-recruitment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 21:47:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/volunteer-recruitment/</guid><description>Sorry, we are not currently accepting applications at this time.
If you have ideas about how we can accomplish these goals and have some spare time to volunteer, we would love to hear from you. Community volunteers will assist with a variety of things, including sharing your opinions on staff projects, helping with future events &amp;amp; contests, and helping us bring new communities to Snoonet.
Specifically, community volunteers will work with subreddit communities and provide advice to staff. Volunteers will help expand the subreddit communities on Snoonet and focus on helping them get set up and providing them with general support and assistance. Community volunteers will consult with communities, specifically with an eye to understanding their needs and advising staff on tools and policies that should be developed to assist with community moderation and growth.
We are primarily looking for people with ideas, energy, and a willingness to contribute to the community. Community volunteers will not be network operators, and as such, extensive familiarity with IRC commands, prior experience, and a specific time commitment are not required. We are looking for people with knowledge of basic IRC commands, including how to set up channels and assist others in that respect. If joining Snoonet staff is something that interests you, this would be a great way to get to know us, gain experience working with our communities, and be considered for future staffing needs.
If you are interested in applying, please visit the Volunteer Application and send an application to apply [at] snoonet.</description></item><item><title>SubWatch</title><link>http://localhost:1313/subwatch/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 21:38:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/subwatch/</guid><description>SubWatch is a thread announcer bot, it will alert the channel of new threads posted in subreddits of your choosing. It&amp;rsquo;s able to watch private subreddits and announce threads based on keywords in the title.
You can view the source code here.
If you need assistance, you can /join #subwatch and ask for help.
How do I get SubWatch in my channel? /invite SubWatch - If you are a channel operator or have invite privileges, just /invite SubWatch to your channel as you would any other user.
What are the commands? $add &amp;lt;subreddit&amp;gt; +/-[keywords] [subreddit] etc&amp;hellip;
This will add a new subreddit to be watched in the channel. Keywords are optional and must be separated with &amp;ldquo;|&amp;rdquo;. If the subreddit has already been added, you can use this command to add new keywords to the list.
Example: $add pics +puppy +kitten -rabbit will post new threads from /r/pics if they have &amp;ldquo;puppy&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;kitten&amp;rdquo; in the title, but not &amp;ldquo;rabbit&amp;rdquo;.
$del &amp;lt;subreddit&amp;gt; +/-[key|words] [subreddit] etc&amp;hellip;
This will remove a subreddit from the channel&amp;rsquo;s watch list. If keywords are specified, they will be removed from the keyword list and the subreddit will continue to be watched on the channel.
$list
This will list the subreddits currently being watched on the channel, along with any keywords that have been set.
$stop/$start
This will pause and unpause SubWatch on the channel.
$clear
This will clear the watch list for the channel.
$help
This will print the command usage in the channel.
Note: you must have +o or +h in the channel to use add/del/stop/start/clear.
How to add private subreddits - Add /u/SnoonetSubWatch as an approved submitter to the subreddit.
- Create a wiki page at /r/[subreddit]/wiki/subwatch and add the name of the channel to grant permission. You can separate multiple channels with a comma, the content of the page for a single channel should simply be #channelname.
- Make sure the wiki isn&amp;rsquo;t disabled on the subreddit.
- Add the subreddit as normal.</description></item><item><title>Guide Handbook</title><link>http://localhost:1313/guide-handbook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 21:30:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/guide-handbook/</guid><description>Overview As a Community Guide, you are tasked with assisting users in familiarizing themselves and getting setup on IRC, as well as providing support. With our new orangechat integration, Snoonet expects a large influx of users, many of whom will be using IRC for the first time - some directly via Kiwi or a client of their choice and many through our custom designed IRC&amp;lt;&amp;mdash;&amp;gt;OC link.
Your role here on Snoonet will be critical to helping Snoonet as a community. This Handbook outlines all the information you need to know. Please read it carefully and familiarize yourself with its contents. While we understand everyone is a volunteer and wants to have a good time, it is important that this Handbook is followed to ensure that users feel comfortable using our network. Ask a staff member in #staff (discussed below) if you have any questions.
Access As Community Guides, you are assigned a special vHost in the format snoonet/guide/username, which grants you access to #staff, for conducting community and guide-related business, and #optalk, for communicating with OPs of large network channels. Please keep all guide-related business in #staff, with the exception of specific user assistance as outlined below.
These channels also grant you access to Sherlock, a user tracking bot used for checking if someone is ban evading. Instructions for using Sherlock can be found here. Information from the bot is not to be shared outside of #staff and #optalk.
Automatic half-op is enabled in #optalk, #help, #snoonet, and #staff. However, Community Guides are not granted any OPER or services access beyond what you already have on a per-channel basis as an OP or half-OP.
Policies and Procedures For our standard set of network rules see the network rules page
Information about Snoonet BNC can be found on the BNC page
The guidelines for channels can be found on the channel rules page
More info
Important Resources Channel modes
User modes
Anope Commands
Snoonet Bots
Why Snoonet
NickServ: /ns help ChanServ: /cs help BotServ: /bs help MemoServ: /ms help IRC: /helpop
Assisting Users As Community Guides, you are expected to assist users in #help with general network and IRC support queries. Remember to always be polite and understand that many users are not familiar with how IRC works. Topics and discussions in #help are to be kept only to network related support - general discussions should be moved to #snoonet or a relevant on-topic channel.</description></item><item><title>Statistics</title><link>http://localhost:1313/statistics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 21:29:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/statistics/</guid><description>Statistics will be shutdown on Thursday, May 24th until a suitable replacement has been created.
In anticipation of the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) coming into effect on May 25, 2018, Statistics will no longer be offered as a network service. All data collected by the bot will be erased. We will be working on a GDPR-compatible option but have no planned release at this time.
Our current plans are to develop the replacement at this github repo: https://github.com/snoonetIRC/StatsBot
If you have any questions, please join us in #help and ask!</description></item><item><title>Snoonet bots</title><link>http://localhost:1313/bots/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 22:04:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/bots/</guid><description>Snoonet offers custom services and bots catered to reddit and unique to our network.
These channel bots have been created specifically for our users! Any channel op can /invite them. Click on the links below for commands and instructions. gonzobot - a customized Cloudbot implementation for the communities on Snoonet. SubWatch - automatically posts subreddit threads, is able to watch private subreddits and announce threads based on keywords in the title. *If you have any issues or feature suggestions, please feel free to create a support ticket!</description></item><item><title>InspIRCd help system</title><link>http://localhost:1313/helpop/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 22:03:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/helpop/</guid><description>InspIRCd Help System Categories: [User Commands](#User Commands)
User modes
Channel modes
Extended Bans
Key:
&amp;lt;these brackets&amp;gt; denote required information.
{these brackets} denote that you may pick one of the options presented.
[these brackets] denote entirely optional parameters.
User Commands back to top
General User Command Help:
/helpop CUSER
*This will list user commands. To see the detailed instructions for a command type /helpop [COMMAND]. Without a [COMMAND] parameter, this will list all /helpop commands and descriptions.
To change your nickname on Snoonet to a new nick type:
/NICK &amp;lt;newnick&amp;gt;
To join a channel type:
/JOIN &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt;
To join two or more channels type:*
/JOIN &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt;,&amp;lt;channel&amp;gt;
To leave a channel type:
/PART &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt;
To leave two or more channels type:
/PART &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt;,&amp;lt;channel&amp;gt;
To cycle (leave and rejoin) a channel type:
/CYCLE &amp;lt;channel
This overrides restrictions that would stop a new user joining, such as user limits and channel keys.
To send a message to a user or channel specified in type:
/PRIVMSG &amp;lt;target&amp;gt; &amp;lt;text&amp;gt;
To send a notice to a user or channel specified in type:
/NOTICE &amp;lt;target&amp;gt; &amp;lt;text&amp;gt;
To send a notice to a channel, such as one that is set it invite-only, indicating that you would like to join type:
/KNOCK &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt; [message to channel]
To set the mode for a channel or a nickname specified in type:
/MODE &amp;lt;target&amp;gt; {+|-}&amp;lt;modes&amp;gt;[{+|-}&amp;lt;modes&amp;gt;] [mode parameters]
A user may only set modes upon themselves, and may not set the +o usermode. A user may only change channel modes of channels where they are at least a halfoperator.
A list of User modes
A list of Channel modes
To devoice yourself from a specified channel type:
/DEVOICE &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt;
To retrieve a channel topic type:
/TOPIC &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt;
To set a channel topic you must be either halfoperator, or the channel mode must be set to +t. To change the channel topic to one you provide type:
/TOPIC &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt; &amp;lt;topic&amp;gt;
To kick a user from a channel type:
/KICK &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt; &amp;lt;nick&amp;gt; [reason]
You must be at least a halfoperator to kick a user from a channel.
To remove a user from a channel type:
/REMOVE &amp;lt;nick&amp;gt; &amp;lt;channel&amp;gt; [reason]
You must be at least a halfoperator to remove a user from a channel. A removed user will part with a message stating they were removed from the channel and by whom. This command overrides auto-rejoin.</description></item><item><title>User modes</title><link>http://localhost:1313/umodes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 21:58:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/umodes/</guid><description> Syntax Description B Marks the user as a Bot. I Hides all channels a user is a member of in /WHOIS L Stops user from being redirected to another channel when joining a channel with +L that is full R User can only receive PRIVMSGs from registered (+r) users. S Strips control codes from messages to the user. (In Private Message/Notice) T Prevents you from receiving CTCP requests c Requires other users to be in a channel with the user before being able to PRIVMSG/NOTICE them. d Makes the user stop receiving channel PRIVMSGs/NOTICEs. g Provides control over who can private-message a user via /ACCEPT lists. h Marks an oper as available for help (Oper only) i User cannot be seen in /WHO o User is an IRC Operator r Marks a user as &amp;ldquo;registered and identified&amp;rdquo; from Services. w User can receive WALLOPS x Masks a users hostname. Disallows others from getting your IP address.</description></item><item><title>#android</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/android/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:35:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/android/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#apple</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/apple/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:35:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/apple/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#askscience</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/askscience/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:35:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/askscience/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#futurology</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/futurology/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:35:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/futurology/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#linux</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/linux/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:35:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/linux/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#linuxmasterrace</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/linuxmasterrace/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:35:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/linuxmasterrace/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#pcmasterrace</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/pcmasterrace/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:35:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/pcmasterrace/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#physics</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/physics/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:35:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/physics/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#programming</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/programming/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:35:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/programming/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#science</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/science/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:35:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/science/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#snoonet</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/snoonet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:35:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/snoonet/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#space</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/space/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:35:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/space/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#technology</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/technology/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:35:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/technology/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#techsupportgore</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/techsupportgore/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:35:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/techsupportgore/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#trackers</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/trackers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:35:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/trackers/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#v8supercars</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/v8supercars/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:35:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/v8supercars/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#bicycling</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/bicycling/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:32:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/bicycling/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#climbing</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/climbing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:32:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/climbing/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#f1</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/f1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:32:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/f1/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#fantasyfootball</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/fantasyfootball/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:32:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/fantasyfootball/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#formula-e</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/formula-e/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:32:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/formula-e/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#hockey</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/hockey/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:32:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/hockey/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#longboarding</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/longboarding/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:32:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/longboarding/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#motogp</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/motogp/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:32:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/motogp/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#peloton</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/peloton/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:32:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/peloton/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#redditsquaredcircle</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/redditsquaredcircle/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:32:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/redditsquaredcircle/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#wec</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/wec/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:32:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/wec/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#casualconversation</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/casualconversation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/casualconversation/</guid><description>Can you give us a description of your community: what it&amp;rsquo;s about, what rules you may have and any resources you would like to include
We do. I like to change up the colors on our CSS page for different holidays throughout the year. We also have a neat announcement bar that pops up when you scroll down, it normally has a quirky quote on it. What sets your community apart from others?
/r/CasualConversation is a subreddit for general chat about almost anything that you can think of. The main rules here are to &amp;ldquo;respect others&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t take things too seriously.&amp;rdquo; Mostly we just want people to have a friendly place to have conversations but we do have a detailed rules page here. Oh we also have a Snoonet rules page. We have a bunch of resources for our community, our Steam group, Music room, Minecraft server and of course our Snoonet channel.
What inspired this community?
I was looking through reddit to find a general chat type subreddit but I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find one. So I thought I would try and make my own and well I guess it worked. Sort of like an &amp;ldquo;off topic&amp;rdquo; like what you would see on message boards but for reddit. What sets your community apart from others?
Our community is extremely friendly. Maybe even too friendly. We also have pretty great CSS on our sub. What is your goal with this community?
To have a place to chat with strangers with a great atmosphere. What is your community (in)famous for?
Idk I guess just circlejerking about how friendly we are. What is the most popular post of all time in the subreddit?
So&amp;hellip; I had a birthday and got no gifts. I think this shows a lot of what this community is all about. Do you have any favorite quotes or posts from your users?
I&amp;rsquo;m sure if I went digging I would find the one I liked but I just can&amp;rsquo;t think of it at the moment. What do you hope your community gains from this subreddit?
A sense of learning how to be an all around better person, sharing your stories and maybe making some new friends. Some threads in the sub has already show how our sub has impacted people&amp;rsquo;s lives for the better.</description></item><item><title>#dag</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/dag/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/dag/</guid><description>#dag is a channel created by people - for people. We are a community that communities more than most communities could ever hope to community - and our aim is to continue communitying until we become to best community amongst all communities. We would love to have more people that are passionate about peopling to help us community even more so than we already do.
We are currently attempting to train dagbot (@dagb0t) to be a genuine, passionate, peopling person - so far, we have had no luck. If you wish to contribute to moulding dagbot&amp;rsquo;s future, please, feel free to join us.</description></item><item><title>#drama</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/drama/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/drama/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#foreveralone</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/foreveralone/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/foreveralone/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#foxes</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/foxes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/foxes/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#frogscast</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/frogscast/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/frogscast/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#fuckduck</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/fuckduck/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/fuckduck/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#fucking</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/fucking/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/fucking/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#hugs</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/hugs/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/hugs/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#IRCDrama</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/ircdrama/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/ircdrama/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#mingle</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/mingle/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/mingle/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#misanthrope</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/misanthrope/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/misanthrope/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#mnfh</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/mnfh/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/mnfh/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#offtopic</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/offtopic/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/offtopic/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#pornoverlords</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/pornoverlords/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/pornoverlords/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#random</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/random/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/random/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#skuldsux</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/skuldsux/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/skuldsux/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#talk</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/talk/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/talk/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#trollchromosomes</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/trollchromosomes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/trollchromosomes/</guid><description>( /r/TrollChromosomes)
Can you give us a description of your community: what it&amp;rsquo;s about, what rules you may have and any resources you would like to include?
We are #TrollChromsomes, the official IRC Chat for all the troll subs, mainly TrollXChromosomes and TrollYChromosome. We welcome all to come check us out! We are a safe and friendly place, and whether you go to the troll subs or just have found us from the server, we&amp;rsquo;d love to have you. The more the merrier. But even your favorite bar has rules, and you can find ours here What inspired this community?
One day two of the original founders separately saw a post in /r/trollx advertising the newly made subreddit of /r/troll4troll. They started a conversation in the comments that there should be an IRC channel for the community and later on that day (Friday, May 2nd 2014) we had a channel created over on Freenode. Not even a month later we were moved to Snoonet for a variety of reasons. What sets your community apart from others?
We wanted to be welcoming to people and we&amp;rsquo;ve been told by numerous users that we&amp;rsquo;re the friendliest channel on the server. Most of our users tell us they haven&amp;rsquo;t even wandered out to the rest of Snoonet or IRC. But besides the friendliness? Imagine all of the openness, humor, and sense of community you feel in both TrollX and TrollY? Well that&amp;rsquo;s what you get with #TrollChromosomes! What is your goal with this community?
Being an offshoot of the TrollX/YChromosome(s) communities, we strive to make all trolls happy. If you like IRC and you like TrollX and TrollY, then hopefully you&amp;rsquo;ll enjoy the chat with us. We just like having a place where people can hangout and reply to people instantly, instead of like on the website where comments are a lot slower and it&amp;rsquo;s sometimes not as easy to make friends that way unless you are very active in the communities. It&amp;rsquo;s also easier to make friends in the channel if you&amp;rsquo;re more of a lurker in the subreddits. What is your community (in)famous for?
We are famous for our kindness and friendliness! We are still young though and there are so many cool things we have planned! What is the most popular post of all time in the subreddit?
This is the most popular post and honestly I think it represents us pretty well sometimes: http://redd.</description></item><item><title>#trollxy</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/trollxy/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/trollxy/</guid><description/></item><item><title>##neopets rules</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/neopets/rules/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/neopets/rules/</guid><description>Welcome to the ##neopets IRC channel!
This is a place for Neopians to discuss things. Have fun, relax, join in the conversations, or start your own conversation. There are some rules that you will need to abide by, in addition to the general Snoonet Rules:
No racism, homophobia, transphobia, harassment, or bigotry of any kind. Don&amp;rsquo;t be a dick. The Channel OPs reserve the right to interpret dickishness. No flooding or spamming the channel. Do not ask for personal information. Do not post personal information of others. This is grounds for a network ban. Mark all NSFW or NSFL links as such. If you can&amp;rsquo;t open it in front of a church, it needs to be marked. Respect your fellow users. No harassment or trolling of any kind. If you want to talk dirty, send nudes, or use bigoted language: do it in PM. If you want to argue about the channel rules, do it in PM. Multiple warnings will result in removal from the channel or a ban. All kicks/removals/bans are at the discretion of the channel OPs.
If you have any issues with a user in the channel or need help you can type the name of an OP to get their attention, or you can /msg opsname message.
If you are new to IRC here are a few starter commands— To change your name from a Snooname:
/nick username To set auto-join:
/msg NickServ AJOIN ADD ##neopets When you&amp;rsquo;ve picked a nick that you like and you are ready to hang around, we recommend registering your name:
/msg NickServ REGISTER password email See Snoonet&amp;rsquo;s Help and; Guidelines for more.</description></item><item><title>##PartyMansion rules</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/partymansion/rules/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/partymansion/rules/</guid><description>We want ##PartyMansion to be a fun place for hedonism, coke, booze, strippers, and Dr Phil worship. Don&amp;rsquo;t be a dick and spoil the party for everyone else. Since &amp;ldquo;don&amp;rsquo;t be a dick&amp;rdquo; seems to be misunderstood, here is a comprehensive list of rules in place that you will need to follow in order for ##PartyMansion to remain a happy place of food porn, shitty music, and poor meme-ing.
##PartyMansion&amp;rsquo;s Rules:
Don&amp;rsquo;t be a dick. &amp;ndash; To expand, don&amp;rsquo;t do anything to intentionally attack another user. If a channel op requests for you to stop; stop. Failure to do so will result in a kick/quiet, and possibly a channel ban. Depending on the nature of the incident, the ban may be permanent. We have a very strong no-dick policy.
No real names! Refrain from using the names of users in the channel - respect their right to privacy and refer to them by their IRC nicks only.
Don&amp;rsquo;t be a dick.
No homophobic/racist/transphobic/sexist or otherwise discriminatory language or sentiments. Please bear in mind that not everyone is from the same walk of life as you are, words you might find acceptable can be offensive to others. In these cases, please refer to Rule #1.
Don&amp;rsquo;t be a dick.
No excessive bot spam. Bots in their nature can be very spammy and we understand this, but please respect the channel and exercise restraint.
Don&amp;rsquo;t be a dick.
No flooding. If you have logs or something similar to post, put them in a paste at either privatepaste.com or pastebin.com.
Don&amp;rsquo;t be a dick.
Tag your NSFW pictures/links.
Don&amp;rsquo;t be a dick.
Lurking is discouraged. We regularly remove lurkers from the channel, so please make an attempt to be part of the community. This is us looking out for our channel regulars and not a slight on you &amp;ndash; a channel filled with lurkers is a channel filled with potential leaks. Lurking in its broadest sense is failure to participate in the channel after multiple warnings/pings, yet being active elsewhere.
If any problems arise, feel free to contact a channel op/halfop via PM.
&amp;ndash;Please note that all kicks/bans are at the discretion of the channel ops. If you have concerns with any of the decisions made then please contact one of the ops via private message so as not to disrupt the channel further&amp;ndash;</description></item><item><title>##troll_politics rules</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/troll_politics/rules/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/troll_politics/rules/</guid><description>In addition to the usual Snoonet network rules, follow the channel rules:
DON&amp;rsquo;T BE A SHITWEASEL. Mods reserve the right to interpret shitweaselness. No sexism, racism, homophobia, transphobia, harassment or rudeness will be tolerated. If you are experiencing current harassment in the chat, whether in the main room or private chat, please copy the log and email the transcript to an active op, or if none are available to Ops@TrollChromosomes.com and the mods will respond appropriately. No unsolicited PMs. This means you. Do not advertise. This includes, but is not limited to, public spam, private message spam, repeated solicitation of services, and solicitation of other network channels. Posting the personal information of others is grounds for a permanent ban. Attempting to collect personal info of users is dealt with in the same manner. A good rule of thumb is if you have to log into to see it, you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t share it. Exchanges for money, goods, or services are strictly prohibited. No NSFW links allowed unless it relates to political content. Please respect your fellow users. Do not intentionally harass other users. This includes &amp;ldquo;trolling.&amp;rdquo; Get along with others! We understand that there are multiple types of humor, but do not excessively attack any other user on this network. Please note that sarcasm doesn&amp;rsquo;t translate well over IRC. Please be mindful that this is an internet chat room mostly consisting of trollX- &amp;amp; Yers – we enjoy the fact that we can have a friendly, welcoming atmosphere for people that can also be very flirty and sexual too. If anyone asks you to back off because they feel uncomfortable from your attention or words, please feel mindful that this isn&amp;rsquo;t a personal attack on you but instead the person in question just wants to feel comfortable. 18+ members only Want to talk dirty? Do it in a PM. Want to send nudes? Do it in PM.</description></item><item><title>#asianladyboners</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/asianladyboners/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/asianladyboners/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#askmen</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/askmen/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/askmen/</guid><description>Can you give us a description of your community: what it&amp;rsquo;s about, what rules you may have and any resources you would like to include?
#askmen is the IRC channel for the /r/AskMen subreddit. We&amp;rsquo;re here to allow subreddit participants to talk to each other. Only rules are be respectful, listen to the ops as directed, and have fun!
What inspired this community?
This channel gives /r/AskMen subreddit members a place to come and casually talk to one another.
What is your community (in)famous for?
Being a place where people can ask male-centric questions and get honest and helpful answers.
What is the most popular post of all time in the subreddit?
http://www.reddit.com/r/AskMen/comments/2avcur/hey_men_i_dont_think_you_get_enough_credit_for/</description></item><item><title>#aspergers</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/aspergers/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/aspergers/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re the official IRC channel for the subreddit /r/aspergers. You can sum us up in two words: socializing and support. Our primary function is to be a place for people on the entire Autistic Spectrum to have a safe and friendly place to chat, socialize, and discuss anything and everything. We&amp;rsquo;re also a support channel for folks dealing with a new diagnosis, mental health issues, or needing general advice. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter if you&amp;rsquo;re diagnosed or not, everyone is welcome!
We&amp;rsquo;ve got people on at all times of the day, across all sorts of time-zones. Activity wanes and grows all the time but you&amp;rsquo;re welcome to idle about for as long as you want, or jump in and start or join a conversation. If you need any help, just chat to one of the channel staff and we&amp;rsquo;ll get back to you as soon as we&amp;rsquo;re available.
We look forward to seeing you in the channel soon and we hope you have fun. You can see some more information about the channel and our rules here.</description></item><item><title>#aspergers rules</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/aspergers/rules/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/aspergers/rules/</guid><description>All operator actions are discretionary. If an op asks you do something, there is probably a good reason for it! If you want to argue your case, either head over to the channel ##AspergersOpTalk or PM us. We can be reasonable.
All Network rules cascade down to all channels. Read the snoonet network rules here.
Our channel rules are as follows
Be respectful towards other users. Bullying and attacking people for any reason will not be tolerated. Stalking or broadcasting personally identifiable information about a user will result in an immediate and permanent ban. Keep debates friendly and constructive. See the section &amp;ldquo;On debates&amp;rdquo; for more information. You are expected to be reasonably appropriate. This means, for example, don&amp;rsquo;t engage in sexual roleplay in the public channel Don&amp;rsquo;t bring outside drama into the channel! Resolve it in private. No spamming. Tag all NSFW content, this includes links and image links Please keep any logs of the channel private, some users may share things in channel that they would prefer not sent to others outside of the channel On debates: It appears that the stereotype that people on the Spectrum love to argue is true! We often have debates in the channel about all sorts of interesting topics. Our userbase has many differing opinions, and it can be fun to challenge and discuss these. But remember that there is a fine line between a healthy debate and a fight. Do not exchange insults, do not provoke someone who is not interested in a debate, and do not be abusive toward someone who disagrees with you. If you start personally attacking someone for their beliefs, you&amp;rsquo;ve automatically lost the argument and you might be kicked by an operator. In other words; play nice.
Debates can also get out of hand and start disrupting the normal flow of conversation of the channel. It&amp;rsquo;s very easy for only a few debating people to totally dominate the channel. It&amp;rsquo;s also very easy for you to become impassioned by an on-going debate, and not see how your conversation is obstructing other people from speaking. Be mindful of this. If an Op asks you to stop or move the debate, please do so. Check out the below section &amp;ldquo;On #aspergers-alt&amp;rdquo; for information on where you can go to continue your debate elsewhere.
On general behaviour: Even though most of us are on the Autistic Spectrum, you should have a general idea of what is polite and socially acceptable.</description></item><item><title>#casualconversation rules</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/casualconversation/rules/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/casualconversation/rules/</guid><description>#casualconversation Looking for live conversation? Share a story, ask a question, or start a conversation about anything you desire in our IRC channel. Maybe you&amp;rsquo;ll make some friends in the process.
Starter Commands If you are new to IRC, here are a few starter commands—
To change your name from a Snooname: /nick username
Set auto-join: /msg NickServ AJOIN ADD #casualconversation
Send someone a PM: /query username
Tag or ping someone type the first few letters of their nickname and hit tab
And when you&amp;rsquo;re feelin' comfy, we recommend registering your name: /msg NickServ REGISTER password email
→ See IRC Prelude &amp;amp; Snoonet&amp;rsquo;s Help &amp;amp; Guidelines for more.
Rules Be what you want other people to be. Like on the /r/casualconversation, when in the channel you should aim to be as polite as possible. This makes others feel welcome and conversations can take place without users being rude to one another.
Respect others. Remember—you&amp;rsquo;re speaking with humans.
Don&amp;rsquo;t take things too seriously. Keep it casual. We are all here to have a nice time chatting it up so let&amp;rsquo;s all just have a good time.
Warning(s) will be given for…
Posting NSFW links and excessive immature sexual discussion Flooding and spamming the channel Abusing the bots Advertising and self-promotion Posting memes Discussing subreddit drama &amp;amp; Any other behavior that holds up the general conversation Kicks are stern warnings. Multiple warnings or kicks will result in a ban at the discretion of the channel Ops.
→ All #casualconversation rules fall under the umbrella rules of Reddit and Snoonet&amp;rsquo;s Network.
Moderators The role of mods is to regulate the channel and to keep the collective chill by enforcing the rules above.
Extras Syntax Function /me action Posts an action .tell nick Leaves a message /whois nick or /ns info nick Check info /ns GROUP Adds nick to group /ns IDENTIFY password Identifies nick /ns GHOST password Claims nick References / Resources Channel Stats
Basics IRC Prelude by irchelp.org, Snoonet Help
Bot Gonzobot Command List
Signs of Life /r/irc, /r/snoonet, #snoonet, #help
^Feedback? ^Message ^the ^Mods ^· ^Made ^with ^♥</description></item><item><title>#depression-alt rules</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/depression-alt/rules/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/depression-alt/rules/</guid><description>#depression-alt Purpose #depression-alt provides a space away from #depression where the rules are relaxed. Certain topics normally prohibited in the main channel will be permitted here, meaning that discretion is advised.
If you can not handle discussion of self harm and/or more specific suicide methods, it is advised to immediately /part or /leave the channel. Network and channel rules still apply. Please see below for more information.
Channel Operators The team handling #depression-alt is the same team that currently handles the #depression channel.
If you need to contact an operator for assistance, you may find a list of operators by clicking here.
Rules &amp;amp; Guidelines In order to encourage open discussion, try to keep discussions in the channel. Please use discretion when discussing certain sensitive topics (such as politics and/or religion) in the channel. You may not advertise your own channel or service through our channel or directly through our users unless authorization has been provided by channel operators. Please refrain from bringing drama into our channel from other IRC channels. Additionally, please do not share others' personal information in the channel. Graphic depictions of specific suicide/self harm methods and abuse as well as glorification of suicide/self harm are prohibited in this channel. Any decisions made by our operators are final. If you believe that a decision made by particular operator is unfair, please try talking to that operator directly, or message another channel operator.</description></item><item><title>#r4r rules</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/r4r/rules/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/r4r/rules/</guid><description>#R4R Channel Rules
(Note: All subreddit rules are also required to be followed, visit the sidebar of the subreddit if you don&amp;rsquo;t know them. Snoonet rules are also to be followed and enforced)
Channel is strictly 18+
Don&amp;rsquo;t be an asshole. This goes for sexist generalizations, racist and homophobic slurs/remarks, ad hominems, being obnoxious, etc. In general, respect people&amp;rsquo;s boundaries and be civil. If someone finds your humor or choice of topic offensive, please respect that. If you feel that someone is being rude to you, please speak up and/or notify a mod as soon as possible.
Attention &amp;ldquo;whoring&amp;rdquo; is not tolerated in the channel. This means being overtly sexual, spamming pictures of yourself, asking for compliments, and just general attention seeking comments. Mods have the right to decide what is considered to be attention &amp;ldquo;whoring&amp;rdquo; and have the right to warn, kick, and ban if necessary.
Want to talk dirty? Do it in a PM. Want to send nudes? Do it in a PM. Want to ask for pictures? Do it in a PM.
For links containing nudity, please tag them NSFW when they are posted. People do IRC from work! For privacy and safety reasons, send nudes via PM and only when both parties want to send/see said pictures. Not everyone wants to see your, your brother&amp;rsquo;s, your grandma&amp;rsquo;s or your next door neighbour&amp;rsquo;s butt. Public decency. Please.
Blatant trolling, extreme creepy behavior, or making serious personal threats will typically be met with an immediate ban. However, since not every situation is the same, OPs reserve the right to warn/kick/ban as they see fit.
Do not come into the channel asking &amp;ldquo;ASL,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;WHERE R THE GIRLS?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;HOT GRLS PM ME!&amp;rdquo; and saying that the channel is a sausagefest. This is not a meat market.
Sending pms to those in the channel you do not know is prohobited, especially if they may be considered creepy or unsolicited. That includes asking ASL to every single person or messaging people with names that might seem &amp;lsquo;female&amp;rsquo; PMing should be secondary to communication in the channel. Talk to the people, get to know them!
Nothing said in here is private. However, don&amp;rsquo;t post people&amp;rsquo;s personal information without their consent (i.e., real names, Facebook profiles, etc.) This also includes scraping information from the chat and/or posting personal information from the chat publicly on the internet.</description></item><item><title>#reddit rules</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/reddit/rules/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/reddit/rules/</guid><description>Be reasonable and keep conversation interesting! We understand humor of all sorts, but don&amp;rsquo;t excessively attack or belittle another user in the channel. And though minor racist or otherwise abusive remarks may be accepted as a matter of course on IRC as well as Reddit, don&amp;rsquo;t make it your mission to &amp;lsquo;pick on&amp;rsquo; another user. Excessive racism and bigotry is not tolerated, and punishable by a ban.
Linking Tag links that are NSFW as [NSFW] - not every one wants to view mature content. Many are chatting from households, work offices, or just flat out don&amp;rsquo;t want to see that kind of stuff. Failure to do so will result in a warning and an eventual ban. Do not publish referral links without asking openly in the channel if people don&amp;rsquo;t mind you doing so. We&amp;rsquo;re not your army, but we also don&amp;rsquo;t mind helping friends in need.
Support your arguments Arguing with others is fine; it&amp;rsquo;s the way of life. However, if you&amp;rsquo;re going to argue a point to someone, maintain the high ground and be able to support your arguments with facts. As a whole we hate whiny arguments, so if you&amp;rsquo;re going to argue be smart about it and at least give others a reason to side with you.
Don&amp;rsquo;t flood and don&amp;rsquo;t repeat lines You will be automatically punished (a quiet or a kick) for doing so. If you continue to do it, it will be grounds for a channel ban.
Don&amp;rsquo;t be easily offended Don&amp;rsquo;t let remarks get to you. If something or someone on IRC is bothering you, discuss it with a channel operator. Keep in mind that if you&amp;rsquo;re offended often in #reddit, then the real world has quite a few surprises for you.</description></item><item><title>#socialskills rules</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/socialskills/rules/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/socialskills/rules/</guid><description>Hi, #socialskills is an irc channel hosted on snoonet for those looking to have friendly conversation and/or receive advice in regards to social relationships. Keep in mind that we are not professionals. For advice and help with mental health troubles #depression and #anxiety are better. Hope to see you there!
In addition to the general Snoonet Rules you will need to abide by the following channel rules:
Above all else, being socially awkward is ok, being mean is not Be respectful of others Keep in mind some of the people here are socially awkward, be patient with them Bringing drama from another channel is not allowed Circlejerks about how much you dislike someone in the chat are not allowed, you will be kicked/banned if you are seen participating in one Trolling and troll advice on socializing will result in punishment If you feel any of these rules have been broken please pm GhostyOne or one of the other OPs Have fun! Multiple warnings will result in removal from the channel or a ban. All kicks/removals/bans are at the discretion of the channel OPs.
If you have any issues with a user in the channel or need help you can type the name of an OP to get their attention, or you can /msg opsname message.
If you are new to IRC here are a few starter commands— To change your name from a Snooname:
/nick username To set auto-join:
/msg NickServ AJOIN ADD #socialskills When you&amp;rsquo;ve picked a nick that you like and you are ready to hang around, we recommend registering your name:
/msg NickServ REGISTER password email See Snoonet&amp;rsquo;s Help and; Guidelines for more.</description></item><item><title>#streetfighter rules</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/streetfighter/rules/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/streetfighter/rules/</guid><description>#StreetFighter Welcome to the official irc channel for /r/streetfighter on Snoonet! This channel is a place for Street Fighter fans to gather and discuss the games, strategies, tournaments, and more.
On this page you&amp;rsquo;ll find:
Channel Rules
Guide to a Pleasant IRC Experience
Links to Useful Information Outside of IRC
Channel Rules Everyone is welcome as long as they can follow these rules, as well as the Snoonet Network Rules:
Be kind to each other! Don&amp;rsquo;t be rude, don&amp;rsquo;t have a temper, and don&amp;rsquo;t be discriminatory. Show the people around you respect, and they&amp;rsquo;ll reciprocate.
Mark all NSFW links as such.
Please keep arguments civil. If things start to get out of hand, take it to a private message.
Please check back here every so often. The rules are a bit fluid and may change. It&amp;rsquo;s always a good idea to keep up to date!
Guide to a Pleasant IRC Experience Follow this quick guide for a more enjoyable IRC experience.
Use /nick to change your irc nick. We&amp;rsquo;d recommend your Reddit username, but it&amp;rsquo;s not required.
Use /msg nickserv register to create an account for your nick. This is a great way to make sure nobody can ever impersonate you.
Use /msg NickServ AJOIN ADD #streetfighter to add this channel to your autojoin list so that you&amp;rsquo;ll automatically join when you connect to SnooNet.
When looking for a game, state your region and platform. It&amp;rsquo;ll help you find other players faster. Example: &amp;ldquo;Anyone want to play SF4? I&amp;rsquo;m in the US on PC&amp;rdquo;
We have a really cool bot with commands like .schedule and .streams that&amp;rsquo;ll give you the schedule for whatever tournaments might be going on, as well as what Twitch channels they&amp;rsquo;re streaming on.
Links to Useful Information Outside of IRC The following are various links you might find useful in improving your SF4 game.
A glossary of Street Fighter terms and notation
/r/StreetFighter Beginner&amp;rsquo;s Guide
/r/StreetFighter Intermediate&amp;rsquo;s Guide
Miscellaneous Street Fighter and hardware informations
The Footsie Handbook by Sonic Hurricane</description></item><item><title>#Troll_NSFW rules</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/troll_nsfw/rules/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/troll_nsfw/rules/</guid><description>In addition to the usual Snoonet network rules, follow the channel rules:
DON&amp;rsquo;T BE A SHITWEASEL. Mods reserve the right to interpret shitweaselness. No sexism, racism, homophobia, transphobia, harassment or rudeness will be tolerated. If you are experiencing current harassment in the chat, whether in the main room or private chat, please copy the log and email the transcript to Ops@TrollChromosomes.com and the mods will respond appropriately. No unsolicited PMs. This means you. Do not advertise. This includes, but is not limited to, public spam, private message spam, repeated solicitation of services, and solicitation of other network channels. Posting the personal information of others is grounds for a permanent ban. Attempting to collect personal info of users is dealt with in the same manner. A good rule of thumb is if you have to log into to see it, you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t share it. Exchanges for money, goods, or services are strictly prohibited. Assume all links are NSFW. It&amp;rsquo;s still a good idea to mark them, and be as descriptive as possible. Please respect your fellow users. Do not intentionally harass other users. This includes &amp;ldquo;trolling.&amp;rdquo; Get along with others! We understand that there are multiple types of humor, but do not excessively attack any other user on this network. Please note that sarcasm doesn&amp;rsquo;t translate well over IRC. Please be mindful that this is an internet chat room mostly consisting of trollX- &amp;amp; Yers – we enjoy the fact that we can have a friendly, welcoming atmosphere for people that can also be very flirty and sexual too. If anyone asks you to back off because they feel uncomfortable from your attention or words, please feel mindful that this isn&amp;rsquo;t a personal attack on you but instead the person in question just wants to feel comfortable. 18+ members only Want to talk dirty? Do it in a PM. Want to send nudes? You can do it in the channel, but remember, there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of people in this channel. Do not make a big deal about the presence or absence of women in channel. The same goes for demanding pics, making a big deal about someone being female, specifically looking for women to talk to, etc. If you do not follow the rules, you may be muted, kicked, and/or banned at the discretion of the ops. If you have an issue with this, message the mod in question. Don&amp;rsquo;t drag your drama into the main channel or other channels.</description></item><item><title>A Guide to Being an Op in #anxiety</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/anxiety/mods/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:07:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/anxiety/mods/</guid><description>What is my job as an op? Help keep the channel as a safe and healing place that&amp;rsquo;s enjoyable to all who stop by and/or frequent the channel. Do this by: Be kind, remember to mind triggers like everyone else Making users feel welcome (welcoming new users to the channel when you can and involving users in conversations) Overseeing conversations in channel and keeping an eye out for rule breakers and trolls Stop people that are there solely to cause trouble (trolls - those pushing buttons on purpose) or anyone harassing another user Also by being a voiced user it lets other users know you are someone to PM if they are having issues either personal, or in the channel For any user that seems to be or claims to be suicidal, refer them to the suicide hotline 1 (800) 273-8255 - National Suicide Prevention Lifeline or http://www.suicide.org/international-suicide-hotlines.html. We are not professionals. If the problem persists, warn them that you will have to mute or ban them, if they persist; remove their chat privilege with !mute or !ban When issues come up what is the protocol for dealing with them? If you are online and available to users, stay oped in the channel, and de-oped if you are offline, busy, or otherwise unavailable. To op yourself just type in: !op and !deop to de-op yourself.
Use your discretion when dealing with problematic users. Sometimes a simple topic change could handle the situation. Sometimes a user may deserve a warning. Sometimes a user will not relent until they are banned. You may choose to PM a user about their behavior or maybe just gently prod them in channel. However you choose to do it, a warning is preferred before any more severe action. Try referring people to the link to #anxiety rules in the topic. Typically, the process should be: Warning (You may do this as many times as you feel necessary) Removal (You may do this as many times as you feel necessary) Ban (If a user returns after being banned, contact Snoonet staff as it is against Snoonet policy) Use this document to track troublemakers. Please try to include a reason and/or expiration for your bans when appropriate. Expiration is specified as an integer followed by one of d (days), h (hours), or m (minutes). Combinations (such as 1h30m) are not permitted. Feel free to discuss issues with your fellow ops/voiced users in #anxietymods.</description></item><item><title>#psychic</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/psychic/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:03:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/psychic/</guid><description>Can you give us a description of your community: what it&amp;rsquo;s about, what rules you may have and any resources you would like to include?
#Psychic is the official chatroom for /r/Psychic, the largest reddit community for psychics, intuitives, empaths or people interested in extrasensory perception.
The chatroom mostly serves as a place to chill and chat about anything, including topical things like psychics! Our rules are pretty simple, you can find them here. We also have a good resource for IRC information and help here if ever it&amp;rsquo;s required.
What inspired this community?
It was on a sunny April in 2016, when our resident Dane Luhaja was on a walk through Denmark, when something came to him. The wind, breezed across his face, as he attempted mindfulness. Finally, a psychic connection was made, and a vision came to him, &amp;ldquo;We need a chatroom&amp;rdquo;. Some say he frantically* ran to his computer, made a post to /r/Psychic in the hopes that his dreams would come true. Then, a mod appeared. They agreed, and the chatroom was made. The rest, as they say, is history.
*might be slightly embellished
What sets your community apart from others?
We are the largest psychic-related IRC channel (and subreddit) and we&amp;rsquo;ve all developed a close bond with each other.
There&amp;rsquo;s also the fact that we have literal occultists and spirit talkers here but that&amp;rsquo;s neither here nor there.
What is your goal with this community?
To create a chat for people with like-minded beliefs, but also to create a healthy environment that everyone can feel welcome to.
Does your community have any traditions or special events?
Aside from a secret santa/exchange we do, not particularly. Meetups have been organised before though.</description></item><item><title>#rainbow</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/rainbow/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:03:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/rainbow/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#RLB</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/rlb/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:03:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/rlb/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#uktrees</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/uktrees/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:03:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/uktrees/</guid><description>The only rule is NO SOURCING. Specifically:
Don&amp;rsquo;t try to buy or sell drugs here. Don&amp;rsquo;t ask where to buy or sell drugs. Don&amp;rsquo;t link to any darknet markets. Don&amp;rsquo;t give out contact info of dealers, or mention the names of darknet vendors. Channel Operators: rory &amp;amp; Iota</description></item><item><title>#wanttobelieve</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/wanttobelieve/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:03:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/wanttobelieve/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#astralprojection</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/astralprojection/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:03:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/astralprojection/</guid><description>Can you give us a description of your community: what it&amp;rsquo;s about, what rules you may have and any resources you would like to include? Its about people. About people who had out of body experiences (aka astral projections) and a place for them to express that. Its also for people wants to learn about them. We are the biggest subreddit in this niche. Mainly because our founders came together from three different subreddits with the same niche. We are happy to serve 4K people as of the time of writing this.
What inspired this community? A year or two back there were 3 (including this one) astral projection related subreddits. I use to frequent this one and sent a message to the mod of this sub(at that time) that I can help with css if he ever needs it. But that mod abandoned the sub and never got my message. Then as luck would have it , a new mod (/u/lobob123 ) took over this sub. /u/lobob123 read my message and replied back saying he was happy to receive any css help. I (/u/DaMan123456 ) of course accepted and did my best to upgrade the css and clean the sub. I really wanted to help out. While we were chatting and working on making /r/AstralProjection the best we could make it, we thought &amp;ldquo;why don&amp;rsquo;t we merge all the other related subs into one? This way we can a)serve more people and b) have all the information in one place.&amp;rdquo; And then me and /u/lobob123 set out do exactly that. We told our vision to make one big subreddit to /u/Captain_Midnight who at the time was running /r/OutOfBody. It was the second biggest to our sub. He was very kind and went along with the merger. Then came /r/astralprojectionnow. This sub had no mods, so I become the mod of this sub and then redirected everyone to /r/AstralProjection. Along the way we recieved help from /u/Psichonaut . So us four mods share a really cool connection in making all of this possible. But its mainly thanks to our readers we are here.
So TLDR: A desire to help out and a desire to be one big repository to and for all astral projection / out of body experience related thigns made this sub what it is.
What sets your community apart from others? We like to think its our helping attitude and commitment to our readers.</description></item><item><title>#atheism</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/atheism/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:03:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/atheism/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#freemasonry</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/freemasonry/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:03:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/freemasonry/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#genderqueer</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/genderqueer/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 10:03:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/genderqueer/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#england</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/england/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/england/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#israel</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/israel/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/israel/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#korean</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/korean/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/korean/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#maine</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/maine/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/maine/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#milwaukee</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/milwaukee/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/milwaukee/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#newzealand</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/newzealand/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/newzealand/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#philadelphia</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/philadelphia/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/philadelphia/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#philippines</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/philippines/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/philippines/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#portugal</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/portugal/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/portugal/</guid><description>Can you give us a description of your community: what it&amp;rsquo;s about, what rules you may have and any resources you would like to include?
Our community serves the purpose of discussing Portugal or portuguese in the world, that&amp;rsquo;s our main rule too. What inspired this community?
There was a need for it I guess. What sets your community apart from others?
We&amp;rsquo;re a friendly people and like to help strangers. We also have francesinhas and pastéis de nata. What is your goal with this community?
Discuss everything related to our beautiful country and help each others out. What is your community (in)famous for?
We once made the news but we don&amp;rsquo;t like to talk about that. What is the most popular post of all time in the subreddit?
Photos of an old Portugal. We have a flair just for our best posts and it&amp;rsquo;s one of the best there. Do you have any favorite quotes or posts from your users?
&amp;ldquo;Bitoque Caralho&amp;rdquo; What have you learned from being a part of this community?
I learned a lot about a range of subjects but I mostly developed a thick skin for some stuff Does your community have any traditions or special events?
On friday, every two weeks we have a thread where we discuss anything, in the other weeks we have a cultural thread. Sometimes we do some cultural exchanges with other national subreddits. Does your community have any associated social media or websites? (facebook/twitter/instagram/etc) Also, follow us on Twitter!
Not yet!</description></item><item><title>#r4r-Florida</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/r4r-florida/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/r4r-florida/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#russian</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/russian/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/russian/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#sanfrancisco</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/sanfrancisco/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/sanfrancisco/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#scotland</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/scotland/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/scotland/</guid><description>Can you give us a description of your community: what it&amp;rsquo;s about, what rules you may have and any resources you would like to include?
It&amp;rsquo;s fairly self explanatory, really. It&amp;rsquo;s the national subreddit for the country, Scotland! Open to any and all, though we have our number one rule that each post must be related to Scottish matters (either directly or indirectly). What inspired this community?
Again, self-explanatory - it&amp;rsquo;s the national subreddit! Much like /r/Columbia or /r/Iran. What sets your community apart from others?
We are extremely sarcastic, but very friendly. It sounds somewhat oxymoronic but hey - we like to think of ourselves complicated. What is your goal with this community?
Online bonds, general banter, sharing of news, making friends or a support group - whatever our subscribers want it to be. What is your community (in)famous for?
Swearing. Irreverence in general, really! We can take a joke, we can laugh at ourselves, we are very strongly opinionated but we are very friendly and I like to think helpful too :) What is the most popular post of all time in the subreddit?
That&amp;rsquo;s an easy one. This post of this image, during the referendum. That was a period of great turmoil in the sub! Do you have any favorite quotes or posts from your users?
I have one user in particular who I always enjoy reading comments from, but I won&amp;rsquo;t mention their name here as it would be a personal choice and it&amp;rsquo;s not up to me to mention them! But one of their comments that I love was on the topic of what it feels like to get kicked in the nuts: &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;d say it&amp;rsquo;s more like pain and nausea had a baby together, and that baby is trying to gnaw it&amp;rsquo;s way downward and out through your guts and ballsack.&amp;rdquo; What have you learned from being a part of this community?
Develop a thick skin. Don&amp;rsquo;t rise to the gr8 b8 m8. Does your community have any traditions or special events?
Hunners. The Homecoming, Rabbie Burns Night, St Andrew&amp;rsquo;s Day, Haggis, Irn Bru, Whisky&amp;hellip;the list goes on :) Does your community have any associated social media or websites? (facebook/twitter/instagram/etc) Also, follow us on Twitter!
Not yet!</description></item><item><title>#sudcamx</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/sudcamx/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/sudcamx/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#sweden</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/sweden/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/sweden/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#thenetherlands</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/thenetherlands/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/thenetherlands/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#toronto</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/toronto/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/toronto/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#uk</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/uk/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/uk/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#wales</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/wales/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/wales/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#austria</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/austria/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/austria/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#burlington</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/burlington/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/burlington/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#canada</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/canada/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/canada/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#dc</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/dc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/dc/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#denmark</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/denmark/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/denmark/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#europe</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/europe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/europe/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#fifthworld</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/fifthworld/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/fifthworld/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#iran</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/iran/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:57:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/iran/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#army</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/army/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/army/</guid><description>Can you give us a description of your community? /r/army is a community dedicated mostly to past, present, and future members of the United States Army, although it is open to other branches of the military, service men and women from other countries, and those who are just interested in the Army and its culture. We ask each other questions about daily goings-on, share pertinent news, support one another, entertain ourselves, and have informational threads where people can ask questions about the military on an open floor. It is not official nor does it necessarily represent the opinion of the US Army.</description></item><item><title>#badsubhub</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/badsubhub/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/badsubhub/</guid><description>Can you give us a description of your community: what it&amp;rsquo;s about, what rules you may have and any resources you would like to include?
Hi, we&amp;rsquo;re the #BadSubHub, otherwise known as the de facto /r/badhistory IRC channel (although anyone else on the badacademic subreddits are encouraged to come visit). /r/badhistory is the place where you can see bad history get taken down, in many cases with great aplomb. It&amp;rsquo;s /r/AskHistorians at the pub, where we&amp;rsquo;re all raging drunk and swearing like sailors.
We&amp;rsquo;re also part of the general /r/BadSubHub academy, which also includes subs like /r/badscience, /r/badlinguistics, /r/badlegaladvice, and /r/bad_religion. If there&amp;rsquo;s a discipline, there&amp;rsquo;s probably a badacademia subreddit for you to submit to.
The rest of the post will be dealing with /r/badhistory specifically, as most users in the IRC are /r/badhistory users.
What inspired this community?
It all started a long time ago, when one user decided that we need a sub to feature the large amounts of bad history found all over Reddit. Since then, we&amp;rsquo;ve grown to be the largest badacademia sub, complete with injokes and Nazi moderators all on our own. What sets your community apart from others?
/r/badhistory is known for Rule 5, or the &amp;ldquo;explain why your submission is bad history&amp;rdquo; rule. It&amp;rsquo;s the reason why the subreddit hasn&amp;rsquo;t completely descended into mindless circlejerking (although we do still jerk) and the reason why many people are attracted to the subreddit. What is your goal with this community?
Our goal is to debunk and discuss bad history that shows up, whether it&amp;rsquo;s from an article, a Reddit comment, a blog post, a TV show, a porno (yes, really), a comic, a commercial, etc. What is your community (in)famous for?
We&amp;rsquo;re known for, and in no particular order, our R5, our injokes, our devotion to Volcano, our fascist-communist-theist-Whig-drunk-SJW-pinko-statist-reactionary moderation team, and for being literally SRS (see /r/badhistory/wiki/accusations) What is the most popular post of all time in the subreddit?
A PSA: Do not trust heavily upvoted responses in AskHistorians just because they are upvoted and gilded. Do you have any favorite quotes or posts from your users?
We recently did a /r/bestof2014 contest, found here. Here, you can find what our subreddit considered our greatest hits in 2014. What do you hope your community gains from this subreddit?</description></item><item><title>#beermoney</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/beermoney/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/beermoney/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#ems</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/ems/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/ems/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#firefighting</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/firefighting/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/firefighting/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#history</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/history/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/history/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#math</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/math/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/math/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#mturk</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/mturk/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/mturk/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#protectandserve</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/protectandserve/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:51:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/protectandserve/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#againstmensrights</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/againstmensrights/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:46:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/againstmensrights/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#britishpolitics</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/britishpolitics/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:46:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/britishpolitics/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#news</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/news/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:46:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/news/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#politics</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/politics/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:46:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/politics/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#SyrianCivilWar</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/syriancivilwar/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:46:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/syriancivilwar/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#UkrainianConflict</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/ukrainianconflict/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 09:46:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/ukrainianconflict/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#guitar</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/guitar/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:09:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/guitar/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#kpop</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/kpop/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:09:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/kpop/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#listentothis</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/listentothis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:09:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/listentothis/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#metal</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/metal/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:09:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/metal/</guid><description>Can you give us a description of your community?
Our community is founded on the discussion of heavy metal music and its related news and events. The IRC channel is more relaxed than the subreddit and non-metal related general discussion is encouraged. Homophobia and racism are not permitted in the channel or the subreddit. What inspired this community?
&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;Satan. What sets your community apart from others?
We&amp;rsquo;ve had continuous activity for a number of years. We&amp;rsquo;re busy 24/7. And if nobody&amp;rsquo;s talking, there&amp;rsquo;s still someone idling waiting for conversation. What is your goal with this community?
Our IRC community has been running with a fairly consistent number of users for over three years, and is currently one of Snoonet&amp;rsquo;s most active chats. We would like to continue in a similar fashion but extend an invitation to new users. What is your community (in)famous for?
Our lawyers say we shouldn&amp;rsquo;t talk about it right now. But we&amp;rsquo;re pretty famous for our unimpeachable musical recommendations! Not a fan of metal? Come hang out for a while and you will be. What is the most popular post of all time in the subreddit?
Our top post of all time is a self-post discussion thread about the death of Slayer&amp;rsquo;s Jeff Hanneman from 2013. Way to be a downer, question guy. How about this also-popular post regarding a petition to allow Gwar to play the 2015 Super Bowl Halftime Show instead? Do you have any favorite quotes or posts from your users?
We have a bot that handles quotes for us. Let&amp;rsquo;s just say there&amp;rsquo;s a reason why /u/dustin_the_wind has 29 quotes stored on the bot. &amp;lt; sabytmobile_&amp;gt; Dunwich? &amp;lt; Dunwich&amp;gt; sabyt? &amp;lt; sabytmobile_&amp;gt; Hi &amp;lt; Dunwich&amp;gt; hi &amp;lt; grisher&amp;gt; hi &amp;lt;@Mike&amp;gt; hi &amp;lt;@Shreddit&amp;gt; hi &amp;lt; t_deg&amp;gt; hi &amp;lt; Jalkion&amp;gt; hi &amp;lt; Blasphemophagher&amp;gt; hi &amp;lt; jesusfucknugget&amp;gt; hi &amp;lt; quorthon&amp;gt; hi &amp;lt; grrrreg&amp;gt; hi What do you hope your community gains from this subreddit?
/r/metal is primarily a place to share and discuss music. There&amp;rsquo;s so much new music out there that we can&amp;rsquo;t possibly hope to have it all in one place, so it spills over to #metal. We&amp;rsquo;re also a great place to come for more in-depth recommendations. Whether you like grindcore, black metal, stoner, thrash, doom or any of the million other subgenres of metal, there&amp;rsquo;s someone in #metal who has devoted his or her life to being a pedant about it!</description></item><item><title>#music</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/music/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:09:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/music/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#radioreddit</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/radioreddit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:09:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/radioreddit/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#vaporwave</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/vaporwave/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:09:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/vaporwave/</guid><description>Can you give us a description of your community?
Vaporwave is a subculture that had started emerging at around 2010, and has become more prominent in the early 2010&amp;rsquo;s. The term originates from the term vaporware. It is considered a musical genre, as well as having a visual aesthetic. The genre has since developed and expanded, and the following is an attempt to describe &amp;ldquo;classic&amp;rdquo; /r/vaporwave/w/basics</description></item><item><title>##electronic</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/electronic/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:09:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/electronic/</guid><description>Can you give us a description of your community? ##electronic is created for members all across the Snoonet network to have a place to discuss and share their Electronic Music finds. The channel is going to be a place where fans of eletronic music can all share their music. The channel itself has a subwatch bot which has a plethora of electronic findings and has a few subs equipped to share music. Some of those include EDM, Chillstep and ElectronicMusic. However, we are always looking forward to expanding our collection and would encourage any and every newcomer to share their music. We may not be at our keyboards all the time! but we will reply eventually.</description></item><item><title>#crayonpop</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/crayonpop/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:09:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/crayonpop/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#folkpunk</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/folkpunk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:09:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/folkpunk/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#theoryofreddit</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/theoryofreddit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:06:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/theoryofreddit/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#toolbox</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/toolbox/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:06:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/toolbox/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#subredditdrama</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/subredditdrama/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:05:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/subredditdrama/</guid><description>/r/subredditdrama is where you go to watch other people on reddit argue. It was first started when there were several highly upvoted posts on /r/reddit.com about user-v-mod conflict. This is the very thread in which it was created.
Although it was initially founded to be a meta subreddit for general drama and calling out mod abuse, as the community grew (and became kinda witchhunt-y) new rules about neutrality were added and the subreddit&amp;rsquo;s purpose shifted to linking arguments. The mods idealize the subreddit as a place to draw entertainment out of other people fighting, but a lot of our users draw a lot of entertainment of discussing (and rehashing) the fights that are linked.
If you&amp;rsquo;re a meta redditor, if you like drama, or you want to know keep up with whatever current reddit shitstorm is brewing, /r/subredditdrama is the place.
#subredditdrama is a casual channel for discussion of drama and just about anything else. Saying mean things about MillenniumFalc0n will earn you the respect of every one. Except MillenniumFalc0n, of course, because he hates fun.</description></item><item><title>#srs</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/srs/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:05:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/srs/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#circlebroke</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/circlebroke/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:04:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/circlebroke/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#enhancement</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/enhancement/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:04:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/enhancement/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#modclub</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/modclub/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:04:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/modclub/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#srdbroke</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/srdbroke/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:04:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/srdbroke/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#automoderator</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/automoderator/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:03:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/automoderator/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#worldbuilding</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/worldbuilding/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:01:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/worldbuilding/</guid><description>#worldbuilding is a DIY community centered on the activity of creating fictional worlds, either for fun or as part of the process of writing, making a tabletop RPG, or similar. All genres and experience levels are welcome. We also serve as an off-topic social space for the /r/worldbuilding community more generally.
Our community is small, intimate, and depth-focused. To this end, we are actively moderated in order to maintain an environment that is pleasant, productive, and conducive to detailed discussion. Because we are a DIY-focused community, we ask that you don&amp;rsquo;t try to get us to make content for you.
A number of our users are experts in particular fields, and we try to be helpful. Feel free to come to us for criticism, or to give feedback to others.
Useful links:
/r/worldbuilding Chat Rules and a summary thereof Regulars List If You Are New To IRC</description></item><item><title>#twodee</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/twodee/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:01:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/twodee/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#trek</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/trek/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:01:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/trek/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#tumblrinaction</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/tumblrinaction/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:01:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/tumblrinaction/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#thewalkingdead</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/thewalkingdead/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:01:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/thewalkingdead/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#TheLastAirbender</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/thelastairbender/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:00:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/thelastairbender/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#OnePiece</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/onepiece/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:00:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/onepiece/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#breakingbad</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/breakingbad/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 22:00:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/breakingbad/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#bettercallsaul</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/bettercallsaul/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:57:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/bettercallsaul/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#AnimeSketch</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/animesketch/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:57:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/animesketch/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#writerchat</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/writerchat/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:54:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/writerchat/</guid><description>Why /r/writerchat
A lot of communities, here on Reddit and elsewhere, have a mythical veil placed around writing. It makes people believe that writing is something fantastical when it is not. Writer Chat is here to help de-mystify that veil and encourage everyone to write, with no crap added on.
We have a strong sense of community and welcome every writer, whether they are new to writing or already a professional. We are not limited to a genre; in fact, we encourage diversity. We hold weekly threads and monthly contests in order to encourage participation in the community.
We have an active chat room where a lot of the writers in the community like to hang out for live feedback in addition to just shooting the breeze. You can check it out at #writerchat on irc.snoonet.org
As for critiquing, a lot of people have complained about the lack of a strong online community to find critique partners. /r/writerchat aims to fill that gap.
A brief history of /r/writerchat
Writer Chat started out as a private chat room on a completely different server than Snoonet, with no subreddit whatsoever. In order to avoid Reddit drama and the works, the chat room was selective with whom it let enter.
After spending some time in the private chat room and developing our friendly neighborhood bot, Ampersand, the majority of the chat wanted to open doors to the public. Writer Chat then created a subreddit and moved to Snoonet, where it became public.
The subreddit was unused and unadvertised for five months until August 2016, when the moderators of the chat room decided to actively seek new members in order to expand. Weekly threads, word war weekends, and monthly contests were then implemented in order to help with expansion.
/r/writerchat goals
/r/writerchat aims to be a community where writers of all kinds can gather and feel at home, whether it be in the chat room or on the subreddit. We ask our members to contribute to the community through critique and through content.
We have only two rules:
Don&amp;rsquo;t be an asshole Don&amp;rsquo;t make us add more rules Just these two rules have been the backbone of our attitudes and have worked well for over a year. Everyone in the community has a similar mindset for respect and helpfulness.
When you join IRC
You&amp;rsquo;ll be greeted by our friendly neighborhood bot, Ampersand. Don&amp;rsquo;t be alarmed!</description></item><item><title>#writingprompts</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/writingprompts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:53:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/writingprompts/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m /u/SurvivorType, Co-Lead Moderator of /r/WritingPrompts along with our founder /u/RyanKinder.
We are a subreddit and chat room dedicated to inspiring people to write! Find a prompt that moves you and respond with a story or a poem.
When I created my reddit account, the sub had around 235 subscribers. That seems like a long time ago now. Since then, we have become a default subreddit with nearly 2.5 million subscribers. That is quite a change.
One thing that has never changed is our commitment to getting people writing. That is what sets us apart from other communities. We don&amp;rsquo;t ask that you be polished. We don&amp;rsquo;t ask that you be published. All we ask is that you get writing. As long as you are willing to try, we want everyone to get involved.
There have been a number of incredible films and narrations created based on prompts and stories. You can find them in our wiki.
We also have a showcase for subscriber favorites at /r/bestofWritingPrompts where you can read some of the best content the subreddit has to offer. Anyone can post a story that would like to help an author get recognition on a prompt response.
We hold many contests throughout the year, culminating on our annual novelette contest. Reading the entries and seeing some of the talent demonstrated is an amazing experience.
Our chat room is a great place to come for both idle chit chat as well as ask for a critique on your writing. It&amp;rsquo;s a warm and welcoming environment where we offer plenty of help and encouragement in your writing endeavors. Discussions can range anywhere from gaming to subreddit policy, and everything in between. Usually it&amp;rsquo;s utter seething madness though. We kinda like it that way.
We hold word sprints in which we see who can write the most words in a set period of time on whatever story they happen to be working on. There is also a side project called Writer&amp;rsquo;s Tabletop™ Fantasy RPG which is a role playing game, now hosted in #wtfrpg.
Our main chat room is always open, so drop by and say hello. We hope to see you there!</description></item><item><title>#shutupandwrite</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/shutupandwrite/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:53:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/shutupandwrite/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#printsf</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/printsf/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:52:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/printsf/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#nosleepOOC</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/nosleepooc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:52:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/nosleepooc/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#books</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/books/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:52:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/books/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#bookclub</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/bookclub/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:52:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/bookclub/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#allnightwriters</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/allnightwriters/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:51:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/allnightwriters/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#100daysofketo</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/100daysofketo/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:48:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/100daysofketo/</guid><description>Can you give us a description of your community: what it&amp;rsquo;s about, what rules you may have and any resources you would like to include? The 100daysofketo community is directly linked to our subreddit: /r/100daysofketo. It was started as a support community for people who are on the keto diet who wanted to commit to 100 days of keto eating. Every 100 days (or so), we start a new round with goal setting, and continue through the 100 days with various challenges and events to keep people motivated to succeed!
Our only rule is don&amp;rsquo;t be an asshole!
What inspired this community? Starting and sticking with a new diet is hard! Especially when it is as restrictive as keto can be sometimes. I know that when I started I felt really overwhelmed. Sometimes, even waiting 10 minutes for a response on a Reddit post was too long to wait and I had fallen off the wagon due to a misunderstanding or over-emotional problem. We started our online community as a way to provide immediate feedback and support and also to foster a more face-to-face interactive community for our users.
What sets your community apart from others? Compared to the other keto communities, we are less about the science and technical aspects and more about the day-in day-out nitty gritty of sticking to the diet. Our channel serves as another line of support for those days when you need assistance and just want to talk to someone who&amp;rsquo;s experiencing the same problems that you may be having. We&amp;rsquo;re all here to help each other!
What have you learned from being a part of this community? Our community and our participants are awesome! We have people participating in our challenges from all over the world and all walks of life. Keto is such an amazing tool for so many people and it&amp;rsquo;s amazing to be a part of their success. Inspiring others has also made me a much more positive person.
Does your community have any traditions or special events? We have themed weekly threads that help keep the 100 days interesting, like Motivational Monday, Workout Wednesday, and Food Friday! We are very user-centric, so if you have a great idea for a new tradition, let us know!!
Helpful Links: Community FAQ and Guidelines Challenge Archive</description></item><item><title>#tea</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/tea/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:48:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/tea/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#stopgaming</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/stopgaming/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:48:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/stopgaming/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#stopdrinking</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/stopdrinking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:45:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/stopdrinking/</guid><description>Can you give us a description of your community?
Stopdrinking is a community for people to motivate each other to control or stop our drinking. We welcome anyone who wishes to join in by asking for help, offering advice from personal experience, sharing stories, or just encouraging someone who is trying to quit drinking or cut down on their alcohol consumption. The general guidelines for participation are in the /r/stopdrinking wiki and there are some specific ones for IRC.
In the #stopdrinking channel we spend much of our time simply chatting and goofing around in a friendly and informal manner. However, the moment someone needs help or to talk seriously all that is needed is to say so and we drop our conversation, listen and try to help. If you are new, expect a bot and maybe a few humans to greet you when you first join but after that we won&amp;rsquo;t pester you. It&amp;rsquo;s left up to you to ask for help or to talk seriously. Otherwise, feel free to join in the banter or even just lurk. There is no &amp;ldquo;right way&amp;rdquo; to participate. The community guidelines can be checked to learn about the few &amp;ldquo;wrong ways&amp;rdquo; which are either discouraged or prohibited. In particular we ask that you do not participate in conversation when you are drinking.
What inspired this community?
The initial inspiration and organization came from /u/Franks2000inchTV. It was based on his vision that everyone feel welcome regardless of how we are trying stop or control our drinking. Today, this inclusive acceptance remains a guiding principle with the current mod team. Inspiration in the community is bolstered by individuals sharing the benefits of sobriety and by sharing new problem-solving strategies and coping methods that individuals develop to help them stay sober. Getting sober and maintaining a non-drinking lifestyle are difficult for many people to understand, as are the issues that arise in pursuing their goal. The majority of adults do not encounter problems related to drinking on a level that many people on SD experience. The world can be an isolating, scary, confusing place for the newly sober person. Members in the community frequently express how safe and refreshing it is to interact with people that &amp;ldquo;get it&amp;rdquo;.
What sets your community apart from others?
In a general sense, the stopdrinking community is unlike many subreddit-based communities due to the care members have for each other.</description></item><item><title>#meditation</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/meditation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:45:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/meditation/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#depression</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/depression/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:44:36 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/depression/</guid><description>Purpose || Channel Operators || Rules &amp;amp; Guidelines || Ban Appeals || Webchat || Links &amp;amp; Resources
If you are experiencing thoughts of suicide or self-harm, please reach out to any of the crisis resources listed below as opposed to using #depression.
We are a peer support community aimed primarily at helping those struggling with depression. This page contains resources to aid those suffering from depression or its related ailments. Please consult these resources if you feel that you need assistance beyond peer help.
One of the most helpful things we can do for one another is listen. As fellow human beings, we understand that life gets difficult. Sometimes, the thing that we need most of all when we are feeling overwhelmed or depressed is a listening ear. When times get tough, we will be here.
What exactly can we do? Our main function is to listen, be here for one another and offer peer support. Whether you’re just having a bad day, issues that are bringing you down, or currently suffering from one of the many variations of depression, we are here for you.
Please understand that although we are here to provide peer support, our channel is not intended as a replacement for counselling from a qualified professional and as such, all information/advice provided by our users is to be considered anecdotal and does not carry any weight. Please note, we are not affiliated with /r/depression – that said, they are a wonderful group and we encourage you to check them out.
back to top
Channel Operators Channel Owner: Duck Channel Admin: Caeli Channel Staff: A_D GhostyOne jglauche toomin tulpa74 void Channel Rules &amp;amp; Guidelines (Last updated: September 17th, 2021)
Please be respectful towards others.
Be mindful of other conversations taking place as multiple concurrent conversations can be either distracting or overwhelming for others. Use discretion when discussing sensitive topics (drugs, vaccines, religion, sex, etc.) in the channel. Keep all discussions concerning politics in #depression-offtopic Do not:
Bring drama into our channel from elsewhere. Likewise, Kindly refrain from bringing drama from our channel into other channels. Post personally identifying information about yourself. Explicitly discuss suicide methods or self-harming. In order to keep our channel safe and welcome for others, we reserve the right to remove any user at any time, with or without notice and for any reason.</description></item><item><title>#cooking</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/cooking/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:44:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/cooking/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#bodyweightfitness</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/bodyweightfitness/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:41:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/bodyweightfitness/</guid><description>/r/bodyweightfitness is a place for all people to find quality discussion about training using your bodyweight as resistance. Though our focus is on bodyweight, you&amp;rsquo;re welcome to discuss any and all training modalities. In order to keep the standard of discussion high, help out newbies, we have a FAQ that is required reading. We also expect you to have put some effort into finding an answer to your questions. /r/bodyweightfitness' userbase is &amp;ldquo;awesome combination of no-nonsense jerks and really friendly people, both of whom generally seem to know what they&amp;rsquo;re talking about&amp;rdquo;. People from all training modalities and levels visit and contribute to the sub. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a the father of two who can&amp;rsquo;t do a single chinup and wants to learn how to do one, or a teenager who is banging out one-armers all day every day and wants advice on how to get to the next level, all are welcome.
We have weekly threads dedicated to moronic questions, members' own routines, learning about training theory, learning about exercise technique, form checks, slip ups and fails in training, and personal achievements. Then we also have a monthly feedback thread where users can give suggestions and feedback on the moderators actions. Alongside this we have an extensive wiki with exercise progressions, bodyweight training info, and much, much more. On top of all of this we have regular AMAs with notable people who have a lot of experience with bodyweight training, like Ninja Warrior contestants, high level gymnastics coaches, and many, many more. Finally, we also occassionally organize challenge months, where we all focus on a single exercise progression, and try to improve our abilities in that. With the support of some of our most knowledgeable users, these are always a huge success.
If you come to our IRC channel, you&amp;rsquo;ll find a bunch of helpful and knowledgeable users ready to talk about anything and everything, or answer questions you have that need answering. We provide eachother with support and sometimes exercise together.
Some quotes, from both the sub and IRC:
&amp;ldquo;Just because it&amp;rsquo;s bodyweight training doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean it&amp;rsquo;s no equipment training.&amp;rdquo; - Saint Emmet, slayer of kipping, fixer of handstands, upholder of the true strict rep
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve hurt both my wrists from furious masturbation. What upper body exercises can I do?&amp;rdquo; - /u/motobrit
&amp;ldquo;Well you can just go fuck yourself.&amp;rdquo; - /u/161803398874989 &amp;rsquo;s second highest rated comment of all time</description></item><item><title>#beer</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/beer/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:41:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/beer/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#yogscast</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/yogscast/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:39:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/yogscast/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#xboxone</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/xboxone/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:39:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/xboxone/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#steam</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/steam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:39:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/steam/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#spaceengineers</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/spaceengineers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:39:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/spaceengineers/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#casualminecrafting</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/casualminecrafting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:38:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/casualminecrafting/</guid><description>Can you give us a description of your community?
We&amp;rsquo;re a group of like-minded dedicated Minecraft players who love to engage in casual gameplay and discussion. The more the merrier.
What sets your community apart from others?
We&amp;rsquo;re one of the few Minecraft servers out there that really try hard to maintain that old-school feeling of community. You may watch YouTubers play on servers like Mindcrack and Hermitcraft and wish you could play on such a rich and inviting server, but they&amp;rsquo;re both very locked down. Well, wish no longer!
What is your goal with this community?
To make sure everyone has fun playing a game that they love.
What is your community (in)famous for?
Selfie threads.
What is the most popular post of all time in the subreddit?
Currently it is this post titled &amp;ldquo;Bull. Shit.&amp;rdquo;
What have you learned from being a part of this community?
That if you build it - they will come.
Does your community have any traditions or special events?
Right now we&amp;rsquo;ve only done it once, but we had a Christmas in July event this year. I hope it can continue on as a tradition.
Every few weeks we host a UHC match (Ultra Hardcore survival) on the weekend. That&amp;rsquo;s always a ton of fun.
Does your community have any associated social media or websites? (facebook/twitter/instagram/etc)
None other than reddit/IRC</description></item><item><title>#RSOC</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/rsoc/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:37:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/rsoc/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#RoosterTeeth</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/roosterteeth/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:37:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/roosterteeth/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#rddt</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/rddt/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:37:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/rddt/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#psychonautwiki</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/psychonautwiki/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:36:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/psychonautwiki/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#pokemoninsurgence</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/pokemoninsurgence/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:36:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/pokemoninsurgence/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#playstation</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/playstation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:35:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/playstation/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#montageparodies</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/montageparodies/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:35:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/montageparodies/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#holidaybullshit</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/holidaybullshit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:35:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/holidaybullshit/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#GTAAPS4</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/gtaaps4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:34:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/gtaaps4/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#GTAA</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/gtaa/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:34:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/gtaa/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#gghazi</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/gghazi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:33:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/gghazi/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#gaymers</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/gaymers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:33:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/gaymers/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#games</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/games/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:31:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/games/</guid><description>Can you give us a description of your community?
The goal of /r/Games is to provide a place for informative and interesting gaming content and discussions. The quick list of rules can be found in the sidebar of the subreddit, and there is a full rules page for more information. What inspired this community?
There were a few mods in /r/gaming that saw a split in the community between people who wanted lighter, quicker, more humor focused content and others who wanted more detailed discussion and informative submissions. We created /r/games to focus on the latter of those two groups. What sets your community apart from others?
We allow a broad range of content while also having fairly strict rules in place to eliminate a lot of the low effort types of content. We also do fairly strict moderation inside the comments to keep discussion on topic. What is your goal with this community?
To encourage quality discussion and informative posts for a broad gaming community. What is your community (in)famous for?
Being a more heavily moderated subreddit that is willing to remove popular submissions or comments if they violate the rules. What is the most popular post of all time in the subreddit?
The highest scoring post of all time in the subreddit is: Buying a PS4 game on your smartphone causes your PS4 to wake up, download the game and go back to sleep. It is not necessarily the best representation of the subreddit though due to the fact that posts that are short and not controversial tend to be the most upvoted but not lend themselves to the best discussion. Do you have any favorite quotes or posts from your users?
Not really - I tend to like the discussion and analysis more, which doesn&amp;rsquo;t really lend itself to singling out a particular quote or post. What do you hope your community gains from this subreddit?
A place to learn about, discuss, and share insights about games and the surrounding community. What have you learned from being a part of this community?
That there is no shortage of people who are willing to criticize and praise every decision that is made, no matter how insignificant. Also, I am constantly surprised with how dedicated certain individuals in the community are for collecting and presenting information.</description></item><item><title>#gamedeals</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/gamedeals/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:31:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/gamedeals/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#EVE</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/eve/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:31:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/eve/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#destinythegame</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/destinythegame/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:31:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/destinythegame/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#CorruptReality</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/corruptreality/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:30:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/corruptreality/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#textfriends</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/textfriends/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:27:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/textfriends/</guid><description/></item><item><title>##muacjdiscussion</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/muacjdiscussion/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:26:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/muacjdiscussion/</guid><description>Can you give us a description of your community: what it&amp;rsquo;s about, what rules you may have and any resources you would like to include? As /r/circlebroke puts it: circlejerk without the satire. Here is where you can complain about trends in makeup or on MUA, rant about anything makeup related, have casual conversations&amp;hellip; really anything.
What inspired this community? Makeup needs to be discussed, and we are just the sub to handle that need
What sets your community apart from others? We are the &amp;ldquo;Text Tuesday&amp;rdquo; of makeupaddiction. Discussion all day, every day
What is your goal with this community? Mainly to hold in depth discussion on makeup and its trends.
What is your community (in)famous for? Discussing makeup
What is the most popular post of all time in the subreddit? A discussion thread called &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not like other girls&amp;rdquo; that focuses on the apparent need to focus on comparing yourself to others and how it is not important.</description></item><item><title>#wet_shavers</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/wet_shavers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:24:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/wet_shavers/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#socialskills</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/socialskills/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:24:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/socialskills/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#sex</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/sex/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:21:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/sex/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#parenting</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/parenting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 21:20:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/parenting/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#longdistance</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/longdistance/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 19:40:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/longdistance/</guid><description>Can you give us a description of your community: We are a support community dedicated to helping couples in Long Distance Relationships! No matter how many miles or kilometers apart, we&amp;rsquo;re all here to reach a common goal&amp;hellip;.to close the distance! Bashing, harassing, trolling, flaming or spamming will result in post removal and a VERY possible ban. What inspired this community? Many people have long distance relationships, and having a place to post and talk about them is a great way for people in LDRs to feel supported. What sets your community apart from others? We&amp;rsquo;re the only community on Reddit that supports those in long-distance relationships What is your goal with this community? To support everyone in a LDR, until they close the distance. (They&amp;rsquo;re welcome to stick around afterward though!) What is your community (in)famous for? Couple selfies from meeting our SOs What is the most popular post of all time in the subreddit? &amp;hellip; A couple selfie, from a lady that surprised her guy by arriving early!</description></item><item><title>#anxiety</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/anxiety/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 19:25:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/anxiety/</guid><description> /r/Anxiety is a supportive community for all things anxiety related. Rules can be found on the sidebar however a brief rundown would be: As a supportive community we take racist, sexist, homophobic, transphobic, ableist or just generally offensive messages seriously and therefore posts or replies with such will be removed. Contact the moderators if you disagree with a message or post being removed. When asking a specific question, it would helpful if you provide your general info(age, gender, type of anxiety, trigger examples, medications (if any), country, no insurance, etc.)
As a rule of thumb: If your anxiety is interfering with how you want to live your everyday life, if it is preventing you from doing things you want to do, or if you now run your life around your anxiety, you should get an evaluation and consider therapy.
We are not psychiatrists or psychologists, and we cannot diagnose you or give medical advice, we can only share our own experiences.
Please no advertising of &amp;ldquo;quick fix&amp;rdquo; products/ideas. If you are wanting to post about something that may be viewed as such message the moderators to run it by beforehand.
/r/Anxiety (Internal) Links
Image Megathread Music Megathread Challenge Archive FAQ Positive Distractions/Pleasant Events External Links
Wikipedia page on Anxiety Finding a Therapist (USA) Free/Cheap/Sliding Scale Services Anxiety UK Anxiety Zone Forum Anxiety Central SA2beXposed (forum for anxiety and depression sufferers) Drug FAQs Free Meditation Clips Free PDF/Workbooks Related Subreddits
/r/socialanxiety /r/agoraphobia /r/panicparty /r/suicidewatch /r/offmychest Read Full List</description></item><item><title>#asianbeauty</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/asianbeauty/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/asianbeauty/</guid><description/></item><item><title>#banished</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/banished/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/banished/</guid><description/></item><item><title>BNC Help</title><link>http://localhost:1313/bnc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 21:43:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/bnc/</guid><description>What is a BNC? A BNC (or Bouncer) is a service which keeps you connected to IRC 24/7. Instead of connecting directly to Snoonet, you connect to the bouncer, which stays connected. The bouncer will send you notifications while away when pinged or messaged and play back messages which you missed while you were disconnected. This way, you can always be part of the conversation.
How do I get one? Once you have a nick registered with NickServ for one month, you are eligible to request a BNC. You need to join ##bnc and type /requestbnc. Then, wait for an operator to approve your request. Usually this is done within an hour or two. When your request is approved, details on connecting to your account will be sent to your account via MemoServ. To read them, type /ms read new
How do I check how long my nickname has been registered? You can use the command /msg nickserv info NICKNAME to check how long you&amp;rsquo;ve had an account. For example:
/msg nickserv info gonzobot What are the restrictions? Your BNC account will be deleted after 30 days of inactivity. All regular Snoonet rules apply to BNC users. How do I connect through my BNC? Instead of connecting to irc.snoonet.org on port 6667, you will connect to bnc.snoonet.org on port 5456 (SSL on port 5457). Set a server password in your IRC client. This password should be &amp;ldquo;username:password&amp;rdquo;, using the credentials sent to you via MemoServ. These are not your NickServ credentials. Then connect to this server. If your bouncer becomes disconnected from Snoonet for any reason, type /znc connect into your BNC window to reconnect it.
Examples of correct connection configurations:
[AndChat] [HexChat] [HoloIRC] [irssi] [Mutter] [Palaver] [Textual] Can I use KiwiIRC with BNC? You can, the link you will need is KiwiIRC, and the connection configuration may be found [here] .
What modules are loaded? Snoonet offers four modules on our free bouncers:
nickserv: /msg Snoo_nickserv help. perform: /msg Snoo_perform help. push: /msg Snoo_push help. simple_away: /msg Snoo_simple_away help. How do I keep myself logged in to NickServ? Take advantage of the nickserv module to keep yourself logged in. Type /msg Snoo_nickserv set password, where password is your NickServ password. Your bouncer will automatically identify your nick for you should you ever reconnect for any reason.
How do I receive notifications on my phone or mobile device?</description></item><item><title>BNC Push Notifications</title><link>http://localhost:1313/push/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 21:43:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/push/</guid><description>What is push? Push notifications are a free, convenient way to get notified when someone sends you a private message, mentions you in a channel, or says one of your highlight words while you are away from IRC. Notifications can be sent to your phone, tablet, mobile device, computer, or web browser.
Requirements In order to receive push notifications, you&amp;rsquo;ll need a Snoonet BNC account, a PushBullet account, and the PushBullet app installed on any devices on which you wish to receivel notifications. Instructions can be found in the setup instructions below.
Setup If you do not already have one, signup and configure your client for the Snoonet BNC
Create a free account with PushBullet.
Install the app on all devices for which you would like to receive push notifications.
Go to your account settings, scroll to the bottom, and select Create Access Token. Copy the generated code, you&amp;rsquo;ll need it in the next step.
Configure notifications to your account using /msg Snoo_push set token [Access Token (from step 4)].
Enable notifications /msg Snoo_push enable and send a test message with /msg Snoo_push test to confirm it&amp;rsquo;s working - you should receive a &amp;ldquo;Test Message&amp;rdquo; notification on your configured device(s).
By default, you will always receive a notification on mentions or PMs. To only receive notifications when away or disconnected, /msg Snoo_push set away_only yes (you are automatically marked away when all clients disconnect).
I&amp;rsquo;d like to see the message in the notification instead of just &amp;lsquo;Highlight&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;Private Message&amp;rsquo; You can turn the privacy option off using /msg Snoo_push set private no
Can I set certain highlight words to receive push notifications on? Yes. In addition to your current IRC nick, you can add and delete words from a highlight list. Please enter one word per command.
To add a word: /msg Snoo_push highlight add [word] To delete a word: /msg Snoo_push highlight del [word] To view your highlight list: /msg Snoo_push highlight list Can I ignore certain nicks? Absolutely. The ignore list works the same way as the highlight list, with one nick per command.
To add a nick: /msg Snoo_push ignore add [nick] To delete a nick: /msg Snoo_push ignore del [nick] To view your ignore list: /msg Snoo_push ignore list I&amp;rsquo;m not receiving notifications Set /msg Snoo_push enabled to turn notifications on.</description></item><item><title>IRC Servers</title><link>http://localhost:1313/irc-servers/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 21:43:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/irc-servers/</guid><description>IRC Servers Network Maintenance Our official timeframe for network maintenance is Wednesdays between 12 AM (midnight) PDT and 2 AM PDT. If needed, general network maintenance, server updates, or bug fixes will be performed during this timeframe. We will occasionally perform urgent maintenance during Sunday nights.
IPv4 and IPv6 Round Robin Connectivity irc.snoonet.org : 6667 (6697 for SSL)
IPv6 only Round Robin ipv6-irc.snoonet.org : 6667 (6697 for SSL)
Asia-Pacific Servers only Round Robin asiapac-irc.snoonet.org : 6667 (6697 for SSL)
European Servers only Round Robin eu-irc.snoonet.org : 6667 (6697 for SSL)
Tor Connectivity Our TOR hidden service is currently unavailable.
Please visit here for more information.
You may access the Snoonet IRC network from any IRC client using any of the above addresses.
We use a signed wildcard certificate from Let&amp;rsquo;s Encrypt. Our SSL fingerprint is:
AB:71:85:E8:60:44:82:FA:B8:77:74:DF:16:D3:B0:95:7A:F3:46:8E</description></item><item><title>Law Enforcement Guidelines</title><link>http://localhost:1313/le-guidelines/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 21:43:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/le-guidelines/</guid><description>Law Enforcement Guidelines What is Snoonet? Data Retention Information How do I make a preservation request? Requests for Snoonet Account Information Emergency Disclosure Requests Foreign law enforcement requests Submit a request These guidelines provide U.S. law enforcement with information about Snoonet, its business and user records, and the legal process required to compel Snoonet to produce information regarding Snoonet users in the course of criminal and civil investigations.
This guide is for informational purposes only. It is not a commitment by Snoonet to take specific action in a given circumstance and creates no contractual obligation.
Snoonet takes the privacy of its users seriously. Snoonet therefore insists on compliance with procedural requirements, scrutinizes requests and legal process for facial validity and legal sufficiency, and objects to legal process, when appropriate. Although Snoonet provides these guidelines, Snoonet does not waive and expressly reserves all available rights and objections and your compliance with these guidelines does not necessarily equate with compliance with the relevant legal requirements.
What is Snoonet? back to top
Snoonet is an Internet Relay Chat Network designed to be used by Reddit communities and users. Snoonet is not affiliated with Reddit, Inc. in any way.
What Account Information does Snoonet have?
• Users are not required to register their nicknames and therefore email addresses are not always available
• If a user does choose to register their nickname, they are required to provide a valid email address to receive a verification code
Data Retention Information back to top
User Account Information is retained by Snoonet in accordance with Snoonet&amp;rsquo;s privacy policy; some information is collected by Snoonet automatically and some information is provided to Snoonet at the user&amp;rsquo;s discretion.
What information exists once a user has deleted their user account?
• Backup records of the account may be available but will vary depending on the time elapsed since the deletion.
How do I make a preservation request? back to top
We do not retain data for law enforcement purposes unless we receive a valid preservation request before a user has deleted that content from our platform or before the Preservation Period expires.
Consistent with 18 U.S.C. § 2703(f), Snoonet will preserve records for up to 90 days pending issuance of legal process if it receives a written preservation request in the form noted below:
Signed by the requesting official; Include the Snoonet user name; Identify the records to be preserved; Identify the time period for which records are to be preserved (maximum 90 days); Confirm that valid legal process is forthcoming; Have a valid return official email address; and Be sent on law enforcement letterhead to lawenforcement [at] snoonet.</description></item><item><title>Law Enforcement Requests</title><link>http://localhost:1313/le-request/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 21:43:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/le-request/</guid><description>Law Enforcement Requests The information on this page is to only be used by law enforcement personnel. For more information on Snoonet law enforcement guidelines, click here.
Preservation Request Requests for Snoonet User Account Information Emergency Disclosure Requests Preservation Request back to top
To submit a preservation request, do the following:
Create a Snoonet Ticket System Account here. The email address field must be your official agency email. • For Reddit Username field, fill in your Title and full name (e.g. Officer Joe Smith)
Send an email to lawenforcement [at] snoonet.org Requests for Snoonet User Account Information back to top
To submit a Snoonet user account information request, do the following:
Create a Snoonet Ticket System Account here. The email address field must be your official agency email. • For Reddit Username field, fill in your Title and full name (e.g. Officer Joe Smith)
Send an email to lawenforcement [at] snoonet.org Emergency Disclosure Requests back to top
To submit an emergency disclosure request, do the following:
Create a Snoonet Ticket System Account here. The email address field must be your official agency email. • For Reddit Username field, fill in your Title and full name (e.g. Officer Joe Smith)
Send an email to LEemergency [at] snoonet.org The request will automatically be assigned an ticket number and an additional form will be sent to you. Fill out the additional form and attach it to the ticket or reply to the automated email with the completed form.</description></item><item><title>Mission Statement</title><link>http://localhost:1313/mission-statement/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 21:43:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/mission-statement/</guid><description>Snoonet is a community hub designed to accommodate and explore community culture. Our network infrastructure is built and maintained by the top communities on the internet, and their most proactive community leaders. Our design is to stay within the times, so we grow with communities. Our goal is simple: Be there with your communities, grow together, and aim for progression at every turn.
The vision is simple. Value your communities. We value the proactive members within communities that develop tools, that create infrastructure within their moderation teams and community as a whole, that aim to simply make things better for those around them. We value the understanding that every community is beautiful, whether our interests conflict or mesh well, the staff team is built around various community leaders with an amazing range of interests. Great deeds go a long way within Snoonet!
This is all for you. We all started as individuals looking to do something more. We value the connections people make with each other and see the vastness for potential each individual has. None of this is possible without you!
Lending a helping hand. In the past, we&amp;rsquo;ve gathered resources from our infrastructure to host community game servers, community events, and staffed large discussion networks to help individuals, and communities to promote awesome ideas they&amp;rsquo;ve had. We pitch in where we can as far as server resources, money donations, and development is needed.
Always be about something positive. When life turns aspects of our everyday lives into something black white and grey, our only option is to seek out the colours, wherever they may be. We will go out of our way to help those within our communities on professional and personal levels. There&amp;rsquo;s always a bigger picture, and the finest details are highlighted by working together.
Welcome the voice of the internet.</description></item><item><title>Privacy</title><link>http://localhost:1313/privacy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 21:43:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/privacy/</guid><description>Snoonet&amp;rsquo;s top priority is the privacy and safety of its users. We take great measures to ensure that everyone&amp;rsquo;s information is secure and that no personally identifying information is available outside of what users wish to share on their own. Our privacy features include the following, and we are constantly evaluating the measures we have in place and implementing additional security as it becomes available.
Privacy Features IPs are hidden by default for all users with umode +x and replaced by a one-way hash in the users host. For unregistered users, their IP will be replaced with Snoonet-hash.IP. Registered users automatically receive a vHost, user/AccountName.
Registration information, including e-mail addresses, are hidden in the user&amp;rsquo;s NickServ info. Users may select to hide additional information as well with /ns help set hide
User channels are not visible in their WHOIS by others and is automatically set on connect with the umode +I. Users may elect to disable this user mode if they wish. Private and secret channels are never displayed to users not also in those channels, regardless of the user mode setting.
Private messages can be restricted by users with a variety of user modes. PMs can be limited to users in common channels, registered users, or a configured whitelist. See User Modes for more information.
What can I do to protect my privacy? Assume everything is public Like anywhere on the internet, the best way to protect your privacy is to assume everything you share is public. While Snoonet does everything it can to protect your privacy, we cannot stop users from sharing information you share with them. Many users log their own channels and private messages, and some do not respect privacy as much as we would like.
Do not share personal information Similar to the above guideline, any personal information you share is subject to the intent of others, malicious or not. While doxxing is strictly against our rules and will be dealt with accordingly, once information is shared online, it cannot be removed.
Register your nickname By registering your nickname with a strong password, only you can use your nick. This ensures that users you speak with know and can verify they are speaking with you and not someone attempting to impersonate you. For more information on registering, please see our NickServ instructions.
Verify staff members If you are requesting assistance in #help or need to contact a staff member, please be sure to provide confidential or sensitive information only to Snoonet Staff.</description></item><item><title>SSL/SASL Fingerprints</title><link>http://localhost:1313/ssl/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 21:43:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/ssl/</guid><description>Snoonet uses LetsEncrypt for its SSL certificate. Due to the high turnover of the certificates, we will not be listing fingerprints here. However, the certificate will always be valid for *.snoonet.org and snoonet.org, and our webpage should share the same certificate. If in doubt, please feel free to ask in #help for a confirmed fingerprint.</description></item><item><title>Terms of Service</title><link>http://localhost:1313/tos/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 21:43:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/tos/</guid><description>By connecting to Snoonet, you are understood to have agreed to these terms. You agree to not use Snoonet to:
(1) Facilitate the downloading/receiving, or distributing of pirated software, movies, games, music, or other materials subject to restrictive copyright law (2) Start, participate in or maintain a botnet, as a client or a botnet director (3) Engage in hateful or harassing behavior, or behavior that is disruptive to other Snoonet users or staff (4) Sell, trade or facilitate the distribution of illicit substances (5) Attempt to circumvent a network ban by changing your ISP-assigned network address (IP), or utilizing a Virtual Private Network (VPN) or other proxy to access IRC (6) Impersonate another Snoonet user or staff member for personal or financial gain (7) Engage in acts of fraud and/or libel To help protect our users from abuse, we run an open proxy monitor which will automatically scan connections to our network for open proxies. If you do not consent to this, please do not use Snoonet IRC.
Snoonet IRC, its operation staff and network operators reserve the right to remove you from the network at any time, with or without notice and for any reason. Certain Internet Service Providers may be restricted from connecting to Snoonet; You may be required to register an account before using our network. Attempts to circumvent network bans may be reported to the applicable ISP at discretion. Failure to adhere to these terms and conditions will lead to prompt removal from the network. While we will make every effort to inform of updates to our terms of service, these terms and conditions may change at any time without notice. In the event of a discrepancy between the initially agreed-upon terms and the terms listed on this webpage, the terms listed on this webpage shall prevail. If you do not agree with these terms of service, please do not connect to our IRC network.
Last updated: August 5th, 2021</description></item><item><title>Tor</title><link>http://localhost:1313/tor/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 21:43:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/tor/</guid><description>We are in the process of bringing back our TOR hidden service. At the moment, we maintain that direct connections to Snoonet from the TOR network are not permitted and ask that you utilize an alternative service to connect, providing that it complies with our rules.
More information will be communicated when possible.</description></item><item><title>Why Snoonet?</title><link>http://localhost:1313/why-snoonet/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 21:43:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/why-snoonet/</guid><description>Snoonet is a network run by redditors, for redditors. Thousands of redditors and hundreds of subreddits already use Snoonet every day. Snoonet provides better security and support because of our focus on reddit users and reddit communities. We serve as a centralized reddit hub. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a casual or serious user, there&amp;rsquo;s a reddit-related channel for you. Snoonet protects your privacy IPs and registration information are visible only to yourself and Snoonet Staff. User channels are hidden from their WHOIS - Other users cannot view what channels you are in unless you explicitly allow it. Private messages can be restricted to only users you want to message you For more information, please see our Privacy and Security page.
Snoonet offers a free BNC (ZNC) Learn about our BNC setup, and policy. Exceptions can be made for users from large subreddits. Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on chats, we offer an always connected service so your nickname stays connected 24/7. Make sure to have a registered nickname before issuing this command: /requestbnc Snoonet offers notifications to your phone, tablet, or mobile device Read more about push notifications to keep up-to-date on IRC when away from your computer. Receive a notification on your mobile device whenever you are pinged or messaged. Reply directly from your device using your client of choice. Snoonet offers subreddit vhosts (*@subreddit/username) You need to have a registered nickname in order to use this command. You must also be in the appropriate subreddit channel with 40 or more users (and be on the access list): Please inquire in #help or open a ticket on our support platform to have your vhost assigned. Snoonet offers custom services and policies catered to reddit and unique to our network. Channel bots created specifically for redditors, which any channel op can /invite. SubWatch - automatically posts subreddit threads, is able to watch private subreddits and announce threads based on keywords in the title. gonzobot - a customized Cloudbot implementation for the communities on Snoonet. Priority enforcement for reddit nicks and channels. Mods of corresponding subreddits get preference for IRC channels, and unlike on Freenode and other networks, you no longer have to use the #reddit-channelname format. Additionally, If you own a username on reddit, you will be able to use the corresponding nickname on Snoonet. Custom webchat built in cooperation with Snoonet, and simple, short-form channel links (https://webchat.</description></item><item><title>Important changes to Snoonet and a partnership with IRC.com</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2018/11/22/important-changes-to-snoonet-and-a-partnership-with-irccom/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Nov 2018 21:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2018/11/22/important-changes-to-snoonet-and-a-partnership-with-irccom/</guid><description>Snoonet is expanding its family and linking up with the new IRC network, IRC.com. For Snoonet users, the only real change you&amp;rsquo;ll feel is an influx of new users with some new cloaks. Staff wise, we are taking on no new opers over the link, and all current staff will remain as they are.
In order to reduce confusion between Snoonet and IRC.com users, a few changes will be made to cloaking and services bots. For most users, these changes will not be noticeable. Note that all these changes may not happen at once, for example, the cloak changes will take a bit more time than the rest.
1. Services will now display a vHost of @services instead of @snoonet/services/*. For example NickServ!NickServ@snoonet/services/NickServ will now simply be NickServ!NickServ@services.
2. vHosts for newly registered users will now either display @irc.com/user/&amp;lt;username&amp;gt; or @snoonet.org/user/&amp;lt;username&amp;gt; depending on which side of the network the user registered on.
3. Default and Snoo-ed nicks will change from SnooXXXXX to GuestXXXXX in order to be more network agnostic. Note that this will also affect how services force-nicks users to protect nicknames. As we understand that a number of channels ban Snoo-ed nicks we are providing a grace period of 7 days to channel operators to update their ban lists.
4. Unregistered users will now display a cloak containing @irc-&amp;lt;hash&amp;gt;.IP instead of @Snoonet-&amp;lt;hash&amp;gt;.IP. Note that this will not affect old bans against Snoonet-.IP cloaks, both types will be checked where needed.
TL;DR: The vHosts services bots use are changing to be more name agnostic. We&amp;rsquo;re making newly registered nicks have vhosts based on the side they registered on. We&amp;rsquo;re changing snoo-ed nicks to Guest. Cloaks are also undergoing changes to be more name agnostic, though bans on old ones will still work.
If you have any questions or concerns please don&amp;rsquo;t hesitate to ask a Snoonet staff member in #help or through our support system located at https://support.snoonet.org/</description></item><item><title>Updates to our Privacy Policy and Services</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2018/05/24/updates-to-our-privacy-policy-and-services/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 May 2018 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2018/05/24/updates-to-our-privacy-policy-and-services/</guid><description>As part of our ongoing mission to serve our users and their communities, Snoonet is implementing some changes to our services and our policies to better reflect our commitment to privacy and security. Specifically, we have made some changes in support of the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), which comes into effect on May 25, 2018.
A brief overview of some of the changes: Our new Privacy Policy will come into effect on May 25, 2018. The revised policy doesn&amp;rsquo;t change the amount of data that we request from you, or impact how we use it.
Instead, the policy provides more details about the information we collect, how we use it, and how we comply with GDPR and other privacy legislation. We have also provided information about how to request the removal of your information from both our IRC network and from services like our support system. As announced yesterday, we no longer offer the Statistics bot as a network service, and have purged all data collected by the service. For more information, please visit the Statistics page. We have updated the messages that are sent to you upon connecting to our IRC network to notify you of our revised Privacy Policy and to seek your consent to these changes. Additional information Privacy and security have been a long-term priority for us at Snoonet, and you can review our Privacy and Security page for additional information about our network&amp;rsquo;s privacy features, steps that you can take to protect your privacy when using our services, and some answers to frequently asked questions.
It&amp;rsquo;s important to be aware that by using our services on or after May 25, 2018, you will be agreeing to the changes outlined in our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these changes, it is important that you stop using our services and take steps to delete your accounts and data. For more information, please consult the policy or contact us through our support system at https://support.snoonet.org.</description></item><item><title>Updates to our Network Rules and Terms of Service</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2017/10/23/updates-to-our-network-rules-and-terms-of-service/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2017/10/23/updates-to-our-network-rules-and-terms-of-service/</guid><description>From: Snoonet Management We&amp;rsquo;ve refreshed our Network Rules and updated our Terms of Service to make things easier to understand. These changes will go into effect as Monday, October 23rd, 2017 at 05:00 GMT. Your continued use of Snoonet after this date and time will constitute your acceptance of these changes.
Important to know We&amp;rsquo;ve not made any major changes to our rules for some time. In fact, the only major changes we&amp;rsquo;ve made are to update some of the information as certain pieces were out of date. We&amp;rsquo;ve also moved certain items to different categories to make an easier read. You will now easily be able to find what you are looking for. Our Terms of Service have been updated to include that we run an Open Proxy Monitor on our network. This information has previously been communicated in our MOTD, shown to all users when they connect to Snoonet. Our Terms of Service have been updated to include how we protect our users from abuse. If you have any questions, we encourage you to join #snoonet and ask your question there.
Thanks for using Snoonet!</description></item><item><title>Snoonet IRCv3</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2017/01/09/snoonet-ircv3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 04:28:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2017/01/09/snoonet-ircv3/</guid><description>Snoonet looks to quickly adopt full IRCv3 capability. We will be developing a new website based around The Lounge to give our website an actual use. We look forward to seeing the implementation of IRCv3. When we get the &amp;lsquo;Okay!&amp;rsquo; we will upgrade all our IRCd software to implement full IRCv3 functionality.
We love IRC IRC is an old protocol that can finally benefit from a face lift to make our modern clients better to use. Please look at the IRCv3 project here and check out our road map. The aim is to upgrade the protocol of IRC to provide better functionality of future developments. We look to see its health and growth remain positive!
IRCv3 Roadmap and Documentation. You can view the progress here: https://github.com/ircv3/ircv3-specifications/milestone/4/ You can view the IRC documents here: http://ircdocs.horse You can view the clients progress here: http://ircv3.net/software/clients.html If you love IRC as well, try to help and pitch in where you can!</description></item><item><title>Moving Forward!</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2016/12/29/moving-forward/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2016/12/29/moving-forward/</guid><description>Moving Forward: Management Changes Welcome our new Network Director We would like to announce the appointment of bloodygonzo as our new Network Director. Bloodygonzo will be responsible for leading and making executive decisions for Snoonet, and will have final say regarding network operations going forward. Many of you already know bloodygonzo from his involvement in Snoonet communities, including the popular network bot, gonzobot. He&amp;rsquo;s distinguished himself as a leader on the network and a champion for increasing community interaction.
Network Leadership Jeff &amp;ldquo;Paradox&amp;rdquo; Sandberg and Shane &amp;ldquo;rdv&amp;rdquo; Allen will be moving to founder roles, retiring from day-to-day operations. They remain as network owners and will provide input and advice to network operations where appropriate, and will continue to play a role in identifying talent and managing staff.
bloodygonzo bloodygonzo has made your network community bot gonzobot! You can see it here and utilize it! He helps new-comers with creating python modules, and has the idea of helping every body that needs something in their community! You can contact bloodygonzo at bloodygonzo [at] snoonet.org for additional information!
What does this mean? We expect to continue to strive towards the goals of our Mission Statement. We&amp;rsquo;ll continue supporting communities as usual, offering network assistance in #help and discussion in #snoonet. Expect updates from bloodygonzo in the New Year as we move forward together.
The new network director will be focusing entirely on the mission statement
Keep it real.</description></item><item><title>Introducing our newest partner - Private Internet Access!</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2016/12/15/introducing-our-newest-partner-private-internet-access/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 23:48:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2016/12/15/introducing-our-newest-partner-private-internet-access/</guid><description>Today, Snoonet is pleased to announce our newest partner - Private Internet Access!
Owned by London Trust Media, Private Internet Access is a provider of consumer VPN services. Their sponsorship couldn&amp;rsquo;t come at a better time as Snoonet continues to grow and develop new, innovative things for its communities!
Private Internet Access have generously donated $25,000 to Snoonet to assist with community building efforts. In addition, they have provided us with 11 new servers which will be equally dispersed among our geographic profile as needed. We are extremely grateful to them for this as it&amp;rsquo;ll allow us to focus on bigger and better things as we finish up with 2016 and head in to 2017!
To celebrate this new, exciting partnership, Private Internet Access would like to give away 5,000 accounts with a free 1-year subscription to the service. These are available on a first come, first serve basis and Snoonet will initially be giving out only 500. If you&amp;rsquo;d like one, fill out our request form.
Check out the news release from Private Internet Access here</description></item><item><title>Privacy Concerns</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2016/12/15/privacy-concerns/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2016/12/15/privacy-concerns/</guid><description>Our Privacy Mission There&amp;rsquo;s been chatter about Snoonet, or myself Shane &amp;ldquo;rdv&amp;rdquo; Allen individually as Snoonet&amp;rsquo;s owner that we log all traffic on Snoonet, which is incorrect. I&amp;rsquo;ll clarify in a short, simple post.
These accusations are false, the logs are fabricated, and targeted to hinder Snoonet&amp;rsquo;s vision. Snoonet does not log messages on its network, or have any ability to spy on its users. The staff all work together to keep each other accountable for their actions. I would be no exception, even as Snoonet&amp;rsquo;s owner.
However the users on Snoonet do keep private logs of the channels they are in, which can not be avoided on any platform.
I personally was doxxed, harassed, threatened, and belittled. However, I&amp;rsquo;ll take one for the team.
I made a post clarifying the situation here on reddit
SSL If you feel your messages are being spied on by your internet service provider, the government, or even on Snoonet&amp;rsquo;s end, please connect to irc.snoonet.org on port 6697. We have a signed certificate for secure authentication. If you need help setting up your IRC client, please ask in #help
Extra security online Snoonet will be working directly with Private Internet Access to provide users with home VPNs for their home devices. This will help increase anonymity if users such are looking for extra security online. The details have not yet been worked out on its partnership, however we look to have the ability to offer free, or reduced payment to users on Snoonet.
If you would like to apply/be in the queue for a Private Internet Access VPN, make a post with this form Snoonet&amp;rsquo;s Mission Statement This is a reminder of what Snoonet is about. Trolls will not sway this vision.</description></item><item><title>Channel Operator Tools</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2016/12/11/channel-operator-tools/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2016/12/11/channel-operator-tools/</guid><description>Channel Verification Process We developed a new tool that channels can enable. When enabled, new users joining a channel will need to verify via the web in order to earn voice status (able to speak in a +m moderated channel) . This will hinder ban evaders and gives staff new options to work with to help deter and stop abusive users. It can be used in event channels with large amounts of users, or used as a tool to force people to make an effort to chat in the channel. The inner workings behind the engine will be explained in detail to the #optalk crew before making it public to all channels as a service on Snoonet.
How it works User joins channel User is sent a link to a secure website to prove they are a real person Magic happens on our backend After visiting the URL sent to them, mode +v is applied to their nickname You may currently request this verification process on your channel by asking in #snoonet or #optalk.</description></item><item><title>Updated Mission Statement</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2016/12/02/updated-mission-statement/</link><pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2016 00:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2016/12/02/updated-mission-statement/</guid><description>Snoonet is a community hub designed to accomodate and explore community culture. Our network infrastructure is built and maintained by the top communities on the internet, and their most proactive community leaders. Our design is to stay within the times, so we grow with communities. Our goal is simple: Be there with your communities, grow together, and aim for progression at every turn.
The Vision is Simple Value your communities. We value the proactive members within communities that develop tools, that create infrastructure within their moderation teams and community as a whole, that aim to simply make things better for those around them. We value the understanding that every community is beautiful, whether our interests conflict or mesh well, the staff team is built around various community leaders with an amazing range of interests. Great deeds go a long way within Snoonet!
This is all for you. We all started as individuals looking to do something more. We value the connections people make with each other, and see the vastness for potential each individual has. None of this is possible without you!
Lending a helping hand. In the past, we&amp;rsquo;ve gathered resources from our infrastructure to host community game servers, community events, and staffed large discussion networks to help individuals, and communities to promote awesome ideas they&amp;rsquo;ve had. We pitch in where we can as far as server resources, money donations, and development is needed.
Always be about something positive. When life turns aspects of our everyday lives into something black white and grey, our only option is to seek out the colors, wherever they may be. We will go out of our way to help those within our communities on professional and personal levels. There&amp;rsquo;s always a bigger picture, and the finest details are highlighted by working together.
Welcome the voice of the internet.</description></item><item><title>Snoonet is a community hub for decentralization!</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2016/10/15/snoonet-is-a-community-hub-for-decentralization/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2016 01:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2016/10/15/snoonet-is-a-community-hub-for-decentralization/</guid><description>Snoonet is pleased to support and work with decentralization! We would like to announce a matrix.org bridge from matrix clients to IRC! Have a gander at matrix.org to see what we&amp;rsquo;re about!
Feel free to try it out as well using Riot.im&amp;rsquo;s client: http://matrix.org/docs/projects/client/riot.html - Be sure to register and select #Snoonet from the drop down!
Our core belief will always focus on security, privacy, stability, freedom of speech, and most importantly the inter-connection of people within your communities. We are happy to be a community hub for all people, of any community to connect to.
What does this mean for me? tldr; Snoonet will be a community hub for decentralized clients within matrix.org.
This means you can be connected to every thing, and everybody. You will be anonymous and secured, and able to access Snoonet.org&amp;rsquo;s IRC communities. Most importantly, you&amp;rsquo;re connected within the matrix securely and can . You will have no limitations on who or what you connect with.
Snoonet will be a community hub for matrix.org users as well as normal IRC, and reddit.com users that connect to us through the OrangeChat bridge.
Take a peek at http://matrix.org/docs/guides/faq.html#what-is-matrix to see what it&amp;rsquo;s about!</description></item><item><title>Privacy and Security - How Snoonet Protects You</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2016/04/28/privacy-and-security-how-snoonet-protects-you/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2016 23:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2016/04/28/privacy-and-security-how-snoonet-protects-you/</guid><description>Snoonet recognizes that privacy and security are key issues for many of our users. It is our goal to ensure that our network is safe and your data is secure. We take a number of steps to protect users' privacy and limit the information that is exchanged on our network. We protect your privacy in the following ways:
IPs are hidden by default for all users with umode +x and replaced by a one-way hash in the users host. For unregistered users, their IP will be replaced with Snoonet-hash.IP. Registered users receive a vHost, user/AccountName.
Registration information, including e-mail addresses, are hidden in the user&amp;rsquo;s NickServ info. Users may select to hide additional information as well with /ns help set hide
User channels are not visible in their WHOIS by others and is automatically set on connect with the umode +I. Users may elect to disable this user mode if they wish. Private and secret channels are never displayed to users not also in those channels, regardless of the user mode setting.
Private messages can be restricted by users with a variety of user modes. PMs can be limited to users in common channels, registered users, or a configured whitelist. See User Modes for more information.
For more information on how Snoonet protects you, ways you can protect yourself, and frequently asked questions, please see our Privacy and Security page. If you have any questions, feel free to ask a staff member in #help.</description></item><item><title>Push Notifications - Never miss an important message again</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2016/03/20/push-notifications-never-miss-an-important-message-again/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2016 02:51:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2016/03/20/push-notifications-never-miss-an-important-message-again/</guid><description>Snoonet is excited to add push notifications, a new way to stay up-to-date when away from your computer. Powered by PushBullet, Snoonet can now send a notification to your mobile device when pinged or PMed while away from your computer. With push, never miss an important message again.
What is push?
Push notifications are a free, convenient way to get notified when someone sends you a private message, mentions you in a channel, or says one of your highlight words while you are away from IRC. Notifications can be sent to your phone, tablet, mobile device, computer, or web browser.
Requirements
In order to receive push notifications, you&amp;rsquo;ll need a Snoonet BNC account, a PushBullet account, and the PushBullet app installed on any devices on which you wish to receive notifications. Instructions can be found in the setup instructions below.
To start receiving notifications, visit our push page. Configuration is easy and only takes a few minutes.
If you need assistance, please ask in #help and someone will assist you.</description></item><item><title>Snoonet Rule Updates</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2016/03/19/snoonet-rule-updates/</link><pubDate>Sat, 19 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2016/03/19/snoonet-rule-updates/</guid><description>Network Conduct Solicitation of services to earn financial gain is only permitted by asking the channel operators. No user is to request money from others. While we understand many are in times of need, please register a gofundme account and state why you are asking for money. Please ask permission from the channel operators. Begging, and contacting multiple users requesting money is a network offense and will be dealt with warnings and removal from the network. Channel Rules Channels may be freely registered on Snoonet, however if subreddit moderators claim an already-registered channel with the same name as their subreddit it shall be granted upon request. Communities that have existed on Snoonet for a long period of time will be granted special exemptions. To prevent hostile takeovers of channels, Snoonet operations staff will work with the entire mod team of the subreddit to find the best solution.</description></item><item><title>Hello SubWatch, Farewell rAnnouncer</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2015/11/29/hello-subwatch-farewell-rannouncer/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2015 01:58:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2015/11/29/hello-subwatch-farewell-rannouncer/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;re pleased to introduce SubWatch, a new bot on our network. Subwatch announces new reddit threads on your channel from subreddits of your choosing, and will be replacing rAnnouncer, which is being decommissioned. You will need to transfer your settings in order for your channel to continue receiving thread alerts.
To switch between rAnnouncer and SubWatch, please take the following steps:
• Type \subreddit list to view rAnnouncer&amp;rsquo;s subreddits.
• /invite SubWatch #channel to have SubWatch join your channel.
• Type $add [subreddit name] for each of the subreddits you wish to transfer.
• /kick #channel rAnnouncer
Please note: you must be a channel operator or halfop to use these commands.
Want to keep a close eye on your subreddit? SubWatch is also capable of announcing threads based on keywords in the title, and can securely announce threads from private subreddits.
You can view the commands and further information here.</description></item><item><title>Change to the Default User Modes on Snoonet</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2015/11/22/change-to-the-default-user-modes-on-snoonet/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2015 02:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2015/11/22/change-to-the-default-user-modes-on-snoonet/</guid><description>We know that many communities are concerned about privacy for their users. To that end, in addition to masking user&amp;rsquo;s IPs, we are now setting +I as a default usermode.
What does this mean? Unless you /umode -I, users will now be unable to see channels that you are in. If you wish -I to persist, please type /msg nickserv keepmodes on
Looking for new channels? If you are looking to find new channels, please visit the communities page.
If you&amp;rsquo;d like your channel to be added to this list, please ask in #help or submit a ticket here.</description></item><item><title>The ducks are migrating...</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2015/10/24/the-ducks-are-migrating/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2015 22:45:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2015/10/24/the-ducks-are-migrating/</guid><description>Something spooky is happening on Snoonet. The ducks must have been scared off by something&amp;hellip;where did they go? Wait&amp;hellip;that looks like meatcat, running for dear life out of #foreveralone! Did they finally chase him off? &amp;hellip;WAIT! Is that a zombie behind him?
It&amp;rsquo;s time to choose: you can .bang the monsters and save your fellow redditors or .bef the monsters and let them eat all of your friends.
Later today, the monster hunt will be released.
Rules: All hunting must be done in a channel with at least 10 other people hunting. If you invite gonzobot into #mycoolmonsterhunting channel and there are not 10 other people actively hunting with you you will be disqualified from the contest. The highest average number of kills will win, so killing monsters in 100+ channels will not help you out at all. If there are other ways people find to cheat the system, those involved will be disqualified. Data analysis will be done before the winners are selected. To qualify in the contest, nicknames must be registered or grouped under a registered account. Prizes: Each winner will be given 2 custom vhost coupons which will entitle them to a custom hostname of their choosing, within reason. Winners can choose to give one or both of these coupons away, or use them both for themselves. If you would like to add to the pot by donating extra Humble Bundle license keys or anything else, please modmail /r/snoonet. We will distribute rewards as evenly as we can between the two winners. We&amp;rsquo;d be happy to promote any additional contributions, including who or what communities have donated the prizes. We will include any updates to the prize list here and anywhere else that the contest is announced, including /r/snoonet and @snoonet.</description></item><item><title>Requesting Support</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2015/10/04/requesting-support/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2015 19:37:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2015/10/04/requesting-support/</guid><description>Going forward, please submit all support requests, including network ban appeals, through our support system.
The support system will allow us to track and respond to issues and inquiries in a more efficient and effective manner.
If you require immediate assistance and are not currently banned from the network, Snoonet staff will be happy to assist you in the IRC #help channel. Please keep in mind that you may be redirected back to the support system to create a request due to the nature of your request.</description></item><item><title>Snoonet Bouncer Access on KiwiIRC</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2015/03/16/snoonet-bouncer-access-on-kiwiirc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2015 15:32:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2015/03/16/snoonet-bouncer-access-on-kiwiirc/</guid><description>We are pleased to announce that KiwiIRC now allows you to connect with Snoonet&amp;rsquo;s bouncer (BNC) service. Web BNC can be accessed at https://webbnc.snoonet.org. This change should enable more users to access our BNC service and use it on a regular basis.
Prawnsalad, creator of KiwiIRC, has been working closely with our development team in order to make this possible. We would like to thank prawnsalad for his effort and his contributions to Snoonet. It is always a pleasure to work with someone who goes the extra mile to improve the user experience for our community.
What is a BNC?
A BNC (or Bouncer) is a service which keeps you connected to IRC 24/7. Instead of connecting directly to Snoonet, you connect to the bouncer, which stays connected. The bouncer will play back messages which you missed while you were disconnected. This way, you can always be part of the conversation. How do I get one?
Once you have a nick registered with NickServ for one month, you are eligible to request a BNC. You need to join ##bnc and type /requestbnc. Then, wait for an operator to approve your request. Usually this is done within an hour or two. When your request is approved, details on connecting to your account will be sent to your account via MemoServ. To read them, type /ms read new Please see our BNC page for more information on Snoonet&amp;rsquo;s BNC service.</description></item><item><title>Update on Snoonet's custom vhost program</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2015/03/12/update-on-snoonets-custom-vhost-program/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2015 20:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2015/03/12/update-on-snoonets-custom-vhost-program/</guid><description>A month ago, we trialed a new service allowing users to request a custom vhost of their choosing, provided the custom host didn&amp;rsquo;t contain any slurs or violate any pre-existing network rules.
Due to consensus among network staff and preparation for potential future network updates, we have decided to end this trial service.
Users will no longer be allowed to apply for custom vhosts, but users who received custom vhosts before today will be able to keep them if they wish to do so. Those with custom vhosts who wish to revert back to a normal @user/accountname vhost should ask in #help and an oper will switch the vhost back.
Community vhosts, e.g. @xboxone/XenoBen, can still be requested for users with flags in any channel which has over 40 members. If you have flags in a snoonet community or chat channel which meets the member requirement, you can request a custom @communityname/accountname vhost by typing /vhost #channel, or asking for assistance in #help.
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our vhost services, you can ask an oper in #snoonet (for general questions) or #help (for technical questions).</description></item><item><title>In Remembrance of Edify</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2015/02/28/in-remembrance-of-edify/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Feb 2015 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2015/02/28/in-remembrance-of-edify/</guid><description>Former long-time Snoonet network operator and reddit moderator /u/edify, remembered as Jarod Coonce by his friends and family, has passed away. He was known for organizing television AMAs, and made the television community on reddit &amp;ndash; from /r/thewalkingdead to /r/breakingbad &amp;ndash; what it is today.
Jarod continued his role on Snoonet as a community manager, bringing countless communities to the network during its formative years. He selflessly helped in any way he could. Jarod single-handedly introduced over 300 users to Snoonet overnight by bringing attention to the #BreakingBad subreddit IRC channel, and bringing Live AMAs to the network from Breaking Bad actors. He truly was a force for change, and he will be missed.
Snoonet extends our best wishes to his family and friends. He will be remembered far after his departure not only by us, but by his fellow moderators and the many people his actions touched.
You can find a link to most of the AMAs edify organized here. One of his favorite charities was A Place Called Home, a safe haven for children and teens in Los Angeles. If you&amp;rsquo;d like to donate in his name, you can do so here.</description></item><item><title>Network maintenance schedule</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2015/01/27/network-maintenance-schedule/</link><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jan 2015 02:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2015/01/27/network-maintenance-schedule/</guid><description>Our official timeframe for network maintenance is Tuesday Night into Wednesday Morning between 9 PM PDT and 2 AM PDT. If needed, general network maintenance, server updates, or bug fixes will be performed during this timeframe. All users will be warned via global notice whenever major network maintenance (rebooting hubs, etc) is necessary. Users on specific servers requiring maintenance will be notified by staff via NOTICE or Private Message atleast 24 hours in advance.
In the event of a newly released IRCd update, or new major vulnerability found with our base operating system, this schedule may be extended include Saturday Night/Sunday Morning.</description></item><item><title>Rule Additions</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2014/07/09/rule-additions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2014 12:30:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2014/07/09/rule-additions/</guid><description>Snoonet operations reserve the right to set temporary and permanent channel modes on any channel or user during attacks, to protect users from harmful spam messages (containing, or not containing), malicious dox (private information), malicious software/web pages, viruses, spam, flood. This rule will not allow for censorship and will only be considered when multiple users become targets for attackers. No private channels will be affected.
Examples of modes: Setting channels to registered users only, modifying flood-toggles for channels, making users only receive messages from others that are familiar in channels, and incorporating the network utility sysop (System Operator) in channels where attacks are popular.
Privacy In addition to the no-dox rule. Posting of information about anybody&amp;rsquo;s private life, school, home, hobbies and interests are prohibited unless publicly shared on the network, or a verbal agreement is given by the individual on which information is shared. Sharing information about yourself is at your discretion, and we will not punish any user for information that you shared in a public chat. Punishment of this rule will result in a ban from the network ranging from one month to permanent dismissal. To sum it up, nothing that a reasonable person would deem as &amp;lsquo;private information&amp;rsquo; may be shared with others. We will enforce it by looking in to how the information can be abused, or used to one&amp;rsquo;s advantage before issuing a warning or ban.</description></item><item><title>BNC, Subreddit VHOST, and powerful user channel modes</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2014/05/07/bnc-subreddit-vhost-and-powerful-user-channel-modes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2014 21:31:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2014/05/07/bnc-subreddit-vhost-and-powerful-user-channel-modes/</guid><description>Want to always have your IRC nick connected? Be able to log in to your IRC nickname and resume your session from any computer, or device, from any any where at any time. We now offer BNC access for our users to connect to. This is a service that keeps an IRC nickname always connected to Snoonet and displays messages and chats you might have normally missed as soon as you log on. The service only allows you to have a bouncer (software: ZNC) connected to Snoonet, but will remain connected to Snoonet forever. If you do not log on the service for one full week, the bouncer will automatically be removed, and you&amp;rsquo;ll have to apply again.
/requestbnc - Type this command in any window on IRC and wait for a MemoServ/e-mail to be sent. You must be registered with NickServ to obtain access. Big fan of a certain subreddit? Want a subreddit vhost? All you need is ChanServ access to the subreddit&amp;rsquo;s channel! User vhosts mask your address as *@subreddit/username /vhost #subredditchannel - Only subreddits with 45 users or more in the channel will be accepted. This is to deter creating a subreddit or channel and having any mask desired. New Powerful IRC Modes Our IRC sofrware now allows powerful channel modes to be set to control user population, spam attacks, or simply making your IRC chat easier to read and manage. Check out the channel mode list here! We&amp;rsquo;ve provided some documentation, but if you need more assistance feel free to ask us in #help on Snoonet.
Client Modes to make IRC easier Again, our IRC software now allows for powerful usermodes to be set (/umode +modeshere) with features that can help the busiest of moderators and those wanting more privacy. Check out the user modes here! If you need any help, feel free to ask us in #help on Snoonet</description></item><item><title>Snoonet will be turning 2 on Apr 28!</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2014/04/07/snoonet-will-be-turning-on-apr-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2014 20:01:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2014/04/07/snoonet-will-be-turning-on-apr-/</guid><description>On Apr. 28, 2014 Snoonet will be turning 2 years old! Many of the top 50 subreddit&amp;rsquo;s well respected mods have made a name for themselves as staff on the network. Alongside a few reddit admins that operate behind the scenes, we&amp;rsquo;d like to thank the subreddits and the users of Snoonet for calling our IRC network their chat home.
What makes us unique? We are the first and only IRC network welcoming community oriented chats for reddit.com - We were created by rdv and Paradox who at the time was a reddit.com admin looking to give more to the community. We have an API backend to allow subreddits to easily configure and set up a chat on the network for their subreddits, bringing live chat straight from the threads.
For our second birthday we&amp;rsquo;d like to give back! Visit us in /r/Snoonet and post a thread with idea(s) we can offer to the users!
As of today, our top 10 consistent IRC communities are:
#reddit (Owners: Paradox, rdv)
#Games (Owners: Deimorz, Pharnaces)
#news (Owner: douglasmacarthur)
#f1 (Owners: Kreius, Vilkku, opiates)
#sex (Owner: Elderthedog)
#subredditdrama (Owner: MillenniumFalc0n)
#TechSupport (Owner: Mikee)
#android (Owner: IAmAN00bie)
#bicycling (Owner: Wiggee)
#anxiety (Owner: aperson)
Wildcard Event Channel:
#redditsquaredcircle (Owner: LegaleseFalcon)</description></item><item><title>NickServ AJOIN</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2013/12/08/nickserv-ajoin/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2013 19:25:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2013/12/08/nickserv-ajoin/</guid><description>This post is a PSA about a NickServ module we&amp;rsquo;ve recently enabled that will allow you to be auto-joined to a list of channels you&amp;rsquo;ve set upon identifying. This should be especially useful to webchat users due to the lack of client-side auto-join. To add a channel to your autojoin list use /msg nickserv ajoin add #channelname
To delete a channel from your autojoin list use /msg nickserv ajoin del #channelname
To see the channels currently on your autojoin list you can use /msg nickserv ajoin list
As a reminder, you can get information and help with syntax on any NickServ or ChanServ command by messaging the appropriate service &amp;ldquo;help command&amp;rdquo;. So to see the syntax for the ajoin command you would do /msg nickserv help ajoin</description></item><item><title>Snoonet's birthday</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2013/04/28/snoonets-birthday/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2013 09:39:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2013/04/28/snoonets-birthday/</guid><description>Snoonet IRC network is 1 year old today - first live on 28th April 2012.
We&amp;rsquo;ve had some stability issues in the early days, but things have smoothed out nicely over the year.
Today we are host to over 70 active reddit communities, over 1000 regular users and 12 servers.
Here&amp;rsquo;s to IRC and the future!</description></item><item><title>01/14/2013 - Gaming, Webchat, Network News</title><link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2013/01/14/gaming-webchat-network-news/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2013 10:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2013/01/14/gaming-webchat-network-news/</guid><description>IRC News On Wednesday, Jan. 16 we will be issuing patches and features for the Snoonet Webchat. We are creating a backend for channels to be managed through a webpanel which will be the alpha stage for reddit/other communities' users to remotely set up/modify/view/update their community&amp;rsquo;s IRC channel access lists and settings, including ban lists and invex lists. For other IRC networks out there, check out www.kiwiirc.com as the developer has a lot of goals and a lot of options available to bring a live webchat to your network.
We will be creating a few customized IRC bots that will offer a variety of options for different types of communities.
Some examples will be a VIP-Ask Me Anything robot which will moderate the channel, and accept questions for VIPs to answer directly. The system will work by users submitting a question, and a moderator will approve the question. The questions will remain in a queue until the user is voiced, the bot states the question and the VIP and the user have a short period of time to ask and answer questions before moving on. All questions, answers, and conversation will be compiled in to a markup post which can easily be posted (or automatically) to a reddit thread where the Ask Me Anything thread may possibly continue.
A channel protection bot for channel operators/moderators to utilize and change the settings of to set a &amp;lsquo;bad words&amp;rsquo; type filter list, where they may set punishments for bad words, phrases, links, etc. The bot will also have options to control punishing flooding/repeat lines/repeat offenders, as well as manage the ban lists. This is for channels that grow in size and need moderation while operators/mods aren&amp;rsquo;t around. For those familiar with our network bot &amp;lsquo;sysop&amp;rsquo; - it will be a user controlled/managed bot controlled by channel mods.
While the above may be boring/uninteresting to some,
Games Our network co-founder Paradox and network operator, Ricin will be hosting a large-scale Minecraft server for users to play on. More news will be posted about it as they will require help in moderating the server/keeping an eye on things. If you have any suggestions for other games you&amp;rsquo;d like hosted, feel free to contact us in SnoonetGaming, /r/irc or e-mail support [at] snoonet.org.
We have the resources to host multiple game servers, and will be hosting these servers while we code and produce the competitive gaming tournament aspect of Snoonet.</description></item><item><title>#gnulag</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/gnulag/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/gnulag/</guid><description>GNU/Lag Warning: This channel contains content that is not suitable for users under 18 years of age. IRC channel Can you give us a description of your community: what it&amp;rsquo;s about, what rules you may have and any resources you would like to include?
It&amp;rsquo;s a hangout for programmers and sysadmins. Lurking is disallowed, that&amp;rsquo;s pretty much the only non-obvious rule.
What inspired this community?
LMR is a shit channel.
What sets your community apart from others
Diversity. Where a lot of communities are topical, we&amp;rsquo;ve got all sorts of nerds talking about all sorts of interesting things. Not necessarily computer related, either.
What is your goal with this community?
Make IRC great again. Take over snoonet. What is your community (in)famous for?
Sending matrix users to /dev/null. Hating rollerblades for NO REASON AT ALL (oh we have reasons). THOSE REASONS ARE BULLSHIT Do you have any favorite quotes or posts from your users?
&amp;ldquo;I think my room mate is calling his mother while showering.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;SEEK FILE&amp;rdquo;
What have you learned from being a part of this community?
A ton about programming, linux, even hardware. That weebs are people too, just like me and you.
Does your community have any traditions or special events?
Shamtober. It&amp;rsquo;s cooler than Spooktober. Sending hand pics to Volkor Does your community have any associated social media or websites? (Facebook/Twitter/Instagram/etc)
https://gnulag.net/
https://t.me/gnulag
https://thecum.zone/</description></item><item><title>#greece</title><link>http://localhost:1313/community/greece/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://localhost:1313/community/greece/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>