<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Staff on Snoonet</title>
    <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Staff on Snoonet</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://snoonet.org/staff/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Paradox</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/paradox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/paradox/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>noeatnosleep</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/noeatnosleep/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/noeatnosleep/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m /u/noeatnosleep. Most people call me nens. It&amp;rsquo;s easier to type. I&amp;rsquo;m the LTM Liason and an Operations Manager for snoonet. I often help organize community events, work with newer users in #help, and assist people with network issues. I&amp;rsquo;m connected almost all the time, and if you ever want to chat, just shoot me a message! (/msg noeatnosleep hi)
I&amp;rsquo;ve been on snoonet from the beginning, but I&amp;rsquo;ve been on IRC for many years. I&amp;rsquo;ve been an IRCop on other networks, but I&amp;rsquo;ve found my home here. Snoonet is filled with folks that I enjoy being around. I&amp;rsquo;m often in #reddit, #politics, #srotd, #showgoat, #random, #games, and a bunch of private channels.
Personally, I love motorcycles, history, and tech. I moderate a bunch of related subreddits, but some of my favorites are /r/gadgets , which I am head moderator of, /r/motorcycles, /r/bikebuilders, /r/hackedgadgets and /r/ThisDayInHistory . I also run a little website that has some neat reddit tools and bots and related things on it: http://noeatnosleep.me. Check it out and give me feedback! I&amp;rsquo;m constantly updating it. Feel free to shoot me an email at noeatnosleep@snoonet.org if you need anything!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duck</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/duck/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/duck/</guid>
      <description>Duck (duck@snoonet.org) Hello all, Duck here! Thanks for using Snoonet!
I&amp;rsquo;m part of the operations team, being primarily responsible for maintaining our server infrastructure and making sure things are up-to-date, as well as assisting the staff team with rule &amp;amp; guideline enforcement across the network as needed. I&amp;rsquo;m also involved with the InspIRCd project, whose software powers this network.
When I&amp;rsquo;m not doing network-related things, I can usually be found chatting in a handful of the communities that Snoonet hosts. If you see me, feel free to say hi, or send me a message at any time using /msg Duck Hi!
・゜゜・。。 ​ ・゜゜\​_0&amp;lt; QUA​CK!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ari</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/ari/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/ari/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DavidLuizsHair</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/davidluizhair/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/davidluizhair/</guid>
      <description>Alright? I&amp;rsquo;m DavidLuizsHair or DLH. Nice to meet you. I&amp;rsquo;m a recently appointed community admin. I&amp;rsquo;ve been on IRC intermittently throughout my teenage years, but have recently gotten back into it about a year ago. I&amp;rsquo;ve been on snoonet for about 10 months [as of drafting this message] so I&amp;rsquo;m still relatively quite young compared to others in that respect. I&amp;rsquo;m a pretty big sports fan mostly being a fan of football (soccer), formula 1 and intermittently following some NBA as well. In terms of other interests, I&amp;rsquo;m an avid fan of documentaries and I also intermittently cook, with varying results. Music wise I&amp;rsquo;m all over the board, I&amp;rsquo;m open to new kinds of music although various types of Indie, metalcore and rock tend to be my jam. Use /query DavidLuizsHair if you ever need any network help and I will do my best to help you. I go in phases of reading where I either read intensively or I don&amp;rsquo;t read at all, some of my favourite books include &amp;ldquo;To Kill A MockingBird&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;The Stranger&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;The Guest&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;By The Waters of Babylon.&amp;rdquo; Some of my favourite subreddits include /r/penmanshipporn, /r/soccer, /r/nba, /r/London and /r/BritishProblems .
The following statements below are compiled impressions of what IRC-ers who have interacted with me before describe me.
This is what my profile would look like if Ari created it: &amp;ldquo;Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m DavidLuizsHair. I have like 70 nicknames on Snoonet, most of them animals for some reason. According to Meow_Mix, I like dog gifs and sportsball. Sportsball is the best. I&amp;rsquo;m going to recruit channels to Snoonet that are already here! GO SPORTS, DO THE THING, SCORE THE GOAL!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;DavidLuizsHair i just remembered i had a dream about you. o.0 You took over the world dressed like a KFC bucket.&amp;rdquo; - f5184
&amp;ldquo;If you weren&amp;rsquo;t here I&amp;rsquo;d be fully clothed&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;yes, and if I wasn&amp;rsquo;t here, you&amp;rsquo;d be breaking and entering&amp;rdquo; - owlet
&amp;ldquo;DavidLuizshair used confusion, it was super effective. DavidLuizsHair hurt itself in it&amp;rsquo;s confusion&amp;rdquo; - linuxdaemon
This is what my smile looks like as described by noeatnosleep: http://www.reactiongifs.com/r/gddy.gif
This is the pic Meow_Mix uses to describe me with: http://24.media.tumblr.com/tumblr_m5tqqzDnrt1qet66oo1_500.png
Well, if you&amp;rsquo;ve made it this far. Have a pasta guide: http://pastafits.org/pasta-dictionary/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jameson21</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/jameson21/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/jameson21/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Jameson21. I&amp;rsquo;m a mod over at /r/ProtectandServe and help run #protectandserve. Come join us sometime.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/mike/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/mike/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Mike.
You can verify my identity on the network with the client certificate fingerprint 5f354892970d867aafe9256a1155160d.
If you need to e-mail me, you can contact me using mike [at] snoonet.org.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phase</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/phase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/phase/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ThatOneRoadie</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/thatoneroadie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/thatoneroadie/</guid>
      <description>Heyo! I&amp;rsquo;m ThatOneRoadie, also known as Thor or TOR, from Denver, Colorado, USA. I&amp;rsquo;m one of the Senior Network Operations Staff here at Snoonet, responsible for the upkeep and maintenance of our network of servers. It&amp;rsquo;s a responsibility that changes on a daily basis, encompassing things such as monitoring network routes, upgrading and maintaining our IRC Daemon on all of our hub and leaf servers, commissioning and decommissioning servers on the network, stress testing new servers, and load balancing the users on the leafs that are active. At any given time, I&amp;rsquo;m responsible for the chat network used by over 4500 people simultaneously.
The team of Network Operations Staffers here at Snoonet maintain over 13 Client Leaf servers, and a number of hidden hub servers operating as the backbone to our IRC network. The leaf servers are in many geographically diverse locations, from Los Angeles, USA, to Dublin, Ireland, and even servers in Singapore (clearly you&amp;rsquo;ve never been to Singapore). We strive to keep these servers up-to-date with the latest security and software updates, protecting our users from any breach of data.
I, personally, maintain a number of servers for the Snoonet network, as well as a set of 16 blade servers and a 10TB SAN (Storage Area Network) in my home lab environment. In my free time, I tinker on this home lab with various virtual machines on an enterprise Cisco network. When I&amp;rsquo;m not doing that, I&amp;rsquo;m a student pilot here in the Denver area, working on my Private Pilot&amp;rsquo;s License.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>linuxdaemon</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/linuxdaemon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/linuxdaemon/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m linuxdaemon on Snoonet. I&amp;rsquo;m mostly working in the background, keeping snoonet and its userbase secure. I&amp;rsquo;m mostly active as a member of the dev team, but I&amp;rsquo;m generally around for any community issues that may arise.
I can be reached on IRC via PM /query linuxdaemon or via email at linuxdaemon@snoonet.org
Outside of Snoonet, I am a Computer Science student, currently studying for my bachelors.
My keybase proof can be found here including my client SSL fingerprint</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ricin</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/ricin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/ricin/</guid>
      <description>Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m ricin. I own and operate one of the servers for Snoonet, as well as run some bots (Charlize, etc). I&amp;rsquo;ve been on IRC since 1993 and have been with Snoonet since the beginning. You can find me almost everywhere. Say hi if you see me!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>weylin</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/weylin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/weylin/</guid>
      <description>Hi I&amp;rsquo;m Weylin!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ScarletAngel</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/scarletangel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/scarletangel/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greenish</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/greenish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/greenish/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Greenish and frankly I&amp;rsquo;m on IRC too much for my own good — guess that&amp;rsquo;s how I got this gig, though.
If I&amp;rsquo;m not skulking about the network I&amp;rsquo;m probably studying, fighting the urge to buy some stupid old hardware that no one cares about to do even stupider things with, or suffering the effects of temporary self-inflicted sanity loss due to the previously mentioned activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>nalixor</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/nalixor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/nalixor/</guid>
      <description>Hey, I&amp;rsquo;m /u/nalixor. I&amp;rsquo;ve been a Snoonet regular for about two years now. I first arrived on Snoonet as a lowly user. I pretty much stuck to the #games channel, and made a great many friends whilst there. Soon after that I became a /r/Games moderator.
I went through some tough times, and my friends on Snoonet and my duties as a moderator helped keep my mind off my problems, and helped me work through them, so I have always wanted a way to give back. I finally have an opportunity to give back to the Snoonet community that has made me laugh, made me cry, and helped me develop some lifelong friendships.
Some info about me: I&amp;rsquo;m 30 years old, I&amp;rsquo;m a graphic designer and I have two of the cutest cats in existence. The brown and tan one is called Toru, and the white and ginger one is called Yuuji. I&amp;rsquo;m a massive nerd; I&amp;rsquo;m really into videogames, gadgets (I also mod /r/Gadgets ), cars, TV shows, music and movies. I&amp;rsquo;m on IRC a lot, so feel free to drop by #games and say hi. :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>void</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/void/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/void/</guid>
      <description>Photography. Software Engineering. Caffeine. Sketching. Cocktails. Beards. Animals.
Feel free to ask me about my Small Dog.
🤙🏻</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>leonthemisfit</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/leonthemisfit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/leonthemisfit/</guid>
      <description>hi i&amp;rsquo;m leon and i go QUACK QUACK QUACK</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A_D</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/a_d/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/a_d/</guid>
      <description>Ohai, I&amp;rsquo;m A_D, also sometimes known as Roy_Mustang or A_Dragon.
You can find me in a whole lot of channels, usually I&amp;rsquo;ll be active in #casualconversation and #aspergers, but I do pop up elsewhere pretty often too, I&amp;rsquo;m always in #help and if I am around I will be pinged by any message in that channel. In my free time I like to play games like Factorio, RimWorld and MineCraft, browse Reddit or sit around writing client scripts of varying complexity. I&amp;rsquo;m happy to be PMed at any time, you can do so with /query A_D or /query Roy_Mustang If you&amp;rsquo;re not sure which, drop into #help and have a look at the user list, or better yet, ping me in #snoonet, A_D or Roy_Mustang will always ping me, no matter my nick. You can also e-mail me at A_D@snoonet.org
If you&amp;rsquo;re not sure that you&amp;rsquo;re talking to me, you can whois me, I will always have a staff vhost and will almost always be connected using a client certificate with the fingerprint 42E8 817B B764 0649 7E47 398B A9A0 A434. you can check this in my whois;
* [A_D] has client certificate fingerprint 42e8817bb76406497e47398ba9a0a434
Otherwise, if you really need to verify its me, you can get me to PGP sign something. My public key is on keybase.io if you want to verify something I gave you, you can do so at keybase.io/verify, just paste the text into the block and hit the verify button.
 -----BEGIN PGP SIGNED MESSAGE----- Hash: SHA256 Here is a message for you to verify. This key is owned by me, A_D, A_D@snoonet.org and is listed on https://keybase.io/a_d I sometimes go by the aliases Roy_Mustang and A_Dragon This message can be verified on https://keybase.io/verify or by using my public key My client certificate has the fingerprint 42E8 817B B764 0649 7E47 398B A9A0 A434 My public key has the fingerprint 8707 71C4 2D4B 9BC4 7F27 3F76 C242 F3DD 220F A945 This message was written on Tuesday, March 20, 2018 at 06:47 AM, GMT+2 -----BEGIN PGP SIGNATURE----- Version: GnuPG v2 iQIcBAEBCAAGBQJasJJ/AAoJEMJC890iD6lFfIIQALCUvY8RSZDXfAQEfpTvMBD2 c9gWaenUVffNk5M9zlORymkQI3Cs8IyWEb86c9dcPf+PsKpP4dNDnELITb3VFMBS S84pdyZrxPAfmlID7Cj02G7xE4AQp5RU5ct89Dqz23FXv44+LP0RWk9VDVpBZC5F Q4ZZjdun88Nua/1pERyn54vTxEdZwo7vOVYWZd5zJh65PnKHrKuOt8cK8oMEr3Vo DyyV1Qb7TaWGCnFnP+qnERbrcD0r9mPbmkAVLjqmG66tTy95P5rKosN13T3gvSvB 4GayTzbBTZdQPJz1TWAoBnh+e27Yx/tvzDOrklSx4q+u0xfhhLSGGGIJJhhckXYn OmhgibdnMBeOzJu3uhUYLhelz/3IJMxzc9CnS9a63Do9AFwQMaFqf+MvZd1mxYux UCmJe7KQhJcJQPeJ5zz4caTn7XbiV/BfGvdn6vbPY5Iqc75k8IbrSm+r/uGaHIJG VfYSxGTUvXIJm4WWOvp94gIFKt9wOeACklsdxqUS/5fjswdGVj3gPjn/cyN071Dc bppw/JJhkdIg7X9bmi1KtW6pIlOeqcjQgSCyVLf7VHJ0POEKXsLgtpf06HukYSpz 9Gq4P1lWc6nXAYYAnj9js6+z9RT6m+Xtg7ezsqSP9aMQJBdaLGb4GqYOEUZ+Jnh6 0iHQA20d7kL69JoUsIJe =8JG9 -----END PGP SIGNATURE-----  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Max-P</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/max-p/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/max-p/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>jotun</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/jotun/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/jotun/</guid>
      <description>Hello, I&amp;rsquo;m jotun, a software engineer living in sunny California.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been using IRC - and coding things for IRC - for nearly 20 years. You might&amp;rsquo;ve heard of my game, Idle RPG. If not, you can check it out in #idlerpg on Snoonet!
I discovered Snoonet about a year and a half ago and thought it&amp;rsquo;d be fun to work with a network that combined two of my favorite things - IRC and reddit. Since joining, I&amp;rsquo;ve had some really wild experiences and met some amazing new friends.
If you like to code, or are interested in learning to code, stop by #programming and say hello!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Altdelete</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/altdelete/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/altdelete/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Madbrad200</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/madbrad200/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/madbrad200/</guid>
      <description>Hi,
I&amp;rsquo;m Madbrad200 - or just Brad! I&amp;rsquo;m usually using this nick or some variation of [word]brad200. If you need me for something, I can be found pretty much everywhere but I mostly chat in #Psychic, #textfriends or #mnfh. Feel free to also send me a pm with /query Madbrad200 Hi! or /msg Madbrad200 hi :D
About me: I&amp;rsquo;m from the UK (specifically Leicester, which is definitely not northern), I love art, music (primarily grime), politics, history, flags and just generally learning about weird things. I&amp;rsquo;m also particularly fond of interactive fiction but I haven&amp;rsquo;t wrote much of anything in a few years.
p.s I hate tea
me irl: https://imgs.xkcd.com/comics/team_chat.png</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shadeblast</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/shadeblast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/shadeblast/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zowlyfon</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/zowlyfon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/zowlyfon/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name is Zowlyfon. I am a Free Software enthusiast studying Computer Science in the UK. I mainly develop and maintain custom software for Snoonet, as well as test out experimental ideas.
I am mainly active in #linuxmasterrace and I can also be contacted in #snoonet or via PM.
My email address is Zowlyfon@snoonet.org</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>diss</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/diss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/diss/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>duk242</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/duk242/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/duk242/</guid>
      <description>Aloha! I am duk242
I&amp;rsquo;ve been on IRC for about 20 years now (Snoonet since 2017).
I chill in the #techsupport, #programming, #technology and #games channels for the most part.
IRL I&amp;rsquo;m an Aussie who likes games, gadgets and casual programming.
Feel free to say hi! I&amp;rsquo;m always up for a random chat about tech support, games or whatever.
– duk242</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>flotwig</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/flotwig/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/flotwig/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m flotwig. You might have heard me called flotty, flotsam, Just Wiggy™, or thotwig.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been on IRC since 2007 or 2008 and I&amp;rsquo;ve been on Snoonet since week two of its existence. Nowadays, I&amp;rsquo;m a more active IRCer than I am a redditor.
My favorite channels are ##PartyMansion, #safefromparadox, and #idlerpg.
Back in the day, I operated an IRC server for Snoonet. Now, I operate several smaller non-IRC servers. I run:
 Statistics: A bot which collects and computes various statistics about users. Status: A beta Snoonet status monitor, so you don&amp;rsquo;t have to ask &amp;ldquo;is it just me?&amp;rdquo; next time you can&amp;rsquo;t connect. Unfortunately not quite finished because we are still transitioning over to Anope. Various internal systems, including mail and DNS for irc.snoonet.org.  I strongly believe in Snoonet&amp;rsquo;s ability to sustain growth for the future. We&amp;rsquo;ve come from being ecstatic at having a hundred users to regularly seeing bursts of over three thousand. At the time of this writing, we have 1,462 independent, user-created channels and 2,698 users online&amp;hellip; at 10 AM on a Sunday. Things are good and they&amp;rsquo;re getting better.
 flotwig  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>iownall555</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/iownall555/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/iownall555/</guid>
      <description>Greetings! I am iownall555.
I typically hang out in #linuxmasterrace and a bunch of other channels and have an interest in Linux, FOSS, gaming and programming (primarily Python and a bit of Perl, C and recently Kotlin). Feel free to ask me for help in person if you need it or join #help if your query is specifically network related.
I have a website located here that contains my programming projects among other things. Furthermore as I use PGP my key can be found on Keybase or on my website under the &amp;ldquo;About&amp;rdquo; section.
[12:08:33] »» [iownall555] is a level 5 enchanted Snoonet Staff of +3 spam-reduction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>nekosune</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/nekosune/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/nekosune/</guid>
      <description>My favorite subreddit is /r/snoonet and /r/lgbt </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>viv</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/viv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/viv/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m the resident pl0x bot. While not saying variants of pls and pl0x, and hot, I am usually talking life, work, music, sports and everything else on multiple channels, with #casualconversation being the channel where you&amp;rsquo;ll find me the most active. IRL, I am a web applications developer and an operations engineer.
Oh, and sorry to burst your bubble. I&amp;rsquo;m not Vivian or Vivienne.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rdv</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/rdv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 08:55:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/rdv/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>linuxdaemon PGP</title>
      <link>https://snoonet.org/staff/linuxdaemon/pgp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 21:43:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://snoonet.org/staff/linuxdaemon/pgp/</guid>
      <description> -----BEGIN PGP SIGNED MESSAGE----- Hash: SHA256 Keybase Proof: I hereby claim: - -I am linuxdaemon on snoonet. https://snoonet.org/staff - -I am linuxdaemon on keybase. https://keybase.io/linuxdaemon - -I have a public key whose fingerprint is 6BA9 FA94 713C 0CE7 A6DE F3F6 54D8 57A6 E89C 03E4 - -I have a client SSL certificate whose fingerprint is 33BA AA09 71A7 A1CA A46C 91C4 7369 03C3 - -I have a client SSL certificate whose fingerprint is BB1E 0E89 1077 0B0B 5387 1F52 1BA5 1531 - -The above SSL fingerprint can be verified on IRC by checking my WHOIS info /whois linuxdaemon To claim this, I have signed this proof with the aforementioned key, yielding this cleartext signature -----BEGIN PGP SIGNATURE----- Version: GnuPG v2 iQIcBAEBCAAGBQJY8JtPAAoJEFTYV6bonAPkKWMP/RljSYJmsoA6mA6FqNLU30gB l6aplfMPL9rH7+qcwXjDOje+jR/sIApGWZoSwb9D85GvrrAsrq/92iJI52BdRp82 B8wSE4zQ3MY4YaXJiYgrzVv2Mlq62BaqU7yLPfnwu9yLVEanLTmCv262RDDhqvE9 FCntY7JGMrS+GtXE1Wb4ZZO5RNItEbF+Q191Gv1zo/b1Yo58H435GGo3u88zGy0T ZtSsAJO7jlF7y1bZoR3xrXG8qLaRpJFRCK4XPntpQ8opfN3cpec0/Zp3OP3QuTMO ZdTeV5D0i6rOCGrdMU/JsMaoTlPcYgGR06H9bjIhJ+QYYZv8GBMFgNCMDlzAR6eI GMqnMI8p1PrCwOBVGQtYjZOhhzeF6dFPKxCr/EfPB58Rs+jWHU+XpHCkzeN/MsHC +9tsotZ2nynKYF9pDcgaOympfywRkReLnZ9Jz1fcLa9kgVyjtDQOpjlMEZQfPDuA FgRcw1LpRpKXCYdvAWhOzy4IlaIhTFugrDCxufNs7LXB9/uyIK+iDS/jdHaz8NmR FjzG4xMsLIB7JAPTawsYJ1IL/8RZvuI31FzF7k4QpRpBm0yTBUYfvDbnrdjjEVRA 3rM0NgFbFi4Q2FfKxKIoruv19lScFW9AiiiK30fArf6Mpc4I0kZ1OFXh9qPRQTJg zshEzL7YAg5g9zsDLBnY =4V5f -----END PGP SIGNATURE-----  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>